<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xml:lang="">
<script/>
<channel>
<atom:link href="https://michael833.github.io/tbbfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<title>The Big Broadcast</title>
<link>https://michael833.github.io</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>No © 2009</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:summary>The Big Broadcast </itunes:summary>
<description> WAMU's The Big Broadcast </description>
<webMaster>na ()</webMaster>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name/>
<itunes:email>na</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<itunes:category text="History"/>
<itunes:category text="Leisure">
	<itunes:category text="Hobbies"/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

<!--
Macro: Place <p>, </p>, and <br /> , delete extra line spaces, then highlight text, then Alt + =
^ and reg exp for <p>
$ and reg exp for </p>
Alt =, then Alt -

https://michael833.github.io/tbbfeed.xml



&lt;	<	less than
&gt;	>	greater than
&amp;	&	ampersand 
&apos;	'	apostrophe
&quot;	"	quotation mark



<item>
<title>October 29, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/803 - October 29, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>

<item>
<title>October 22, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/802 - October 22, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


-->



<item>
<title>October 15, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/801 - October 15, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Shepherd Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; A doctor has increased his life insurance to $100,000, feeling that he may be killed. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates April 16, 17 and 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:156, and 13:15)
0:45:00 - Tribute to Dick Bertel   The Golden Age of Radio     Dick Bertel and Ed Corcoran sit down with Vincent Price. (Original air date November, 1972. Station WTIC. Running time 14:05)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Medicine Man”   The law is the star of the show. (Original air date April 28, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:20)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: Dewey-Stassen Presidential debate – 1948
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Crazy”  Has there been a homicide or not? Detective Friday must uncover the truth.  (Original air date August 30, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:59)
2:00:00 - The Weird Circle  “The House and The Brain” An evil spirit kept alive 400 years haunts a house.  (Original air date July 15, 1943. NBC network. Running time 24:48)
2:30:00 - Stroke Of Fate   What if Queen Marie Antoinette had survived the Reign Of Terror? (Original air date October 25, 1953. NBC network. Running time 25:02)
3:00:00 - Suspense   “The Lodger”.   The story of a very unusual “lodger.” Is he really Jack the Ripper? (Original air date February 14, 1948. CBS network. Running time 58:30)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 8, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/800 - October 8, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 8 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Laird Douglas-Douglas Of Heatherscote Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired as a bodyguard for a very unique client. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates April 12 and 13, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:46, and 13:46)
0:30:00 - The Phil Harris-Alice Faye Show    Phil decides to take drastic steps to get the attention of the New York press. (Original air date February 05, 1950. NBC Blue network. Running time 26:06)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Bear Trap”  A little bit of harmless boasting turns sparks confusion and jealousy… and danger. (Original air date April 21, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:38)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospecitve: Hubert Humphrey – 1948 Democratic Convention speech
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big In-Laws”  A gang of truck hijackers are striking frequently, and randomly, seemingly without a pattern.  (Original air date August 23, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:16)
2:00:00 - Richard Diamond, Private Detective  A fake spiritualist is taking advantage of a wealthy family, and Detective Diamond is going to prove it.   (Original air date September 10, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:19)
2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries   “The Lonely Sleep”. A lonely window trimmer invents the ideal mannequin…and she’s so lifelike too!  (Original air date September 25, 1945. CBS network. Running time 29:40)
3:00:00 - Radio City Playhouse  “Long Distance”.   Jan Miner gives a tour-de-force performance in this gripping drama, as a wife of a convicted murderer who tries to stay his execution by telephone. (Original air date July 03, 1948. NBC network. Running time 28:07)
3:30:00 - Favorite Story  “The Legend of Sleepy Hollow”.  Washington Irving’s classic tale about schoolmaster Ichabod Crane and the headless horseman. (Original air date May 29, 1948. NBC network. Running time 27:03)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>October 1, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/799 - October 1, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 1 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Laird Douglas-Douglas Of Heatherscote Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired as a bodyguard for a very unique client. Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates April 9, 10 and 11, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:24, 13:18 and 13:13)
0:45:00 - The Heartbeat Of Broadway  “The Story Behind My Fair Lady” (February, 1959. American Heart Association syndication. Running time 14:22)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Saludos”  Sheriff Dillon must bring three men back to Dodge on horseback — to identify which one of them is a killer. (Original air date April 14, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:31)
1:20:00 - Lum and Abner    The boys plan to dress up like ghosts to scare the widow Jessup out of Lum’s house. (Original air date October 06, 1943. NBC Blue network. Running time 11:31)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Winchester”  Is an older man’s death the result of suicide or murder? Detective Friday and his partner look for answers.  (Original air date August 16, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:20)
2:00:00 - Screen Directors Playhouse  “The Big Clock”.  A classic noir story of a crime reporter who is on the trail of a big murder story, but he can’t reveal the murderer.  (Original air date July 08, 1949. NBC network. Running time 25:52)
2:30:00 - Creeps By Night   “Those Who Walk In Darkness”. Peter Lorre and Boris Karloff team up to inspire terror with this tale of a blind man, his desperate wife and an unscrupulous doctor.  (Original air date April 25, 1944. ABC network. Running time 29:26)
3:00:00 - Best Plays   “Arsenic and Old Lace”.   Original Broadway cast members Jean Adair and Boris Karloff reprise their roles in this screwball mystery black comedy.  (Original air date July 06, 1952. NBC network. Running time 58:17)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 24, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/798 - September 24, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The La Marr Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny’s aborted vacation and aborted romance takes another turn as he closes in on the murderer. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates March 29 and 30, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:33, 14:32, 14:32)
0:30:00 - Richard Diamond, Private Detective    Dick Powell as Richard Diamond; Diamond is hired to be the bodyguard of Timothy… the seal. (Original air date February 05, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:20)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Rock Bottom”  A retired gunman asks Marshal Dillon to return his gun when Largo Greenland comes to town to kill him. (Original air date April 07, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:56)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: President Dwight Eisenhower – Radio and Television Address to the American People on the Situation in Little Rock, Arkansas, September 24, 1957.  
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Screen”  With the help of the Los Angeles News, the police tackle a new and growing problem, crooked TV repairmen.  (Original air date August 09, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:36)
2:00:00 - The Eternal Light   “Men Of The World”.  It’s now six weeks after Yom Kippur, and Nathan and Ezra think that Rabbi David has too much to atone for. (Original air date December 14, 1958. NBC network. Running time 29:44)
2:30:00 - The Big Show    Tallulah Bankhead hosts a cavalcade of stars, including Herb Jeffries, Oscar Levant, Judy Canova and Jane Russell.  (Original air date April 06, 1952. NBC network. Running time 1:27:22)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 17, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/797 - September 17, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The La Marr Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is on vacation, and love is in the air. Unfortunately, there’s also murder. Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates March 26, 27 and 28, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:33, 14:32, 14:32)
0:45:00 - Hank Williams Centennial: Excerpts from Grand Ole Opry (Original air date November 12, 1949. NBC net, WSM station.); Excerpts from Garden Spot Program (Original recording date 1950, various.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Chicken Smith”  The wife of Chicken Smith is seen with the new owner of the Lady Gay Saloon. What will the chicken farmer do about it? (Original air date March 31, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:59)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Sophomore”  A young boy admits a series of petty thefts. (Original air date July 19, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:17)
2:50:00 - The American Trail   “Dispatch To New York”.   Fictitious reporter Tom Farrell writes the story of the adoption of the Constitution in 1787. (Original air date February 06, 1953. The Ladies’ Auxiliary of The Veterans of Foreign Wars syndication. Running time 14:53)
2:08:00 - Eternal Light    “Let There Be Light“.   A new Rabbi in town must gain the trust of his congregants.  (Original air date September 18, 1960. NBC network. Running time 29:58)
2:40:00 - Suspense  “Leinengen vs. The Ants”  William Conrad gives a tour-de-force performance as Leinengen, a man determined to save his land from relentless, vicious, Brazilian Army ants.    (Original air date August 25, 1957. CBS network. Running time 25:45)
3:05:00 - The Adventures Of Philip Marlowe.  “The Fifth Mask”  There were five masks. One for greed, one for cowardice, one for cruelty and one for deceit. They all covered a murder, but it was the fifth mask that really counted! It uncovered the killer! (Original air dates September 08, 1950. CBS network. Running time 29:16)
3:30:00 - Rogers Of The Gazette.  Will’s editorial urging citizens to “Do It Now!,” has unexpected repercussions for an old man and his horse.  (Original air dates November 18, 1953. CBS network. Running time 30:00)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 10, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/796 - September 10, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Jolly Roger Fraud Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an action-packed mystery about a sunken ship in San Diego. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates March 22 and 23, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:47 and 13:37)
0:40:00 - Lum and Abner   Grandpappy Spears has lost his memory, and the boys of the Jot ‘Em Down store are scheming how to bring it back.  (Original air dates April 14, 1943. NBC Blue network. Running time 12:45)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Saddle Sore Sal”  A visitor come to Dodge from the Texas panhandle, with vigilante justice on her mind.  (Original air date March 24, 1957. CBS network. Running time 25:26)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Late Script”  A $20,000 ransom is demanded for the release of a kidnapped businessman. (Original air date July 26, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:30)
2:17:00 - Suspense  “The Rescue”   Jimmy Stewart stars in this nail-biter mystery about a woman on a hotel ledge is threatening to jump to escape her captors (Original air date April 19, 1951. CBS network. Running time 26:06)
3:00:00 - Destination Freedom   “The Making Of A Man”  Part one of the story of Frederick Douglass, an enslaved man who fought for the freedom of his race. (Original air dates July 25, 1948. Station WMAQ. Running time 28:55)
3:30:00 - Destination Freedom   “The Key To Freedom”   Part two of the story of Frederick Douglass, the famous writer, editor and abolitionist.  (Original air dates August 01, 1948.. Station WMAQ. Running time 29:47)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 3, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/795 - September 3, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 3 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Jolly Roger Fraud Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an action-packed mystery about a sunken ship in San Diego. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates March 19, 20 and 21, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:02 and 13:5813:42, 13:37 and 13:41)
0:40:00 - The Stan Freberg Show,excerpts   Stan interviews a shady character claiming to be a union activist. (Original air dates September 29, 1957. CBS network. Running time 17:41)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Spring Freshet”  Two wanted men kidnap Kitty. (Original air date March 17, 1957. CBS network. Running time 18:57)
1:20:00 - Guest Star, excerpts.   Tony Bennett stars.  (Original air date May 09, 1954. Treasury Department syndication. Running time 11:05)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Set-Up”   The cops break up a burglary ring that involves a hatcheck girl. (Original air date July 12, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:13)
2:00:00 - New World A’ Coming    “Hot Spots, U.S.A.”  The role that racism played in the labor tensions in wartime American industry during the Second World War. (Original air date January 07, 1945. WMCA station. Running time 24:37)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Man Who Threw Acid”   A thinly disguised fictional dramatization of the infamous attack on union organizer and newspaper columnist Victor Riesel.   (Original air date July 18, 1956. CBS network. Running time 23:51)
3:00:00 - The Green Hornet  “Dead Men Talk”   An honest judge suspects Axis spies are infiltrating the city’s labor unions. (Original air dates July 25, 1943. NBC Blue network, WXYZ. Running time 29:01)
3:30:00 - Mr. District Attorney  “The Case Of The Hijacked Worker”. The D.A. fights a scheme of “labor pirating.”    (Original air dates August 19, 1942. NBC Red network. Running time 29:42)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>August 27, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/794 - August 27, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The  Clinton Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny continues his investigation of a fire, and every public official seems to be involved! Parts 4 &amp;amp; 5. (Original air dates March 15 and 16, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:02 and 13:58)
0:30:00 - Halls of Ivy      A young man is upset by a routine genetics lecture.  Ronald Colman and Benita Hume star. (Original air dates October 3, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:34)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Grebb Hassle”  Marshal Dillon is threatened by Billy Grebb, after the Marshal kills his brother. (Original air date March 10, 1957. CBS network. Running time 20:02)
1:20:00 - Accent on Jazz   Chris Albertson interviews Lester Young (Original air date August 24, 1958. WCAU-FM. Running time 5:20
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Love”  A woman has disappeared with her two-year-old daughter. (Original air date July 05, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:02)
2:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks    Mr. Conklin wants to get a jump on the school year, and so he calls school into session on Saturday! (Original air date January 29, 1950. CBS network. Running time 29:26)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Whole Town’s Sleeping”  A serial killer named “The Lonely One” is terrorizing the young women of a small town; Jeanette Nolan stars as a woman who won’t be deterred from her nighttime freedom.   (Original air date  June 14, 1955. CBS network. Running time 24:50)
3:00:00 - Doctor Christian  “Old Battle-Axe”  Jean Hersholt stars as Dr. Christian; a retired Kindergarten teacher finds new purpose living with a family with a very special little boy. (Original air dates November 02, 1949. CBS network. Running time 28:50)
3:30:00 - The Big Show, excerpts     Martha Raye is featured on Tallulah Bankhead’s variety show.  (Original air dates January 14, 1951. CBS network. Running time 17:21)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 20, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/793 - August 20, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Clinton Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny may need some extra help in this confusing mystery about building fraud. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates March 12, 13 and 14, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:45:00 - The Challenge Of The Yukon     “Belle Brady’s Gesture”  Sergeant Preston and his talented dog, King, get involved with Belle, the owner of “The Palace Cafe”. (Original air dates April 20, 1944. Station WXYZ. Running time 14:20)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Colleen So Green”  A beautiful woman comes to Dodge, and men fall all over themselves trying to help her. (Original air date March 03, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:59)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Cliff”  An elder woman has been killed by suffocation, and the suspect is likewise an elder. (Original air date June 28, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:14)
2:00:00 - X Minus One    “The Roads Must Roll”  The engineer union goes on strike, and stops the roads from rolling. (Original air date January 04, 1956. NBC network. Running time (27:43)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Most Dangerous Game”  Orson Welles and Keenan Wynn star in the classic tale of man against man.  (Original air date September 23, 1943. CBS network. Running time 29:57)
3:00:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre    Fred Allen looks at heat waves, summer vacations, and does their own version of “The Hour of Good Intentions”.  (Original air dates June 25, 1941. CBS network. Running time 59:35)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 13, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/792 - August 13, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The  Plantagenet Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired for a private investigation and finds a murdered woman at the start! Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates March 8 and 9, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - The Blue Beetle    “Rounding Up The Payroll Bandits”  The Blue Beetle solves a mystery with new-fangled devices like a mobile phone and mobile recorder. (Original air dates June 26 and 28, 1940. Fox Features syndication. Running time 12:38 and 12:37)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Impact”  Marshal Dillon is suspicious of recurrent “accidents” at a ranch, and an elderly woman is at risk.(Original air date February 24, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:30)
1:20:00 - The Player   “Fate Upsets A Plan”  Paul Frees performs all the roles in this gripping thriller. (Original air date 1948. Capital syndication. Running time 13:47)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Run”  Detective Friday pursues a hit-and-run driver after a deadly attack.  (Original air date June 21, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:08)
2:00:00 - Mr. Chameleon     “The Gold Cigarette Holder Murder Case”   Karl Swenson in the role of Chameleon, a detective on the case of some twisted sisters. (Original air date May 3, 1950. CBS network. Running time 30:00)
2:30:00 - Herb Shriner Time,  excerpts  Raymond Scott and Herb Shriner bring their unique flavor to the airwaves (Original air date September 30, 1948. CBS network. Running time 7:00)
2:38:00 - Suspense  “The Long Night”  Frank Lovejoy stars in a tense and emotional drama about an air traffic controller and the lost pilot he must land safely.  (Original air date July 13, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:26)
3:00:00 - The Silver Theatre  “Stars In Their Courses” Parts 1 &amp; 2.    Helen Hayes stars in this drama about a talented actress and her whirlwind romance, rise to fame, and marital strife.  (Original air dates November 13 and 20, 1938. CBS network. Running time 27:00 and 28:08)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 6, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/791 - August 6, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The  Plantagenet Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired for a private investigation and finds a murdered woman at the start! Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates March 5, 6, and 7, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 14:07, 13:46)
0:45:00 - Radio Almanac   excerpt    Orson Welles and Lucille Ball try their hands at comedy together (Original air date  March 8, 1944. CBS network. Running time 13:00)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Hellbent Harriet”  A widow is spiritual and suspicious — and both help her identify her husband’s murderer. (Original air date February 10, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:59)
1:20:00 - The Bob Hope Show excerpt Bob and guest Rhonda Fleming appear in a skit about a happily married couple, based on their newly released film, “The Great Lover.” (Original air date December 20, 1949. Running time 8:39)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Building”  A wealthy woman is missing.  (Original air date June 14, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:02)
2:00:00 - Dimension X     “Hello Tomorrow”   A story of genetic engineering, and imperfection. (Original air date September 15, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:20)
Lucille Ball performs for CBS’s “Suspense”
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Dime a Dance”.  Lucille Ball stars as dance hall girl who is being targeted by a serial-killer of redheads.  (Original air date January 13, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:22)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “The Man Who Came To Dinner”    Lucille Ball and Clifton Webb star in the classic Kaufman and Hart play about an obnoxious  — famous — houseguest. (Original air date March 27, 1950. CBS network. Running time 52:07)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>July 30, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/790 - July 30, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Fathom Five Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is involved with a sea adventure – drowned fortunes, cryptic clues and recovered treasures! Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates March 1 and 2, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - Philco Radio Time excerpt     Oscar Levant is Bing Crosby’s special guest on his musical variety program. (Original air date  November 10, 1948. ABC network. Running time 15:23) 
Information Please panel from left to right: Oscar Levant, John Kieran, Cedric Hardwicke, and Franklin P. Adams.
0:45:00 - Kraft Musical Hall   excerpt    Al Jolson ribs show regular Oscar Levant for his prior week’s appearance on competitor Bing Crosby’s show; Mr. Levant plays a beautiful piano piece. (Original air date  November 18, 1948. NBC network. Running time 6:01)
0:52:00 - Information Please   excerpt     Clifton Fadiman puts questions to guest panel including Lillian Gish, Franklin P. Adams, John Kieran, and Oscar Levant. (Original air date  October 11, 1938. NBC network. Running time 9:50)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Cold Fire”  A bank teller has been accused of stealing $2000 in gold and is killed while resisting arrest. (Original air date February 3, 1957. CBS network. Running time 20:29)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Imposter”  A young boy has disappeared, and Detective Friday and the L.A.P.D. extend their search across the country. (Original air date June 7, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:58)
1:50:00 - Interview with Pulitzer Prize-winning playwright Doug Wright, of the Tony Award-winning “Good Night, Oscar”.  Murray and Doug sit down to talk about Oscar Levant, his radio time and his unique brand of genius.
2:00:00 - Command Performance   excerpt   Oscar Levant performs George Gershwin’s “Rhapsody in Blue”. (Original air date March 29, 1948. Running time 6:07)
2:10:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes  excerpts   Jack is in New York City preparing to perform at Carnegie Hall; Oscar Levant appears in a parody of the radio quiz show Information Please (Original air date January 17, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 15:51)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Murder In G-Flat”.  Jack Benny stars as a milk-mannered piano tuner faced with an unscrupulous dilemma.  (Original air date April 5, 1951. CBS network. Running time 24:55)
3:00:00 - X Minus One  “Almost Human”    A newly-created robot falls into dangerous hands. (Original air date August 11, 1955. NBC network. Running time 23:50)
3:00:00 - Night Beat  “The Night Is A Weapon”   A man suffers from nyctophobia — fear of the darkness — and is the unwitting patsy of a man with a murder plan. (Original air date February 13, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:14)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 23, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/789 - July 23, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Fathom Five Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny gets involved with a sea adventure – drowned fortunes, cryptic clues and recovered trasures! Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates February 27, 28 and 29, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:44, 13:44 and 13:53)
0:45:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly      Fibber, Doc and the Old Timer find the Old Timer’s uranium mine. (Original air date  August 17, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:04)JACKIE ROBINSON holds National Baseball Hall of Fame induction plaque
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Woman Called Mary”  Buffalo Mary has been beaten up and robbed (Original air date January 27, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:57)
1:20:00 - Jackie Robinson, Hall Of Fame Induction speech (Original air date July 23, 1962).
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Bindle”  Detective Friday goes undercover to expose a narcotics ring. (Original air date May 31, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:15)
2:00:00 - The Adventures Of The Saint  “The Saint” is accused of having a photo that is being used for blackmail, but he doesn’t have the photo! Vincent Price stars. (Original air date November 26, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:30)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Three O’Clock”.  Van Heflin stars in this nail biter; A man is tied to a time bomb, which is set to detonate at 3 o’clock.  (Original air date March 10, 1949. CBS network. Running time 26:45)
3:00:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes    Jack and the gang visit the Marine Corps Air Station in the Mohave desert; Jack is mining for gold. (Original air date November 07, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 28:59)
3:00:00 - Frontier Gentleman  “The Gold Digger”   Kendall meets two gold miners who have struck it rich…and a saloon lady very determined to take it away from them. (Original air date September 28, 1958. CBS network. Running time 24:36)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 16, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/788 - July 16, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Bennett Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is on the trail of an arsonist. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates February 23 and 24, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:5, 14:01)
0:30:00 - Duffy’s Tavern      Slippery McGuire wants Archie to invest in a scheme to put split atoms back together. (Original air date December 21, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:35)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Categorical Imperative”  Marshal Dillon and Chester ride out into a blizzard to re-capture an escaped prisoner who will possibly be turned loose anyway! (Original air date January 20, 1957. CBS network. Running time 22:29)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Mailman”  Mail box theft. (Original air date May 24, 1951 NBC network. Running time 26:17)
1:45:00 - The Quick and the Dead  “Chain Reaction”  Bob Hope is our host in this Peabody Award winning series installment that won for “simplifying and dramatizing a difficult technical subject and…dwelling on the good as well as the evil that lies in the conquest of nuclear energy.” (Original air date July 06, 1950. NBC network. Running time 12:49)
2:00:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly  The first two episodes in a story arc about Fibber, Doc and the Old Timer hunting for uranium.  (Original air date August 13 and August 16, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:14, 14:15)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Report From A Dead Planet”.  A spaceship lands on a beautiful world and finds that all the inhabitants have vanished.   (Original air date July 10, 1960. CBS network. Running time 19:26)
3:00:00 - Hiroshima Countdown    An excellent radio documentary; many people involved with the development and the use of the atomic bomb against Japan are heard, including survivors from Hiroshima and Nagasaki. (Original air date August 9, 1985. MPR. Running time 56:22)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 9, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/787 - July 9, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Bennett Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is on the trail of an arsonist. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates February 20, 21, and 22 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50, 13:50)
0:45:00 - The Smiley Burnette Show      Starring Smiley Burnette – the singing, comic sidekick of Gene Autry, Roy Rogers, and other movie cowboys. (Original air date 1950. Running time 12:03)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Ozymandias”   A land dispute ruffles family feathers.  (Original air date January 13, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:56)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Blast”  A gruesome story about a woman murdered with a shotgun. (Original air date May 17, 1951 NBC network. Running time 26:12)
1:50:00 - Interview with Joe Webb, radio researcher of Suspense
2:00:00 - Suspense  “Donovan’s Brain” Part One.  A determined scientist plans to keep Mr. Donovan’s brain alive — with terrible consequences.  Starring Orson Welles. (Original air date May 18, 1944. CBS network. Running time 26:21)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Donovan’s Brain” Part Two.  The brain takes over; Orson Welles in a masterful performance.   (Original air date May 25, 1944. CBS network. Running time 26:25)
3:00:00 - The Amazing Nero Wolfe    A murder mystery with the imperturbable Mr. Wolfe solving a case of a missing original Shakespearean folio. (Original air date November 30, 1945. Mutual network. Running time 27:55)
3:30:00 - The Green Hornet “The Great Detective”.  He hunts the biggest of all game!  Public enemies who try to destroy our America! — but who is he? Oliver Perry is determined to find out the Green Hornet’s secret identity. (Original air date December 26, 1944. NBC Blue network. Running time 29:21)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 2, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/786 - July 2, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Cui Bono Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder in a small town is a big mystery. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates February 16 and 17, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:45, 13:45)
0:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America      “Declaration of Independence”   The debating, the negotiation, and the personal politics of the days leading up to the signing of the Declaration of Independence. (Original air date January 1, 1936. CBS network. Running time 27:11)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Devil’s Hindmost”   A woman leaves her abusive husband, but it isn’t a clean getaway.  (Original air date January 06, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:44)
1:20:00 - “Gallant Men” recited by Sen. Everett Dirksen (November 30, 1966. Capitol Records. Running time 2:38)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Trio”   Detective Friday attempts to keep the streets of L.A. safe during a busy July 4th weekend. (Original air date July 03, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:51)
2:00:00 - The Pursuit Of Happiness  Burgess Meredith is the master of ceremonies for this variety program, featuring Paul Robeson, produced and directed by Norman Corwin. (Original air date November 05, 1939. CBS network. Running time 27:40)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Sorry Wrong Number”   As requested by Big Broadcast listeners! Perhaps the most well-known episode of Suspense; Agnes Moorehead stars as an invalid woman who overhears on a telephone party line a plot to murder someone. (Original air date May 25, 1943. CBS network. Running time 29:09)
3:00:00 - The NBC University Theatre  “The Adventures Of Huckleberry Finn”   A radio adaptation of Mark Twain’s classic; adventures on the Mississippi with Huckleberry Finn, Tom Sawyer, Jim, and other characters. (Original air date July 23, 1950. NBC Red network. Running time 58:16)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>






<item>
<title>June 25, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/785 - June 25, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Cui Bono Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder in a small town is a big mystery. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates February 13, 14 and 15, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:53, 13:53, 13:52)
0:45:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly      In 1954, the future is bold and bright — with new fangled mobile phones and freeways.  (Original air date April 15, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:26)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Shooting Stopover”   While transporting a prisoner to Wichita, Marshal Dillon and other stage coach passengers are trapped at a way station by robbers who are after a shipment of gold.  (Original air date August 30, 1959. CBS network. Running time 24:06)
1:20:00 - In Person: Dinah Shore (Original air date March 19, 1943. Blue network. Running time 14:53)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Drive” John Iverson is found murdered by a piece of concrete. (Original air date August 14, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:56)
2:00:00 - Mr. and Mrs. Blandings  Mr. Blandings gets lost while driving the family to their new dream home. (Original air date August 25, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:12)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “On A Country Road”   As requested by Big Broadcast listeners! The classic thrilled about an escaped madwoman and a couple out of gas in the dark. Cary Grant, Cathy Lewis, and Jeanette Nolan star. (Original air date November 16, 1950. CBS network. Running time 26:02)
3:00:00 - The Jell-O Program Starring Jack Benny    Jack has purchased a new car…a Maxwell! (Original air date October 24, 1937. NBC Red network. Running time 26:16)
3:30:00 - The Whistler  “Highway Of Escape” A young woman, stuck in the desert with her stepfather, finally kills the old man and drives off with the first motorist passing by. A flight across the desert follows. (Original air date July 09, 1945. CBS network. Running time 26:46)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>June 18, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/784 - June 18, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Mason-Dixon Mismatch Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; two fathers lay claim to a young dead woman. (Original air dates June, 1957. CBS network. Running times 28:41)
0:30:00 - The Marriage      Hume Cronyn and Jessica Tandy star; Ben’s father has arrived for a three week visit, and is a most disruptive influence. (Original air date February 7, 1954. NBC network. Running time 23:40)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Marshal Proudfoot”  Chester’s father is in Dodge to visit his son… whom he thinks is the Marshal.  (Original air date July 20, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:26)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: Coretta Scott King — Solidarity Day Address (June 19, 1968. Running time 7:19)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Drills”  A lot of dogged detective work goes into cracking a difficult case.  (Original air date May 10, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:35)
2:00:00 - The U.N. Story  “Letter From Father”.  “A Human Rights Day Program” produced by United Nations Radio and UNESCO. A father writes a letter to his future child, beautifully delivered by an unsurpassed English-speaking actor, Laurence Olivier. (Original air date 1953. Program #53. United Nations Radio syndication. Running time 14:26)
2:16:00 - Let George Do It  “The Father Who Had Nothing To Say”   The son of a convicted murderer needs the help of George Valentine. (Original air date September 13, 1948. Mutual-Don Lee network. Running time 29:49)
2:45:00 - The Witness “Papa Knows Best”   Robert Young, “America’s Dad”, hosts; J. Carroll Naish stars as an immigrant father who breaks up a gang enticing his son.  (Original air date 1959. Episcopal Church syndication. Running time 14:19)
3:00:00 - The Green Hornet   “Johnny Comes Home”  The Green Hornet helps a father to break ties with a gang. (Original air date August 30, 1945. WXYZ station. Running time 28:04)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>June 11, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/783 - June 11, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Flight Six Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder and mystery in Mexico. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates February 2 and 3, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:40, 13:55)
0:30:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre      Fred Allen tries to interest guest Oscar Levant in his new Broadway show, a spoof of Oklahoma! (Original air date April 23, 1944. CBS network. Running time 22:25)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Tragedian”  Marshall Dillon helps an out-of-work actor in Dodge, meanwhile a guilty man’s brother attempts a jail break. (Original air date October 26, 1958. CBS network. Running time 23:47)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Casing”  The L.A. Police lab deciphers fingerprints, photographs, and powder burns to investigate a suicide. (Original air date May 3, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:28)
1:50:00 - The Heartbeat Of Broadway    “The Story Behind Guys and Dolls”.  A wonderful behind-the-scenes documentary about one of the greatest musicals ever written, with the voices of creators Frank Loesser and Abe Burrows, and original cast members Vivian Blaine, Sam Levene, Stubby Kaye, Robert Alda, and Isobel Bigley. (Original air date 1959. Program #2. American Heart Association syndication. Running time 14:39)
2:00:00 - The Damon Runyon Theatre  “The Idyll Of Miss Sarah Brown”   The story that inspired the musical, “Guys and Dolls”; about the gambler “Sky,” and the missionary Sarah Brown.   (Original air date November 7, 1948. Mayfair syndication. Running time 26:35)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Hitch-hiker”   Orson Welles’ masterful performance of Lucille Fletcher’s classic, about a hitchhiker and a motorist on a lonely road, together. (Original air date September 2, 1942. CBS network. Running time 29:32)
3:00:00 - Biography In Sound  “The Actor”  What is an actor? This question is opined on by notable members of the theater world of the 1950s, including Laurence Olivier, Tallulah Bankhead, Lionel Barrymore, Ethel Barrymore, Arthur Miller, Uta Hagen, Jackie Cooper, Peter Ustinov, and Jose Ferrer. (Original air date March 6, 1955. NBC network. Running time 54:26)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>June 4, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/782 - June 4, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 4 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Flight Six Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder and mystery in Mexico. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates January 30, 31 and February 1, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:40, 13:40, 13:40)
0:45:00 - Lum and Abner      Lum and Abner plan a summer vacation — “back to nature” (Original air date September 8, 1942. NBC Blue network. Running time 12:06)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Cherry Red”  A widow is harassed by her husband’s killer. (Original air date December 16, 1956. CBS network. Running time 21:24)
1:20:00 - D-Day Remembrance, excerpts
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Saint”   A stolen car racket is a complicated mystery. (Original air date April 26, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:01)
2:00:00 - Dangerous Assignment    Steve Mitchell’s first assignment takes him to Sicily in search of stolen relief supplies.  (Original air date July 9, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:22)
2:30:00 - A Date With Judy    Judy has been writing fan mail to actor Joseph Cotten, and thinks he has been writing her back… what will she do when he shows up in her town?  (Original air date February 6, 1945. NBC Red network. Running time 26:08)
3:00:00 - CBS Is There  “Sir Frances Drake Defeats The Spanish Armada”  One of the first installments of this popular series — later You Are There — CBS news reporters cover the events of July 29, 1588. An exciting recreation of the sea battle that saved England. (Original air date August 04, 1947. CBS network. Running time 29:50)
3:30:00 - Escape “Conqueror’s Isle”   Supermen are hiding in the South Pacific. (Original air date March 5, 1949.  CBS network. Running time 29:29)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>May 28, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/781 - May 28, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Duke Red Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; the death of a racehorse raises suspicion. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates January 26 and 27, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - Maxwell House Coffee Time      George and Gracie seek a summer replacement, so they can travel to New York to catch the Louis-Conn fight. (Original air date May 30, 1946. NBC network. Running time 25:23)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Braggart’s Boy”  Tom Cleveland comes to Dodge from back East, and turns into a gunfighter…or does he? (Original air date December 9, 1956. CBS network. Running time 21:31)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Speech”  A young kid has pistol-whipped a doctor and stolen a large quantity of narcotics. (Original air date April 19, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:12)
1:50:00 - The American Labor Hour “Captain Hugh Mulzac”. The story of Captain Hugh Mulzac and members of the integrated crew of the “Liberty Ship,” he captained, the SS Booker T. Washington. (Recorded on January 2, 1943, Running time 14:16)
2:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop   “The Parade”    An anti-war story about a parade down the streets of New York that cannot be seen or heard. (Original air date February 7, 1950. NBC network; San Fransisco origination. Running time 29:43)
2:30:00 - The Adventures Of Michael Shayne; Private Detective   Wally Maher and Cathy Lewis star; Detective Michael Shayne is invited to a party to re-create a murder mystery. (Original air date May 28, 1945. Mutual-Don Lee network. Running time 27:14)
3:00:00 - The Hollywood Radio Theater (The Lux Radio Theatre)  “Battleground”  Excellent war stories about the “Battered Bastards Of Bastogne.” (Original air date December 7, 1954.  NBC network. Running time 53:20)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>May 21, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/780 - May 21, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Duke Red Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; the death of a racehorse raises suspicion. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates January 23, 24, and 25, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:30, 13:38, 13:30)
0:45:00 - Lum and Abner      Lum and Abner plan an elaborate party (Original air date March 11, 1943. Blue network. Running time 11:21)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Tail To The Wind&quot;  A non-violent homesteader is violently bullied. (Original air date November 25, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:14)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Threat&quot;  A man has been attacked and robbed, and knows his assailant, but fear keeps him from cooperating with the police.  (Original air date April 12, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:16)
1:50:00 - Tribute to Jack French, radio historian, excerpts from 2020 interview
2:00:00 - Candy Matson, YUkon 2-8209   &quot;The Eric Spaulding Concert&quot;  Natalie Masters stars as private investigator, Candy Matson; a famous conductor hires Candy to prevent his concert from being sabotaged. (Original air date February 7, 1950. NBC network; San Fransisco origination. Running time 29:43)
2:30:00 - A Day In The Life Of Dennis Day   Dennis writes a dramatic radio program, and then has to play all the parts himself! (Original air date November 14, 1946. NBC network. Running time 25:48)
3:00:00 - The Cavalcade Of America &quot;Check Your Heart At Home&quot;  Shirley Booth stars in a story based on the book, &quot;They Sent Me To Iceland,&quot;. A woman puts aside her dreams of a show business career to volunteer for the Red Cross in Iceland when the war begins. (Original air date December 13, 1943.  NBC Red network. Running time 29:16)
3:30:00 - Broadway Is My Beat Sherman Gates is found poisoned in the loge of a movie theatre, which leads to a murdered photographer. (Original air date December 3, 1949. CBS network. Running time 29:34)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>May 14, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/779 - May 14, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Ricardo Amerigo Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a musical mystery. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates January 19 and 20, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - Life With The Lyons    &quot;Mothering Sunday&quot;  Bebe Daniels and her real-life family star in this premiere British sitcom  (Original air date March 31, 1957. BBC. Running time 30:27)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Pretty Mama&quot;  Hank Marble has been shot in the back, leaving behind a young and pretty widow. (Original air date November 11, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:37)
1:20:00 - Aladdin Lamp With Smilin&apos; Ed McConnell  (Original air date 1937. Syndicated, NBC Orthacoustic transcription.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Little Mother&quot;  A woman has been forging charge slips in department stores for the last six years.  (Original air date October 6, 1953. NBC network. Running time 26:24)
2:00:00 - The Life Of Riley   Riley and the family have big plans to pamper Pam on Mother&apos;s Day — but one by one they fall afoul. (Original air date May 14, 1944. NBC Blue network. Running time 22:25)
2:25:00 - The Hank Williams Mother&apos;s Best Flour Show   (Original air date March 15, 1951. WSM station. Running time 11:33)
2:30:00 - The Lone Ranger    A soldier is shot while deserting to help his blind mother. (Original air date February 16, 1944. Running time 28:25)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre   &quot;Lady For A Day&quot;    A comedy-drama about Apple Annie, a Depression-era street person. Her daughter is arriving from Spain, thinking her mother is a society matron. (Original air date May 1, 1939. CBS network. Running time 30:34)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>May 7, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/778 - May 7, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 7 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Ricardo Amerigo Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a famous violin sparks mystery and danger. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates January 16, 17 and 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:34, 13:34, 13:34)
0:45:00 - Stay Tuned For Terror   &quot;The Man Who Raised the Dead&quot;  Author Robert Bloch&apos;s tale written for especially for radio, about the awesome power and responsibility of reanimating the dead.    (Original air date July 27, 1945. WMAQ station. Running time 13:25)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Brother Whelp&quot;  A gunfighter returns to Dodge after six years, and he finds his old girlfriend married to his brother. (Original air date November 18, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:37)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Friend&quot;  Mr. Gray reports that his wife Hazel has been murdered, but there is something suspicious about the circumstances.  (Original air date April 5, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:58)
1:50:00 - Radio Retrospective: V.E. Day, excerpts
2:00:00 - My Friend Irma  Irma&apos;s boss has purchased a race horse named, &quot;Laughing Boy.&quot; (Original air date June 2, 1953. CBS network. Running time 24:49)
2:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America   &quot;Commencement In Khaki&quot;    A romance about the post-war Army College at Camp Kilmer, New Jersey.  (Original air date January 28, 1946. CBS network. Running time 25:47)
3:00:00 - Murder By Experts   &quot;Summer Heat&quot;    A newly graduated lawyer awakes with a dead body in bed and has a very difficult time getting rid of that body! (Original air date June 13, 1949. Mutual network. Running time 28:33)
3:30:00 - New World A&apos; Coming  &quot;The Meaning Of V-E Day To Negroes&quot;    Oliver Harrington, a foreign correspondent for the Pittsburgh Courier, interviews &quot;average&quot; New York Black Americans.  (Original air date May 20, 1945. WMCA station. Running time 24:59)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>April 30, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/777 - April 30, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Caylin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man is found dead and there are too many suspects. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates January 5 and 6, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:53, 13:45)
0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks    Madison High is holding an auction of some very nice furniture, perhaps Mr. Conklin would care to donate?  (Original air date March 19, 1950. CBS network. Running time 26:13)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Crowbait Bob&quot;  An old man dies and leaves everything to Kitty. (Original air date November 10, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:37)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: 1948 Kentucky Derby with Clem McCarthy (Original air date May 1, 1948. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Trunk&quot;   A divorcee named Josephine Allen has been murdered, and her body found in a car trunk.  (Original air date September 7, 1954. NBC network. Running time 26:11)
2:00:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes.   Jack has sold a broken down horse to Rochester for $4. Rochester&apos;s entered him in the Kentucky Derby! (Original air date April 25, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 29:29)
2:30:00 - Suspense  &quot;Elementals&quot;    Stephen Vincent Benét&apos;s story of primal instinct versus human resolve. Can a man and a woman go without food for one week, and then not fight each other for a crumb?  (Original air date June 12, 1960. CBS network. Running time 24:21)
3:00:00 - Four For The Fifth   &quot;The Laughter&quot;    Fred MacMurray stars in this story of the courage of resilience and evils of complacency.  (Original air date June 17, 1944. Treasury Department syndication. Running time 30:34)
3:30:00 - Mr. Keen, Tracer Of Lost Persons   &quot;The Engaged Girl Murder Case&quot;    Mr. Keen solves a murder case while on horseback! (Original air date November 10, 1949. CBS network. Running time 26:17)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>April 23, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/776 - April 23, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Caylin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man is found dead and there are too many suspects. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates January 2, 3 and 4, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:36, 13:36)
0:45:00 - Radio Retrospective: Dorothy Thompson    An excerpt from an NBC special broadcast, Ms. Thompson reports on Nazi Germany&apos;s invasion of Poland. (Original air date September 2, 1939. NBC network. Running time approximately 10:00)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Dirty Bill&apos;s Girl&quot;  Rose, the card dealer in the Long Branch, plans to kill a man. (Original air date October 28, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:32)
1:20:00 - Symphony Sid, excerpt.   Tito Puente performs in a band remote from the &quot;Birdland&quot; club in New York City. (Original air date September 22, 1952.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Ben&quot;  A man is pulled from his car on a deserted street, robbed, and beaten viciously before his car is stolen.   (Original air date March 15, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:07)
2:00:00 - The Halls of Ivy   Dr. Hall has been asked to recite a poem for an appreciative audience, but is reluctant to participate. (Original air date July 5, 1950. NBC network. Running time 26:47)
2:30:00 -  Will of Stratford    An NBC special program celebrating the 373rd anniversary of William Shakespeare&apos;s birth.  (Original air date April 15, 1937. NBC network. Running time 29:52)
3:00:00 - Suspense   &quot;Make Mad The Guilty&quot;    Hume Cronyn stars as an out-of-work Shakespearean actor who fakes his own death when his wife leaves him for her muscular lover.  (Original air date April 10, 1948. CBS network. Running time 29:22)
3:30:00 - The Lady Esther Screen Guild Theatre   &quot;First Love&quot;    Shirley Temple stars in this modern Cinderella story about a young girl who finds romance, despite her cruel relatives.   (Original air date May 14, 1945. CBS network. Running time 26:39)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>April 16, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/775 - April 16, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Forbes Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; mystery abounds in a NY embezzlement case. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates December 29 and 30, 1955. CBS network. Running times 13:32 and 14:32)
0:45:00 - The Stan Freberg Show     Program number 1.  Comedian Stan Freberg lampoons the entertainment industry, and Las Vegas casinos. (Original air date July 14, 1957. CBS network. Running time 29:40)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Til Death Do Us&quot;    (Original air date October 21, 1956. CBS network. Running time 24:50)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Couple&quot;   A confidence team specializes in victimizing churches and clergymen.  (Original air date February 22, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:51)
2:00:00 - The Raleigh Room    The incomparable Hildegarde visits with special guests Hank Greenberg, Paul McGrath and Jackie Keck. (Original air date October 16, 1945. NBC network. Running time 29:38)
2:30:00 -  The Cavalcade Of America    &quot;Sawdust Underground&quot;   The story of two G. I.&apos;s who escape from Nazi occupied France by hiding as a clown and an acrobat in a circus.  (Original air date September 10, 1945. NBC network. Running time 29:11)
3:00:00 - Suspense   &quot;Crossfire&quot;    Starring three Roberts: Robert Young, Robert Ryan, Robert Mitchum. A murder mystery about a fanatical antisemite. Which of three soldiers committed murder?  (Original air date April 10, 1948. CBS network. Running time 59:30)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>April 9, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/774 - April 9, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Forbes Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; mystery abounds in a NY embezzlement case. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates December 26, 27 and 28, 1955. CBS network.)
0:45:00 - Stay Tuned For Terror   &quot;The BoogeyMan Will Get You&quot;   A psychological thriller about a teenage girl&apos;s suspicions and a bachelor. (Original air date 1945. Station WMAQ)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Gunshot wound&quot;    Revenge exacts a deadly toll. (Original air date October 14, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Radio retrospective: Mercury 7 Press Conference, April 9 1959.
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Cast&quot; Over a dozen men have disappeared without a trace.  (Original air date February 8, 1951. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny    Benny&apos;s traditional Easter Sunday show – he and Mary Livingstone stroll down Wilshire Boulevard in Los Angeles, singing &quot;Happy Easter,&quot; and encountering their friends along the way. (Original air date April 13, 1952. CBS network.)
2:30:00 - The Greatest Story Ever Told    &quot;The Resurrection&quot;    (Original air date April 06, 1947. ABC network.)
3:00:00 - The Great Gildersleeve  Sunrise Easter service and an unexpected blessing. (Original air date April 9, 1952. NBC network.)
3:30:00 - The Six-Shooter     A Big Broadcast Easter tradition; Jimmy Stewart stars as Brett Poinset, and investigates a crisis at Easter Creek. (Original air date April 15, 1954. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>









<item>
<title>April 2, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/773 - April 2, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 2 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Todd Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an expensive tip from an ex-con starts Johnny on the trail of stolen goods, and a murder attempt; Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates January 12 and 13, 1956. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - Take It Or Leave It     Fred Allen and his cast of regulars take on inflation, rationing, and Veronica Lake&apos;s new ‘do; Falstaff Openshaw recites a poem on rationing. (Original air date February 28, 1943. NBC network)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;The Gambler&quot;    A riverboat gambler named Jim Ascombe comes to Dodge to kill Jim Cass (Original air date October 07, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Radio retrospective: Interview with Jack Webb, from 1958 reel to reel tape interview.
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Children&quot;   A mother is missing, and her children are begging for food. (Original air date February 01, 1951. NBC network.)
1:50:00 - Excerpt from Anthology  &quot;The Three Witches of Macbeth&quot;  Alec Guinness stars in scenes from Shakespeare&apos;s Scottish Play. (Original air date February 01, 1951. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Dangerous Assignment  Plans for an improved Nazi &quot;buzz bomb&quot; have been stolen. (Original air date February 24, 1951. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - Eternal Light    &quot;The Passover Of Rembrandt Van Rijn&quot;   The famous painter of Amsterdam is commissioned to paint Moses for the city fathers. He searches for descendants of the biblical figure to use for his model.  (Original air date April 18, 1948. NBC network.)
3:00:00 - The CBS Radio Mystery Theatre      &quot;The Corpse That Would Not Die&quot;  A suspenseful tale adapted from Émile Zola&apos;s Thérèse Raquin (Original air date June 07, 1976. CBS network.)
3:30:00 - Lum and Abner      A haunting we will go! (Original air date October 07, 1943. Blue network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>March 26, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/772 - March 26, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Todd Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an expensive tip from an ex-con starts Johnny on the trail of stolen goods, and a murder attempt; Parts 1, 2 &amp;3. (Original air dates January 9, 10 and 11, 1956. CBS network.) 
0:40:00 - X Minus One    &quot;Martian Sam&quot;   The Los Angeles Dodgers sign a real Martian as a left-handed pitcher. (Original air date April 3, 1957. NBC network)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;The Brothers&quot;    (Original air date September 30, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Tomato&quot;   Friday and the L.A. police track down &quot;The Big Tomato&quot; (Original air date January 25, 1951. NBC network.)
1:50:00 - Interview with Susan Stamberg and Deanna Hackney discussing &quot;Women in the Newsroom&quot; 
2:00:00 - The Cavalcade Of America    &quot;Nellie Was A Lady&quot;   The adventures of Nellie Bly, trailblazer reporter for the New York World, who made an around the world journey in less than eighty days, and forever opened up opportunities for women reporters. (Original air date September 17, 1945. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - Destination Freedom    &quot;The Ballad Of Satchell Paige&quot;   The story of the &quot;greatest pitcher of all time.&quot;   (Original air date May 15, 1949. Station WMAQ.)
3:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks      Sometimes called &quot;The Baseball Uniform Shortage&quot;, Madison High doesn&apos;t have enough funds to have a baseball team this spring, but Miss Brooks has a plan, naturally.  (Original air date March 26, 1950. CBS network.)
3:30:00 - The Adventures Of Philip Marlowe      &quot;The Anniversary Gift&quot;. A rare appearance of William Conrad as Philip Marlowe; Marlowe is hired to retrieve a valuable platinum watch from a corpse.  (Original air date April 11, 1950. CBS network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>March 19, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/771 - March 19, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar  &quot;The Lansing Fraud&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man with a $50,000 policy dies but the cause is suspicious; Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates December 15 and 16, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:40:00 - The Adventures of Jane Arden  &quot;Elevator Murder&quot;  Part One, News reporter Jane Arden is trapped in a crowded elevator with a killer, but who is it? Written by Marianne Prugh. (Original air date January 15, 1941. Webber Productions syndication)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke  &quot;Box O&apos;rocks&quot;    Marshall Dillon must solve the mystery of a faux funeral and a coffin filled with rocks. (Original air date September 23 1956. CBS network.)
1:37:00 - Dragnet  &quot;The Big Dance&quot;  (Original air date January 18, 1951. NBC network.)
2:17:00 - Night Beat  Randy Stone dials his phone at random and speaks to a woman about to be murdered by her insane husband. (Original air date July 31, 1950. NBC network.)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  &quot;Front Page Woman&quot;    Paulette Goddard and Fred MacMurray co-star in this adaptation of the film about two news reporters duking it out for clout in the newsroom. (Original air date January 16, 1939. CBS network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>March 12, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/770 - March 12, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar  &quot;The Lansing Fraud&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man with a $50,000 policy dies but the cause is suspicious; Parts 1, 2 &amp;3. (Original air dates December 12, 13, and 14, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:44:00 - Policewoman  &quot;The Case Of The Scheming Bridegroom&quot;   Based on the adventures of the real New York City policewoman, Mary Sullivan. (Original air date June 29, 1947. ABC network)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke  &quot;Thick ‘n&apos; Thin&quot;    Two old friends begin fighting. (Original air date September 16, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Franklin D. Roosevelt addresses the nation for the first time as President of the United States, excerpt (Original air date March 12 1933. All networks.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet  &quot;The Big Holdup&quot;    Detective Friday and his partner are after a viscous killer known as &quot;The Rattlesnake Bandit&quot; . (Original air date January 4, 1951. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Maxwell House Coffee Time  Gracie is inspired to train Girl Scouts-to-be, as the Girl Scouts celebrate their thirty seventh anniversary. (Original air date March 10, 1949. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - The Whistler  &quot;Married To Murder&quot;   Cathy Lewis and Elliot Lewis star in a twisted tale of the art of murder.   (Original air date September 25, 1944. CBS network.)
3:00:00 - Author Meets The Critics  A discussion about &quot;American Argument,&quot; by Pearl Buck and Eslanda Goode Robeson. (Original air date February 06, 1949. NBC network, WNBC New York.)
3:30:00 - The Railroad Hour  &quot;Spring Is Here&quot;. Gordon MacRae stars in this rare musical adaptation of an even rarer musical by Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart  (Original air date May 12, 1952. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>March 5, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/769 - March 5, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar  &quot;The Cronin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar is pulled in to protect a gorgeous and valuable necklace with diamonds and emeralds, known as the  &quot;Circle Of Fire&quot; ; Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates December 8 and 9, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - The Marriage  Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn star; Elizabeth wants a more meaningful life. (Original air date November 15, 1953.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke  &quot;Belle&apos;s Back&quot;    A woman named Belle has returned to Dodge, after living with a gunman. (Original air date September 9, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Oscar Brand&apos;s Folk Song Festival, excerpt featuring Doc Watson (Original air date 1970. WNYC station.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet  &quot;The Big Break&quot;  As slippery a devil as Friday and Romero have ever encountered. (Original air date December 14, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - You Are There  &quot;The Trial Of Anne Hutchinson&quot;  Puritans put the first American feminist on trial in 1637. (Original air date September 26, 1948. CBS network.)
2:30:00 - The Private Files Of Rex Saunders  &quot;High Dividends Or Shallow Graves&quot;  Rex Harrison stars as a &quot;gentleman detective&quot;.   (Original air date May 30, 1951. NBC network.)
3:00:00 - The NBC University Theatre  &quot;Hedda Gabler&quot;    Ibsen&apos;s classic play portrays hardship and life troubles faced by women during 19th century. (Original air date August 27, 1950. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>February 26, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/768 - February 26, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Cronin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar is pulled in to protect a gorgeous and valuable necklace with diamonds and emeralds, known as the  &quot;Circle Of Fire&quot; ; Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates December 5, 6 and 7, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - It&apos;s Time To Smile, excerpt    Guest Betty Hutton wows the crowd on Eddie Cantor&apos;s show, also starring Rudy Vallee. (Original air date January 27, 1943. NBC Red.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Old Pal&quot;    A man is murdered, and the Wells Fargo money stolen; suspicion circles around a young woman trying to leave town. (Original air date September 02, 1956. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Picture&quot;  Sergeant Friday breaks a vicious Los Angeles pornography ring. (Original air date December 07, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - The Ford Theatre    &quot;A Connecticut Yankee In King Arthur&apos;s Court&quot;   Mason Adams stars. The Mark Twain classic: a satire of chivalry, monarchy, religion, and superstition, celebrating American democratic values and ingenuity. (Original air date October 05, 1947. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries    &quot;Tempo In Blood&quot;  A murderer introduces himself to the murderee, and a piano player plays a wrong note!   (Original air date January 12, 1948. CBS network.)
3:00:00 - What Must Be Done      &quot;Education&quot; Part two.  A special series and fascinating discussion about the scourge of racism in the late &apos;60s, and how it affects public education. Panel discussion lead by Percy Sutton. (Original air date July 8 1968. WLIB Radio, New York.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>February 19, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/767 - February 19, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Henderson Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a death in the exotic locale of… Montana?  ; Parts 4 and 5 (Original air dates December 1 and 2, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - Rogers Of The Gazette    Will Rogers, Jr. stars as newspaper editor in a small town, and has been receiving letters from a mysterious &quot;A. Lincoln&quot;. (Original air date November 11, 1953. CBS.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;No Sale&quot;    Two bullies demand that Kitty sell them the Long Branch Saloon, but she&apos;s not going down without a fight. (Original air date August 26, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - One Out Of Seven    &quot;Equality, A Most Wonderful Thing&quot;.  Jack Webb does all the voices in this program, except for the singing of baritone Joseph James; program explores racial equality in post-war America. (Original air date March 20, 1946. KGO station.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Car&quot;  Someone has been robbing food markets, but not the person who confesses. (Original air date November 30, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - An Open Letter On Race Hatred    Peabody Award winning broadcast written and directed by William N. Robson, detailing the 1940s Detroit race riots. (Original air date July 24, 1943. CBS network.)
2:30:00 - Black Radio: Telling It Like It Was    &quot;Civil Rights and Let&apos;s Have Church&quot;   In the fifties and sixties, Black DJs did more than play music — they were among the first messengers of the civil rights movement. In the second half of the hour, we hear about the importance of religious broadcasting to the Black community.   (Original air date January 1996. PRX.)
3:00:00 - X Minus One      &quot;Dwellers In Silence&quot;  Twenty years after mankind abandoned the Earth, a spaceship from Mars lands. (Original air date November 10, 1955. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>February 12, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/766 - February 12, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Henderson Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a death in the exotic locale of… Montana?  ; Parts 1, 2 and 3 (Original air dates November 28, 29, and 30, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:35:00 - Our Miss Brooks    Miss Brooks tries to get Mr. Boynton to take her out to dinner for Valentine&apos;s Day. (Original air date February 19, 1950. CBS.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Annie Oakley&quot;    A woman&apos;s love is being fought for – at least she claims it is. (Original air date August 19, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Rate Your Mate, excerpt    Host Joey Adams questions a husband and wife team on this radio precursor to the popular TV show The Newlyweds. (Original air date August 5, 1950. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Betty&quot;  A gang of swindlers has selling worthless junk to relatives of dearly departed, using obituaries as their entry point.  (Original air date November 23, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Black Radio: Telling It Like It Was    25th Anniversary Edition, Hour Two: &quot;Jack Cooper &amp; Al Benson&quot; and &quot;WDIA, The Goodwill Station&quot;    A brilliant documentary chronicling the history of African Americans and their representation in radio from the earliest days through the 1940s and 1950s. (Original air date January, 1996. PRX.)
2:30:00 - Let George Do It     &quot;The Eight Ball&quot;   Detective Valentine is mixed up in a mystery involving a dead man — who is also named George Valentine!  (Original air date April 2, 1951. Mutual network.)
3:00:00 - Destination Freedom      &quot;The Heart Of George Cotton&quot;  The story of Dr. Ulysses Dailey and Daniel Hale Williams and their pioneering efforts in heart surgery. (Original air date August 8, 1948. Station WMAQ.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>February 5, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/765 - February 5, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Amy Bradshaw Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates death threats against a famous actress; Parts 4 and 5 (Original air dates November 24 and 25, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:25:00 - Jubilee    Ernie &quot;Bubbles&quot; Whitman as M.C. of this variety show created for black soldiers in WWII, featuring Cab Calloway, Burns and Allen and Nat King Cole.  (Original air date February 14, 1944. AFRS.)
0:55:00 - The Studs Terkel Show    featuring Sidney Poitier  (Original air date October 1, 1959. WFMT station.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Snakebite&quot;    Strangers arrive in Dodge and kill a man’s dog, and revenge is swift. (Original air date August 12, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Mail Call    Ida Lupino, Robert Benchley and Groucho Marx perform a parade of the thriller Double Indemnity. (Original air date August 12, 1956. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Parrot&quot;  Arson in a rooming house covers up a double murder.  (Original air date November 16, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Black Radio: Telling It Like It Was    25th Anniversary Edition &quot;Hour One: &quot;In the Beginning&quot; and &quot;Pride &amp; Enlightenment&quot;    A brilliant documentary chronicling the history of African Americans and their representation in radio from the earliest days through the 1940s and 1950s. (Original air date January 1, 1996. PRX.)
2:30:00 - Freedom&apos;s People      &quot;Contributions To Music&quot; part of  &quot;The Story Of The American Negro.&quot; The music that the slaves brought with them to America, and how it grew.  (Original air date September 21, 1944. NBC Red network.)
3:00:00 - Candy Matson, Yukon 2-8209       &quot;Symphony Of Death&quot;  A famous composer predicts that he is going to die, and leaves a musical trail of clues. (Original air date June 20, 1950. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 29, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/764 - January 29, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Amy Bradshaw Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates death threats against a famous actress; Parts 1, 2 and 3 (Original air dates November 21, 22, and 23, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:40:00 - The Chase and Sanborn Hour <br /> Clark Gable guest stars and goes head to head with Charlie McCarthy.  (Original air date October October 29, 1939. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Lost Rifle&quot;    An upsetting tale of child abuse and the consequences. (Original air date July 29, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Mother&quot;  A newborn has gone missing from the hospital. (Original air date November 9, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - Romance <br /> &quot;The Bear&quot;    A western adaptation of Chekov&apos;s one-act farce of the same name, starring Virginia Gregg and John Dehner. (Original air date November 5, 1955. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Charlie McCarthy Show <br /> W.C. Fields and Charlie McCarthy face off at a barbershop.  (Original air date February 20, 1944. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre <br /> &quot;Kiss of Death&quot;   Victor Mature stars in screenwriter Ben Hecht&apos;s story of innocent gangsters, molls and revenge. (Original air date January 12,1948. CBS network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 22, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/763 - January 22, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Broderick Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar must find a missing woman, who was last seen when she was only 11 years old; PARTS 4 and 5 (Original air dates November 17 and 18, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks <br /> Walter Denton&apos;s radio gives a strange and concerning weather report.  (Original air date October 08, 1950. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Letter of the Law&quot;    Marshal Dillon is forced to evict a reformed gunfighter named Brandon Teak from his land. (Original air date July 15, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Church&quot;  A new member of the congregation receives anonymous letters and phone calls threatening her with murder. (Original air date November 2, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>1:50:00 - The Radio Almanac <br /> Ann Sothern and Orson Welles star.  (Original air date May 17, 1944. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Adventures Of Philip Marlowe <br /> &quot;Red Wind&quot;    A real Raymond Chandler story of double-crossing. (Original air date September 26, 1948. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries <br /> &quot;The Vengeful Corpse&quot;  A woman burned as a witch returns to enact revenge.  (Original air date September 12, 1949. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Eternal Light <br /> &quot;Try Not To Love Such A Country&quot;  Stories from Sholem Aleichem:  A young boy arrives from the old country with many of the traditions from the old country.   (Original air date January 13, 1963. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>3:30:00 - I Was A Communist For The FBI <br /> &quot;Draw The Red Curtain&quot;. Dana Andrews stars as comrade Cvetic, assigned to help the Party take over an actor&apos;s guild.  (Original air date July 06, 1952. ZIV Syndication.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 15, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/762 - January 15, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Broderick Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar must find a missing woman, who was last seen when she was only 11 years old; PARTS 1, 2 and 3 (Original air dates November 14, 15 and 16, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - The Studs Terkel Program <br /> Studs Terkel interviews Martin Luther King, Jr.  (Original air date October 28, 1964. Chicago station WFMT.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Passive Resistance&quot;    A man chooses to solve his quarrels without gun violence, and needs protection. (Original air date July 8, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - Lum and Abner <br /> Lum and Abner look into insurance.  (Original air date February 1, 1945. NBC Blue network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Meet&quot;   Joe Friday has a tense assignment, risking his life going undercover. (Original air date October 26, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - New World A&apos;Coming <br /> &quot;Executive Order 8802&quot;     The history of Executive Order 8802, a temporary end to racial segregation in hiring and in the military during WWII. (Original air date November 5, 1944. New York City station WMCA.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Adventures Of Sam Spade, Detective <br /> &quot;The Lazarus Caper&quot;.  Howard Duff stars as Sam Spade.  (Original air date September 12, 1948. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Beyond Tomorrow <br /> &quot;Incident At Switchpath&quot;   An invasion! Based on the story, &quot;The Sky Was Full Of Ships,&quot; by Theodore Sturgeon.  (Original air date April 11, 1950. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>3:30:00 - Arch Oboler&apos;s Plays <br /> &quot;Lust For Life&quot;.  The story of Vincent Van Gogh.  (Original air date August 16, 1945. NBC network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 8, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/761 - January 8, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 9 Jan 2023 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Lorko Diamonds Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a diamond robbery in Algiers; PARTS 4 and 5 (Original air dates November 10 and 11, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre <br /> Fred Allen&apos;s first show of the 1942 season, with guest star Charles Laughton.  (Original air date October 4, 1942. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Gun For Chester&quot;    Chester fears that someone is out to kill him. (Original air date July 1, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - excerpt from  Duffy&apos;s Tavern    Archie wants to film his life story, and hires comedian Larry Storch to impersonate Hollywood stars to fill out the cast.  (Original air date January 11, 1946. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Grandma&quot;   An elderly woman has been passing bad checks. (Original air date October 19, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - X Minus One <br /> &quot;Nightmare&quot;     Based on Stephen Vincent Benet&apos;s poem, &quot;Revolt Of The Machines&quot;;  a clerk discovers what the computers are planning. (Original air date July 21, 1955. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Big Show <br /> Tallulah Bankhead&apos;s star-studded spectacle with guests Eddie Cantor, José Ferrer, Bob Hope, Jimmy Durante, and music by Meredith Willson.  (Original air date November 19, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 1, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/760 - January 1, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 2 Jan 2023 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> 
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Lorko Diamonds Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a diamond robbery in Algiers; PARTS 1,2 and 3 (Original air dates November 7,8 and 9, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:40:00 - Suspense <br /> &quot;The Thirty-Second Of December&quot;   A gambler buys a watch with many dials, including one that travels through time  (Original air date December 28, 1958. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Pucket&apos;s New Year&quot;    (Original air date January 1, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Quack&quot;   A woman commits suicide after being robbed by a phony Dr. Schulte, owner of the Los Angeles College of Psychotherapeutics. (Original air date October 12, 1950.) NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - Maxwell House Coffee Time <br /> George Burns and Gracie Allen decide to board a returning soldier in their home. (Original air date January 3, 1946. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Quiet, Please <br /> &quot;Rain On New Year&apos;s Eve&quot;    The writer of a horror movie gets in the last word.  (Original air date December 31, 1947. Mutual network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Mercury Theatre <br /> &quot;Hell on Ice&quot;    A gripping dramatization of the true story of a 19th-century expedition to the North Pole, and its terrible fate. (Original broadcast date October 10, 1938. CBS network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 25, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/759 - December 25, 2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - The First Nighter Program <br /> &quot;Little Town Of Bethlehem&quot;   (Original air date December 23, 1945. NBC network.) (Running time 27:46)</p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Duffy&apos;s Tavern <br /> Archie is fed up with the holiday, until he receives a visit from a stranger.    (Original air date December 22, 1948. NBC network.) (Running time 28:56)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> Christmas in Dodge City.    (Original air date December 20, 1952. NBC network.) (Running time 27:53)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - The Six-Shooter <br /> A western &quot;A Christmas Carol&quot; with Jimmy Stewart. (Original air date December 20, 1953, NBC network.) (Running time 28:58)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop <br /> &quot;The Day They Gave Babies Away&quot;   A Christmas story about six orphans who must find news homes. (Original air date December 21, 1946. CBS network.)(Running time 29:48)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America <br /> &quot;A Child Is Born&quot;     An original nativity play, by poet Stephen Vincent Benét. (Original air date December 21, 1942. NBC red network.)(Running time 29:27)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks <br /> &quot;The Magic Christmas Tree&quot;     (Original air date December 25, 1949. CBS network.) (Running time 27:20)</p>
	<p>3:30:00 - Philco Radio Time <br /> Bing Crosby leads everyone in Christmas hymns such as &quot;Adeste Fideles&quot;, and presents a moving Christmas play titled, &quot;The Small One.&quot;  (Original air date December 25, 1946, ABC network.) (Running time 27:19)</p>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 24, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/758 - December 24, 2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> 
	<p>0:00:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly <br /> Fibber paints his Christmas tree white. Teeny and The King&apos;s Men sing &quot;The Night Before Christmas.&quot; (Original air date December 18, 1945. NBC network.) (Running time 27:00)</p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Father Knows Best <br /> Sometimes called &quot;Stranded in a snowstorm&quot;; the Anderson family has different ideas of how each would like to spend Christmas. (Original air date December 24, 1953, NBC network.) (Running time 28:07)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop <br /> &quot;Bread On The Waters&quot;     (Original air date December 22, 1938. CBS network.) (Running time 29:49)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - The Greatest Story Ever Told <br /> &quot;No Room At The Inn&quot;. The story of the Nativity, based on the book by Fulton Oursler of the life of Jesus.      (Original air date December 21, 1947. ABC network.)(Running time 24:42)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - Lum &amp; Abner <br /> &quot;Traditional Christmas Story&quot; A walk in the woods is something more. (Original air date December 24, 1944, NBC network.) (Running time 14:42)</p>
	<p>2:15:00 - The Challenge Of The Yukon <br /> A young boy gets a puppy for Christmas, thanks to Sergeant Preston.  (Original air date December 19, 1946. WXYZ station.)(Running time 14:18)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Family Theatre <br /> &quot;Lullaby Of Christmas&quot;.  A Christmas fable about a young boy who could not speak, at the time of the birth of Jesus.  (Original air date December 19, 1951. Mutual network)(Running time 29:56)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Campbell Playhouse <br /> &quot;A Christmas Carol&quot;    Lionel Barrymore in his defining role, in Charles Dicken&apos;s classic ghost story.   (Original air date December 24, 1939. CBS network.)(Running time 54:12)</p>
 </description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 18, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/757 - December 18, 2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> Empty for this first episode. </description>
<itunes:keywords>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Missing Mouse Matter&quot;   A singing mouse named Gulliver has been kidnapped — wait, a singing mouse? (Original air date December 23, 1956. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Suspense <br /> &quot;The Cave&quot;   A fanciful story about two boys who discover pirates in a magical cave on Christmas Day.  (Original air date December 20, 1955. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Where&apos;d They Go?&quot;   Marshal Dillon and Chester ride out to arrest a man accused of robbery but are sidetracked by charitable needs and deeds.   (Original air date December 29, 1957. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Little Jesus&quot;   A Los Angeles Mission reports the statue of Jesus has been stolen the day before Christmas. (Original air date December 22, 1953.) NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Eternal Light <br /> &quot;Anne Frank: The Diary Of A Young Girl&quot;   A radio adaptation of the famous journal by Anne Frank, a Jewish teenager who chronicled her family&apos;s life in hiding under Nazi persecution. (Original air date December 14, 1952. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Rocky Fortune <br /> &quot;The Plot To Murder Santa Claus&quot;     Frank Sinatra stars as detective Rocky Fortune; there&apos;s a plot to murder Santa Claus.  (Original air date December 22, 1953. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:52:00 - excerpt New World A&apos;Coming (Original air date December 24, 1944.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Shadow <br /> &quot;Cold Death&quot;  Orson Welles stars as The Shadow, entering the mind of a Scrooge-like slumlord who keeps the press out of his shantytown with gangsters.  (Original broadcast date December 19, 1937.  Mutual network.)</p>
<p>3:00:00 - Broadway Is My Beat <br /> Nick Norman is just out of Sing Sing after fifteen years and is scheduled to play Santa Claus for the P.A.L. (Original broadcast date December 24, 1949. CBS network.)</p>
</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 11, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/756-11Dec2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> 
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Valentine Matter&quot;  Parts 4 and 5.   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar, investigating  the murder of Danny Valentine. (Original air date November 3 and 4, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - My Favorite Husband <br /> Lucille Ball as Liz Cooper; there are only seven shopping days until Christmas. What is George planning to give Liz for Christmas? (Original air date December 16, 1949. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Cheap Labor&quot;  A peaceful man is threatened by a jealous brother of his fiancée.   (Original air date June 17, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - Excerpt from &quot;The Sound of Jazz&quot; featuring Billie Holiday&apos;s &quot;Fine and Mellow&quot; (Original air date December 8, 1957)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big 38&quot;   A brutal story of a store clerk shot and murdered. (Original air date October 5, 1950.) NBC network.)(Running time 26:04)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Challenge Of The Yukon <br /> &quot;The Man With The Red Coat&quot;  A little girl confuses Sergeant Preston&apos;s red Mountie suit with Santa&apos;s costume. (Original air date December 22, 1948. ABC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Suspense <br /> &quot;Out For Christmas&quot;    Raymond Burr stars as an ex-con who gets out of jail just before Christmas, looking for trouble.  (Original air date December 21, 1958. CBS network.)(Running time 23:29)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Big Town <br /> Edward G. Robinson stars as Steve Wilson of the The Illustrated Press, who investigates a suspicious Christmas charity racket.  (Original broadcast date December 21, 1937. CBS network.)(Running time 26:26)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Quiet Please <br /> &quot;Berlin, 1945&quot;   A great Christmas story about a group of American G.I.&apos;s celebrating the holiday in conquered Germany. (Original broadcast date December 26, 1948. ABC network.)(Running time 28:59)</p>
 </description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>About Jekyll</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle>Podcast Example: About Jekyll</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/jekyll-logo.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/jekyll-hyde.mp3" length="461569" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 01:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> Just a test site with audio posting. Show Notes Available at https://michael833.github.io/test2.html.</description>
<itunes:keywords>jekyll</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>What is Atom?</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle>Podcast Example: What is Atom?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/logo.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/track1.mp3" length="1029183" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 01:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> All about atom and rss - test. Show Notes Available at https://michael833.github.io/test1.html.</description>
<itunes:keywords>atom</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>