<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xml:lang="">
<script/>
<channel>
<atom:link href="https://michael833.github.io/tbbfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<title>The Big Broadcast</title>
<link>https://michael833.github.io</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>No © 2009</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:summary>The Big Broadcast </itunes:summary>
<description> WAMU's The Big Broadcast </description>
<webMaster>na ()</webMaster>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name/>
<itunes:email>na</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<itunes:category text="History"/>
<itunes:category text="Leisure">
	<itunes:category text="Hobbies"/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

<!--
Macro: Place <p>, </p>, and <br /> , delete extra line spaces, then highlight text, then Alt + =
^ and reg exp for <p>
$ and reg exp for </p>
Alt =, then Alt -

https://michael833.github.io/tbbfeed.xml


&lt;	<	less than
&gt;	>	greater than
&amp;	&	ampersand 
&apos;	'	apostrophe
&quot;	"	quotation mark




<item>
<title>January 12, 2025 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/866 - January 12, 2025.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 5, 2025 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/865 - January 5, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 Jan 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 29, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/864 - December 29, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 22, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/863 - December 22, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 15, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/862 - December 15, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>
-->

<item>
<title>December 8, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/862 - December 8, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 8 Dec 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Big Scoop Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; a crusading reporter is murdered before he can expose a national gambling syndicate. (Original broadcast dates November 11, 1956. CBS network. Running time 24:49)
0:30:00 - The Six-Shooter  Jimmy Stewart stars in a story of “A Christmas Carol” retold with a western motif.  (Original air date December 20, 1953. NBC network.) (Running time 28:58)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Squaw”  A story promoting tolerance; a man married to an American Indian woman comes to grief from his son. (Original air date April 27, 1958. CBS network. Running time 23:37)
1:25:00 - Dragnet   “.22 Rifle For Christmas”  The fourth broadcast of this Christmas story about a nine-year-old boy and his new gun. (Original air date December 21, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:45)
2:00:00 - Tales Of The Texas Rangers  “Christmas Present”  Joel Mccrea stars this western crime story, The “Santa Claus Stickup” of December 31, 1931. (Original air dates  December 24, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:14)
2:30:00 - The Whistler  “Christmas Bonus”  An ex-convict is fired from his job in a department store after $10,000 is stolen. (Original air date December 25, 1944. CBS Pacific network.)(Running time 29:52)
3:00:00 - excerpt from The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny    Don is Christmas shopping for shoe laces for Don. Will he get metal or plastic tips?   (Original air date December 08, 1946. NBC network. Running time 17:48)
3:15:00 - Johnny Carson’s Undergraduate Senior Thesis “How to Write Comedy for Radio”  A young Johnny Carson, deconstructs comedy writing for radio, the rules and customs of the art, in his undergraduate senior thesis at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln.  (May, 1949. University of Nebraska-Lincoln.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 1, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/861 - December 1, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 1 Dec 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Silent Queen Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; Johnny finally has an audience with Mavis Slade, an actress in silent movies, and solves the case. Parts 4 and 5. (Original broadcast dates November 1 and 2, 1956. CBS network. Running time 14:18, 14:22)
0:30:00 - The Marriage  Liz gets a job working the perfume sales counter at a department store during the Christmas shopping season. (Original air date December 20, 1953. NBC network.) (Running time 24:26)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Livvie’s Loss”  Livvie Redgate wants desperately to keep her son from becoming an alcoholic like her husband.  (Original air date April 18, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:54)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: Radio Free Europe, excerpts “Holiday Season Behind the Iron Curtain”. (Original air date December 1951. Radio Free Europe. Running time 11:52)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Eavesdrop”  Sergeant Friday and Frank Smith get lucky when they overhear two criminals discussing a murder. (Original air date December 14, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:27)
2:00:00 - X Minus One  “Skulking Permit”  A long-lost colony of Earth tries to prove itself civilized …by creating a criminal. (Original air dates February 15, 1956. NBC network. Running time 28:06)
2:30:00 - The New Adventures Of Nero Wolfe  “The Case Of The Slaughtered Santas” Sydney Greenstreet stars as the sedentary detective investigating a rash of Santas murders. (Original air date December 22, 1950. NBC network.)(Running time 29:26)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “Miracle on 34th Street”  Our Big Broadcast traditional airing of this famous radio adaptation of the classic film; featuring the three adult stars of the original 1947 movie: Maureen O’Hara, John Payne, and — as Kris Kringle –de Edmund Gwenn.   (Original air date December 20, 1948. CBS network. Running time 53:55)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>November 24, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/860 - November 24, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 24Nov 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Silent Queen Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; who killed Barney Slade, and what is the connection to Mavis Slade, an actress in “silent” movies? Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original broadcast dates October 29, 30 and 31, 1956. CBS network. Running time 14:32, 14:31 and 14:38)
0:45:00 - Lum and Abner  “Chester the Turkey” (Original air date November 28, 1946. NBC network.) (Running time 10:13)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Stallion”  Oat Harker takes the prize horse of Dan Stokes and mistreats him. (Original air date May 18, 1958. CBS network. Running time 22:41)
1:20:00 - Elgin Company’s Second Annual Tribute To The Armed Forces, excerpts featuring George Burns and Gracie Allen. (Original air date November 25, 1943. CBS network. Running time 7:54)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Mole”  A burglary in a dry goods store is the latest in a series of similar crimes. (Original air date December 7, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:32)
2:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks  Miss Brooks and Mrs. Davis have only a small squab for Thanksgiving dinner, and all their friends plan to share it. (Original air dates November 27, 1949. CBS network. Running time 29:27)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Screaming Woman”  Margaret O’Brien stars with Agnes Moorehead in this chilling post-Thanksgiving story about a little girl who hears a screaming woman — buried alive. (Original air date November 25, 1948. CBS network.)(Running time 25:32)
2:55:00 - Radio Retrospective: Winston Churchill’s “America’s Thanksgiving Day.  (Original air date November 23, 1944. BBC network.)(Running time 4:02)
3:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop  “We Gather Together”   A special Thanksgiving day broadcast about a small boy in a small town on a Thanksgiving of long ago. Our thanks to Ted Davenport of Radio Memories for providing this lost audio! (Original air date  November 21, 1951. CBS network. Running time 24:21)
3:30:00 - Doctor Christian  “Prelude To Thanksgiving”  Jean Hersholt stars as the country doctor who advises on all matters — including those of the heart. (Original air date  November 22, 1939. CBS network. Running time 24:59)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>November 17, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/859 - November 17, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Phantom Chase Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; Johnny continues island hopping and wraps up the missing stockbroker case. Parts 7, 8, and 9. (Original broadcast dates October 23, 24 and 25, 1956. CBS network. Running time 14:37, 14:37 and 13:57)
0:30:00 - A Date With The Duke, excerpts   Guest Joya Sherrill joins the Duke on his post-war music program. (Original air date October 13, 1945. ABC network, AFRS.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Pussy Cats”  A husband and wife team murder four men in Dodge- will they get away with it? (Original air date March 21, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:45)
1:20:00 - We Interrupt This Broadcast: Iran Hostage Crisis
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Light”  A movie director, has been killed at the studio (Original air date November 2, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:48)
2:00:00 - The Abbott and Costello Show  Costello takes on “The Great Gildersleeve,” on and off the football field. (Original air dates January 20, 1944. NBC Red network. Running time 24:22)
2:30:00 - If Freedom Failed  “The Man Who Died Twice”  The Communists take over the motion picture industry in Hollywood.   (Original air date 1951. AFRS. Running time 30:12)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “The Day The Earth Stood Still”  An alien from space gives mankind a final chance to achieve world peace. (Original air date January 04, 1954. CBS network. Running time 59:55)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>November 10, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/858 - November 10, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Phantom Chase Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; the chase continues for Johnny as he looks for a missing stockbroker accused of embezzlement. Parts 4, 5 and 6. (Original broadcast dates October 18, 19 and 22, 1956. CBS network. Running time 13:40, 13:42, 13:37)
0:30:00 - The Martin and Lewis Show   Guest Mitzi Gaynor holds her own with Jerry Lewis and Dean Martin. (Original air date April 7, 1953. NBC network. Running time 12:53)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Cyclone”  A western detective story; The Cyclone Ranch has been sold under strange circumstances. (Original air date March 14, 1953. CBS network. Running time 26:40)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Number”   How will Detective Friday track down a bank robber? (Original air date October 26, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:36)
2:00:00 - The Stan Freberg Show  The Freberg Build-It-Yourself grand piano, Billy May and his Orchestra.  (Original air dates September 15 and 22, 1957. CBS network. Running time 35:05)
2:30:00 - You Bet Your Life  Groucho Marx kids announcer George Fenneman, and the guests on his radio quiz show.   (Original air date January 25, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:25)
3:00:00 - Escape, “Evening Primrose”  John Collier’s creepy tale about a strange assortment of characters who live inside New York’s department stores. (Original air date November 5, 1947. CBS network. Running time 29:29)
3:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America, “To The Shores Of Tripoli”  Our salute to the United States Marines; starring Joseph Cotten.  (Original air date February 1, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 25:14)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>November 3, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/857 - November 3, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 3 Nov 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Phantom Chase Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is pulled in to find a missing stockbroker accused of embezzlement. (Original broadcast dates October 15, 16, and 17, 1956. CBS network. Running time 13:41, 13:41, 13:54)
0:30:00 - Lum and Abner   Lum has decided to be President of the new health resort, if only Abner would nominate him. (Original air date July 3, 1944. NBC Blue network. Running time 10:38)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Gonif”  The Bissell gang is in town, and Marshal Dillon gives them until sundown to leave Dodge.  (Original air date April 11, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:44)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Pill”   Two Marines are poisoned in a cheap hotel by the slightly mad “Stubby.” (Original air date October 19, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:53)
1:50:00 - Big Broadcast interview: Anastacia McClesky; currently starring as suffragist and civil rights activist Mary Church Terrell in the Broadway musical Suffs. You can listen to our broadcast of “The Long Road”, a Destination Freedom audio biography on Mary Church Terrell, here. 
2:00:00 - Destination Freedom  “Woman With A Mission”   The story of Ida B. Wells who became an “investigative reporter.”  (Original air date April 10, 1949. NBC network, WMAQ station. Running time 29:26)
2:30:00 - Living 1948   “Let’s Sit This One Out” A drama/documentary about why every vote counts in our elections.   (Original air date October 31, 1948. NBC network. Running time 24:04)
3:00:00 - The NBC University Theatre, “All The King’s Men”  A moving radio adaptation of Robert Penn Warren’s novel.  (Original air date January 16, 1949. NBC network. Running time 54:22)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 27, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/856 - October 27, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Medium Rare Matter”  Mandel Kramer stars as Johnny Dollar; Johnny suspects a psychic is a fraud, but can he prove it? (Original broadcast dates October 8, 1961. CBS network. Running time 23:59)
0:30:00 - The Charlie McCarthy Show   Orson Welles is Edgar and Charlie’s special guest. (Original air date October 29, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:12)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Meshougah” Marshal Dillon is called in to stop a gang.  (Original air date February 21, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:56)
1:20:00 - Lights Out  “The Dark” Arch Oboler’s masterpiece; a 1962 Capitol Records reproduction of his 1938 legendary story about an evil force that turns people inside out (Running time 7:22)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Lie”  A tough domestic drama. (Original air date October 12, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:11)
2:00:00 - Escape  “Three Skeleton Key”  Vincent Price creates a terrifying scene, in a lighthouse off a jungle coast, and a ship of… rats.  (Original air date March 17, 1950. CBS network. Running time 28:49)
2:30:00 - The Hall Of Fantasy, “The Tell-Tale Heart”  A twist on Edgar Allan Poe’s classic horror tale.   (Original air date June 1, 1953. Mutual network. Running time 23:54)
3:00:00 - The Mercury Theater On the Air, “The War Of the Worlds”  Orson Welles and John Houseman’s masterpiece; an immersive experience of martians invading the earth. Sound effects by Ora Nichols. (Original air date October 30, 1938. CBS network. Running time 59:34)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 20, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/855 - October 20, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Royal Street Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; a New Orleans antique shop has had a fire, but suspiciously the owner refuses to file a claim. (Original broadcast dates November 25, 1956. CBS network. Running time27:35)
0:30:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre.   Fred visits guest Bela Lugosi’s house and tries to rent it. (Original air date April 25, 1943. CBS network. Running time 24:24)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Yorky” A young boy is injured and left behind after an Arapaho raid. (Original air date April 06, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:34)
1:20:00 - Abbott and Costello Show  “Who’s On First?” (NBC, Original air date April 17, 1947)(Running time 4:27)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Jolt”  A drunken teenager and a riot in chemistry class leads Friday and Smith to a bar and hangout for kids. (Original air date October 05, 1952. NBC network. Running time 24:39)
2:00:00 - Boston Blackie  It starts like a well-known ghost story… Blackie picks up a girl hitchhiker who’s been dead for three years. (Original air date May 28, 1947. Mutual network. Running time 28:09)
2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries   “Corridor Of Doom”  A sick man in a hospital who finds himself walking down an endless hallway…approaching the door with his name written on it!  (Original air date October 23, 1945. CBS network. Running time 28:01)
3:00:00 - Escape, “The Log”  An extraordinary cast performs the story of the last voyage of a submarine without a country.  (Original air date September 20, 1953. CBS network. Running time 27:19)
3:30:00 - Jubilee, The very first program of this AFRS special program, hosted by Rex Ingram, and guest artists Duke Ellington and Ethel Waters.  (Recording date October 9, 1942. AFRS. Running time 29:30)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 13, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/854 - October 13, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Markham Matter”  Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; a man seems to be slowly poisoning his wife. (Original broadcast dates November 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 28:15)
0:45:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes   The cast does its version of, “Mr. Benny Goes To Washington.” (Original air date January 24, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 27:08)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Fawn”  Mrs. Phillips returns to Dodge after living with American Indians for ten years. (Original air date September 26, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:49)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Shot”  Mr. Kelby, the manager of the Pink Rat Cafe, has been shot and killed by the Evans brothers during a robbery. (Original air date September 21, 1952.. NBC network. Running time 25:43)
2:00:00 - Destination Freedom  “Pagan Poet”   A biography of Countee Cullen, the famous poet. His was considered the most “representative voice” of the Harlem renaissance. (Original air date April 03, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:08)
2:30:00 - The George Burns and Gracie Allen Show   George and Gracie spend the night with Rita Hayworth.  (Original air date March 21, 1944. CBS network. Running time 27:45)
3:00:00 - Suspense, “A Ring For Marya”  Cornel Wilde stars as a man who convinces his wife to set fire to his story for the insurance money, then double-crosses her when she’s badly burned in the act.  (Original air date December 28, 1950. CBS network. Running time 28:43)
3:30:00 - Family Theatre, “A Thief In The Night”   Robert Walker stars in this drama about a small-town man with big ideas.  (Original air date May 20, 1948. Mutual network. Running time 28:37)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 6, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/853 - October 6, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 6 Oct 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Primrose Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; Can Johnny find out what’s going on up there at Primrose Camp? (Original broadcast dates October 11 and 12, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50 and 13:45)
0:35:00 - 60th Anniversary special – we’re unlocking audio from the WAMU Vault! Ed Walker and John Hickman talk about old time radio, Jack Benny unlocks his vault, Baltimore Benny with Crabs for Christmas, John Hickman introduces The Story of Gunsmoke, and more!
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Billy The Kid”  The pilot episode of Gunsmoke (Original air date April 26, 1952. CBS network. Running time 29:30)
1:45:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Fraud”  Sergeant Friday goes undercover to trap a gang posing as narcotic cops.  (Original air date October 27, 1953. NBC network. Running time 25:58)
2:22:00 - Excerpt from “An Evening With William N Robson”, with Big Broadcast creator John Hickman, from Recollections (Original air date April 1974. WAMU.)
2:30:00 - The Man Behind The Gun “Prep Joe”   A peabody award winning production; the story of the P.T. boats in the South Pacific, fighting the Japanese. Frank Lovejoy and Jim Backus; produced William N. Robson. (Original air date February 12, 1944. CBS.)
3:00:00 - The Campbell Playhouse, “Rebecca”  Orson Welles, Margaret Sullavan, and Agnes Moorehead star in this radio adaptation of Daphne du Maurier’s novel — before it was a Hitchcock classic film. A new bride at a wealthy estate hears constantly about the previous mistress of the house…Rebecca. (Original air date December 09, 1938. CBS network. Running time 59:00)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>September 29, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/852 - September 29, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Primrose Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Bob Bailey stars as Johnny Dollar; Can Johnny find out what’s going on up there at Primrose Camp? (Original broadcast dates October 8, 9 and 10, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:58, 13:50 and 14:02)
0:45:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny, excerpts Jack and guest Lauren Bacall do a love scene from, “To Have and Have Not,” when in walks guest Humphrey Bogart. (Original air date January 05, 1947. NBC network. Running time 12:08)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Shakespeare”  Hans Conried stars as a traveling interpreter of the Bard. (Original air date August 23, 1952. CBS network. Running time 29:30)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Bull”  Friday is after a vicious gang member who has threatened the family of Frank Smith, Friday’s partner.  (Original air date September 14, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:58)
2:00:00 - X Minus One  “Sense of Wonder”  A spaceship on a ten thousand year journey lands on Earth, from where it took off long ago. (Original air date April 24, 1956. NBC network. Running time 26:16)
2:30:00 - The Damon Runyon Theatre “The Melancholy Dane”   An actor gets revenge on a critic while they are both entrenched in the European Theater.   (Original air date June 12, 1949. Mayfair syndication. Running time 27:08)
3:00:00 - Great Plays, “A Cavalcade Of Drama: From Ancient Greece To Modern Broadway”  A humour and informative look through theater’s history, with excerpts from “The Frogs”, “The Machine”, “Hamlet” and more.  (Original air date October 13, 1940. NBC network. Running time 59:34)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>September 22, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/851 - September 22, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Picture Postcard Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Johnny is in the Alps on a stolen-diamond case. (Original broadcast dates October 4 and 5, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:45 and 13:48)
0:30:00 - The Phil Harris-Alice Faye Show  Phil is roped in to lead his daughter’s Brownie troop on an overnight hike and camp-out. (Original air date October 22, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:19)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Why Not?”  A young woman is on the run from her overbearing father. (Original air date March 30, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:29)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective:  The Invasion Of Peleliu, with excerpts from NBC News, September 22, 1944.
1:30 pm. Dragnet   “The Big Ray”  Domestic tension leads Detective Friday to be suspicious of the circumstances of a man’s accidental death. (Original air date September 4, 1952. NBC network. Running time 27:07)
2:00:00 - Jeff Regan, Investigator  “The Too Many Mrs. Rogers”  Jack Webb stars in this dripping-with-noir story about one man, one jewel, and many wives.  (Original air date October 9, 1948. CBS network. Running time 29:23)
2:30:00 - Suspense, “Crisis”   Versatile actor Martha Scott headlines in this gripping tale of an imagined — and terrifying — future. (Original air date August 19, 1948. CBS Network. Running time 29:34)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theater, “Cheers For Miss Bishop”  Martha Scott as school teacher Miss Bishop, across several decades.  (Original air date March 17, 1941. CBS network. Running time 59:46.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>September 15, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/850 - September 15, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Picture Postcard Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Johnny travels to the Alps on a stolen-diamond case. (Original broadcast dates October 1, 2 and 3, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:55, 13:55 and 13:55)
0:45:00 - Jimmy Carter, “Boyhood Farm Memories (The Living Room)”
0:50:00 - Looking back: cabaret performer Bobby Short, with excerpts from Chappell’s Broadway, 1971.
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Real Sent Sonny”  Marshall Dillon is the target of young Sonny, sent to kill him. (Original air date March 16, 1958. CBS network. Running time 19:59)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Test”  Detective Friday must determine if an unbelievable story is worth following up. (Original air date August 28, 1952. NBC network. Running time 27:00)
1:50:00 - Guest Star featuring Gogi Grant. (Original recording date September 01, 1957. Treasury Department syndication.)
2:00:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly  The famous Fibber McGee closet is heard for the first time, and Gracie Allen appears as a guest to promote her candidacy for President. (Original air date March 05, 1940. NBC network. Running time 28:39)
2:30:00 - My Favorite Husband   Eager to prove that she is not superstitious, Lucille Ball’s Liz takes on “Supercricket.” (Original air date October 21, 1949. CBS Network. Running time 29:41)
3:00:00 - The Campbell Playhouse  “The Murder Of Roger Ackroyd”  Agatha Christie’s classic detective story; Hercule Poirot solves another murder, with Orson Welles as both the Belgian detective and the prime suspect! (Original air date November 12, 1939. CBS network. Running time 1:00:15. Our thanks to Indiana University, for providing this audio through the Indiana University Media Digitization and Preservation Initiative MDPI)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>September 8, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/849 - September 8, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 8 Sep 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Meg’s Palace Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Johnny closes in on the person threatening Meg, proprietor of a seaside restaurant in Cod Harbor.  (Original broadcast dates September 24, 25 and 26, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:48 and 13:55)
0:30:00 - Superman   Jimmy Olsen and Lois are in the woods — as a forest fire rages towards them! And Donnelli has planted dynamite across the only road out of the wilderness. (Original air dates April 24 and 26, 1940. Syndicated. Running time 10:33 and 11:45)
0:55:00 - excerpts from Alan Freed’s Rock’n’Roll Dance Party
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Laughing Gas”  The Marsh Boys break up a laughing gas show when one of them is made a fool of. (Original air date March 9, 1958. CBS network. Running time 23:39)
1:20:00 - Radio retrospective: 1924 World Series, with excerpts from Only a Game
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Paper”  Blank checks have been stolen from “Marty’s Mart,” and are being passed in supermarkets. (Original air date August 21, 1952. NBC network. Running time 27:02)
2:00:00 - The Fred Allen Show  Fred and guest Leo Durocher appear before “the Brooklyn Bar of Justice”  (Original air date April 25, 1948. NBC network. Running time 29:26)
2:30:00 - The Halls Of Ivy   An elder woman enrolls at Ivy College, full of questions for the professors. (Original air date October 24, 1951. NBC Network. Running time 26:28)
3:00:00 - Boston Blackie  The first show of the series. Blackie is accused of stealing a large diamond — but he doesn’t know anything about it! (Original air date June 23, 1944. NBC network. Running time 29:23)
3:30:00 - The General Electric Theatre    “State Fair”   Ann Blyth stars in this radio adaptation of Philip Stong’s classic story of state fairs’ promise of big crowds, excitement… and occasional romance.  (Original air date September 10, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:32)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>September 1, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/848 - September 1, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 1 Sep 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Meg’s Palace Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Johnny is hired to investigate a restaurant in Cod Harbor, Massachusetts, which is run by “Meg.”  (Original broadcast dates September 24, 25 and 26, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:37 and 13:39)
0:45:00 - Superman   Jimmy Olsen has vanished into the woods, and the search for Lois continues.   (Original air date April 22, 1940. Syndicated. Running time 11:29)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Guitar”  Bullies go after a simple-minded man.  (Original air date December 26, 1953. CBS network. Running time 22:41)
1:20:00 - Paul Robeson, “Joe Hill” (3:00)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Impression”  An elderly diamond salesman has been robbed of $150,000 in unset diamonds.  (Original air date August 07, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:57)
2:00:00 - Space Patrol  “The Hole In Empty Space”  A “cycloplex” has been swallowing objects in outer space. (Original air date October 25, 1952. ABC network. Running time 28:58)
2:30:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny   The first show of the 1945 fall season; The NBC “telephone operators” (“Mabel and Gertrude”) appear for the first time. (Original air date September 30, 1945. NBC Network. Running time 28:14)
3:00:00 - Richard Diamond, Private Detective  Agitators use violence to try to take over a union.  (Original air date June 26, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:25)
3:30:00 - Freedom U.S.A.   Senator Dean tries to improve the working conditions of migrant workers in his home state. (Original air date August 10, 1952. ZIV syndication. Running time 26:37)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 25, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/847 - August 25, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Confidential Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Johnny always puts his whole self into his work, but this time it’s personal.  (Original broadcast dates September 10, 11 and 12, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:37 and 13:39)
0:45:00 - Superman    An adventure sometimes called “Donnelli’s Protection Racket”. Donnelli’s protection racket is preying on the candy store run by Jimmy Olsen’s mom.   (Original air date April 17 and April 19, 1940. Syndicated. Running time 11:23 and 11:22)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Surgery”  Writer Marian Clark’s famous script dealing with medical ethics and a life-or-death scenario.  (Original air date February 23, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:26)
1:20:00 - Hobby Lobby    An outstanding performance by Arthur Williamson, the world’s only “fingerless” pianist.  (Original air date 1935. Running time 4:19)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Hate”   Detective Joe Friday’s confronted with a really bizarre mystery — and a suspect who won’t say a word.  (Original air date July 10, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:41)
2:00:00 - Theatre Of Romance  “Love Affair”  Susan Peters, an actor in a wheelchair, portrays a character in a wheelchair, in this unforgettable love story. (Original air date December 14, 1945. CBS network. Running time 25:05)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Flood On The Goodwins” A Nazi and a one-armed Englishman duel on a small boat in the English Channel. Actor Herbert Marshall stars. (Original air date July 14, 1957. CBS Network. Running time 29:14)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “The Wizard of Oz”   The adventures of Dorothy in the land of Oz, starring Judy Garland. (Original air date December 25, 1950. CBS network. Running time 59:46)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 18, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/846 - August 18, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Confidential Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Johnny always puts his whole self into his work, but this time it’s personal.  (Original broadcast dates September 10, 11 and 12, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:37 and 13:39)
0:45:00 - Superman    An adventure sometimes called “Donnelli’s Protection Racket”. Donnelli’s protection racket is preying on the candy store run by Jimmy Olsen’s mom. Part 1.  (Original air date April 15, 1940. Syndicated. Running time 11:38)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Bruger’s Folly” A man just out of prison returns to confront his wife.  (Original air date February 16, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:19)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: The 1968 Democratic National Convention
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Signet”   The restaurant and bar that is run by Mr. and Mrs. Ryner has been robbed. Mr. Ryner’s diamond signet ring has been taken too. (Original air date July 31, 1952. NBC network. Running time 27:23)
2:00:00 - Defense Attorney  Mercedes McCambridge stars as a defense attorney who comes to the aid of a widow named Edith Larkin. Ms. Larkin’s late husband was cheated by a dishonest patent attorney.  (Original air date October 09, 1952. ABC network. Running time 28:44)
2:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks  Rumor has it that Miss Brooks is leaving Madison High and going to move to Connecticut!  (Original air date July 31, 1949. CBS Network. Running time 26:46)
3:00:00 - Stars Over Hollywood  “The House That Built Jack”  Bob Bailey stars with Shelley Winters in this story about a couple who must sell their beloved but troublesome house. (Original air date November 22, 1952. CBS network. Running time 26:46)
3:30:00 - Lights Out  “Oxychloride X”  Arch Oboler’s classic horror story about a college student who invents a universal solvent, with nothing to keep it in.  (Original air date February 16, 1943. CBS network. Running time 29:18)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>August 11, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/845 - August 11, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Curse Of Kamashek Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. An heir to a family fortune is in danger, but is it from an Egyptian curse, or someone he knows? (Original broadcast dates September 6 and 7, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:38 and 13:45)
0:30:00 - Tribute to Bob Newhart
0:35:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny   Jack invites guests Ronald Colman and Benita Hume to make a western movie with him. Jack borrows Ronald’s Oscar, and is held up on the way home. (Original air date March 28, 1948. NBC network. Running time 24:33)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Hot Horse Hyatt” A man is accused of stealing horses, and Marshall Dillon intervenes.(Original air date June 08, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:32)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Rescue”  Two men are robbing stores and bars without a discernible pattern, armed with a .45 and a machine gun. (Original air date July 13, 1954. NBC network. Running time 26:00)
2:00:00 - Gangbusters   A dramatization of the riot and inmate unrest on the prison island in San Francisco.  (Original air date May 11, 1946. ABC network. Running time 26:36)
2:30:00 - Columbia Presents Corwin  “There Will Be Time Later”  Norman Corwin’s deeply moving message a hopeful post-war world.  (Original air date August 15, 1944. CBS Network. Running time 29:15)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theater  “Algiers”  Hedy Lamarr and Charles Boyer star in this romance set in the Kasbah. (Original air date July 7, 1941. CBS network. Running time 59:44)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>August 4, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/844 - August 4, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 4 Aug 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Curse Of Kamashek Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. An heir to a family fortune is more interested in exploring Egyptian antiquities than upholding the family name, much to the dismay of his Uncle. (Original broadcast dates September 3, 4 and 5, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:47, and 13:48)
0:45:00 - The Kraft Music Hall   Bing Crosby and Marilyn Maxwell sing tunes from 1930, and Marilyn imitates Helen Kane as “Betty Boop.” (Original recording June 01, 1944. NBC network. Running time 16:13)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Busted-Up Guns”  The government agent on the Sioux reservation has taken to drinking daily, and is determined to keep guns away from the Sioux. (Original air date July 17, 1960. CBS network. Running time 23:18)
1:20:00 - Celebrating the centennial of living legend Ella Jenkins; excerpt from Smithsonian’s Sound Sessions with Sam Litzinger, produced 2009.
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Roll”  A man has been abducted in front of a downtown bar and taken away in a gray car. The car turns up with bloodstains soon after. (Original air date June 26, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:17)
2:00:00 - X Minus One  “Pictures Don’t Lie”  A radio signal originating from interstellar space turns out to be a television picture. It seems to be coming from an alien spaceship heading towards the Earth! (Original air date October 24, 1956. NBC network. Running time 27:26)
2:30:00 - Destination Freedom   “The Long Road”  The story of suffragist, civil rights and human rights activist Mary Church Terrell. (Original air date August 07, 1949. Station WMAQ. Running time 29:35)
3:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop  “The Trial”  Franz Kafka’s disorienting story foretelling the horrors of totalitarianism. (Original air date May 19, 1946. CBS network. Running time 28:35)
3:30:00 - Suspense  “The Fall River Tragedy”.   Agnes Moorehead stars as an elder Lizzie Borden, recounting her story to a reporter of the day her parents were murdered.   (Original air date January 14, 1952. CBS network. Running time 25:43)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>July 28, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/843 - July 28, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Kranesburg Matter”  Parts 4, 5 and 6. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a pearl thief, family secrets, and murder!  (Original broadcast dates August 29, 30 and 31, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:11, 14:00, 14:12)
0:45:00 - Big Moments in Sports  “Jesse Owens”.  Harry Wismer describes how Jesse Owens dominated the 1936 Olympics. (Original recording 1955. Air Force syndication. Running time 13:58)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Quarter-Horse”  No one in Dodge believes that a quarter-horse from Missouri could be best any other steed, so a race is set!  (Original air date March 28, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:00)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Donation”  Sergeant Friday sets out to break a racket that consists of requests for contributions to phony charities. (Original air date June 12, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:41)
2:00:00 - The Adventures Of Frank Merriwell   “Tap Day” Frank has been framed during a trotting race. A hypodermic needle was planted on him, jeopardizing his chances for admission into, “Skull and Crossbones.” (Original air date June 12, 1948. NBC network. Running time 28:18)
2:30:00 - The Great Gildersleeve   Gildersleeve tries to prove himself the better man than Bullard, by hiking to and climbing “Old Stone Face.” (Original air date November 08, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:46)
3:00:00 - Boston Blackie   “Big Tiny” Mountain has wrestled “Stretcher Lewis” and killed him. Blackie gets a hammer-lock on the clues and solves the murder. (Original air date March 24, 1948. Mutual network. Running time 26:00)
3:30:00 - The Columbia Workshop  “The Trojan Women”.   John Houseman directs his translation of the classic Greek tragedy about the Trojan War, starring Jessica Tandy.  (Original air date December 8, 1940. CBS network. Running time 29:44)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>July 21, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/842 - July 21, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Kranesburg Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a pearl thief, family secrets, and murder!  (Original broadcast dates August 24, 27 and 28, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:15, 14:15, 14:00)
0:45:00 - Bobby Benson and The B-Bar-B Riders  “The Tunnel Of Trouble”.   Don Knotts co-stars in this children’s serial about young Bobby Benson, a twelve year-old orphan, who inherits a ranch from his parents. (Original air date February 16, 1953. Mutual network. Running time 20:00)
1:08:00 - Gunsmoke   “Joke’s On Us”  A dark story about the brutality of Wild West justice and vigilantism.  (Original air date January 09, 1954. CBS network. Running time 22:48)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Whiff”  An unidentified woman is found chloroformed to death. (Original air date June 05, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:53)
1:59:00 - We Interrupt This Broadcast   “Apollo 11 – Man Walks On Moon”  News anchor Bill Kurtis, with some of the broadcast sounds of the first human steps on the moon.  (Running time 3:08)
2:06:00 - Voice Of The Army. Featuring Margaret Whiting. This production is sometimes referred to by the title “On Location”. (Original recording date 1949. Army syndication. Running time 12:55)
2:30:00 - Suspense.  “Never Follow A Banjo Act”. Margaret Whiting stars as a cabaret lounge singer, who is given a dangerous assignment. (Original air date March 02, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:24)
2:40:00 - X Minus One.  “The Light”.  The first men on the moon discover… footprints. (Original air date October 24, 1957. NBC network. Running time 18:05)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre. “The Moon’s Our Home”.   Jimmy Stewart and Carole Lombard star in this romantic comedy about a famous author and actress — who know nothing of each other’s fame when they wed!  (Original air date February 10, 1941. CBS network. Running time 56:57)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>July 14, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/841 - July 14, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Crystal Lake Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to Crystal Lake, for a lovely view of a beautiful lake, a nice quiet spot…for murder!  (Original broadcast dates August 13, 14, and 15, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50 and 14:18)
0:30:00 - The Fred Allen Show, excerpts.  Fred Allen and the gang take on the challenge of how to make the Republican National Convention a good radio show. (Original air date February 07, 1940. NBC network. Running time 30:54)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “One For Lee”  Senator Hooper pays his first visit to Dodge, and is shot as soon as soon as he gets off the train! (Original air date January 26, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:28)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Fourth”  An eight-month-old baby has been stolen, out of a parked car. (Original air date May 29, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:40)
2:00:00 - CBS Is There    “The Citizens Of Paris Before The Bastille”. CBS news team reports live from the scene of the events of July 14, 1789, France.  (Original air date July 14, 1947 NBC network. Running time 27:06)
2:30:00 - Radio Retrospective: Wendell Willkie addressing the crowd at the Republican National Convention, 1940 
2:45:00 - Lest We Forget – These Great Americans    “The Story Of Wendell Willkie”  (Original recording date 1946. Institute For Democratic Education syndication. Running time 14:28)
3:00:00 - The Mercury Theatre   “A Tale Of Two Cities”  Orson Welles stars in this radio adaptation of Charles Dickens’ novel, set in the cross-hairs of the French Revolution.  (Original air date July 25, 1938. CBS network. Running time 59:23)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>July 7, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/840 - July 7, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 7 Jul 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Crystal Lake Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to Crystal Lake, for a lovely view of a beautiful lake, a nice quiet spot…for murder!  (Original broadcast dates August 13, 14, and 15, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50 and 13:50)
0:45:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly   Fibber fixes Molly’s sewing machine. (Original air date June 21, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:06)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Kitty’s Killing”  A religious fanatic named Jacob Leech comes to Dodge to wreak the Lord’s vengeance. (Original air date February 02, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:12)
1:20:00 - Treasury Star Parade  “I Am an American and The Freedom Road, by Langston Hughes” (probably recorded 1942. U.S. government-syndicated series. Running time 13:02)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Shakedown”  Somebody impersonates a police officer to extort money from gamblers. (Original air date May 22, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:27)
2:00:00 - Father Knows Best    The Anderson are back in the days of the American Revolution.  (Original air date July 05, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:35)
2:30:00 - You Are There    “The Signing Of The Declaration Of Independence”  A Big Broadcast tradition; CBS news team reports live from the scene of the events of July 4, 1776 in Philadelphia. (Original air date July 04, 1948. CBS origination. Running time 28:13)
3:00:00 - Stan Freberg Presents the United States of America   “Declaration Of Independence: A Man Can’t Be Too Careful What He Signs These Days”
3:20:00 - Lum and Abner    Abner makes plans for the 4th of July picnic, but Lum isn’t sure he’s up for all the fun. (Original air date July 04, 1945. ABC network. Running time 10:48)
3:30:00 - Inheritance “Paul Revere” A radio play about the ride of Paul Revere, a bit more accurate historically than Henry Wadsworth’s famous poem.  (Original air date December 05, 1954. NBC network. Running time 29:50)
3:50:00 - Songs by Sinatra    excerpts, including Frank Sinatra performing “America the Beautiful,” and “The House I Live In”  (Original air date November 21, 1945. CBS network. Running time 5:05)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>June 30, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/839 - June 30, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Sea Legs Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to Nicaragua.  (Original broadcast dates August 2 and 3, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:01 and 14:02)
0:45:00 - Superman   Batman and Robin save Superman from a piece of hidden Kryptonite, and then try to track down the deadly meteorite. (Original air date May 20 and 21, 1947. Syndicated. Running time 14:26, 14:24)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Moo Moo Raid”  Oney Hager and his very valuable cow have disappeared. (Original air date January 19, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:21)
1:20:00 - One Man’s Family excerpts, featuring Barbra Fuller (Original air date April 25, 1951. NBC network. Running time 9:42)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Mail”  A mail truck has been robbed, twenty-eight sacks of registered mail has been taken. (Original air date May 15, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:49)
2:00:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes    It’s Jack’s birthday, and the whole gang is celebrating up in Canada. (Original air date  February 14, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 29:29)
2:30:00 - The Big Show    Baby Snooks (Fanny Brice) gets an acting lesson from host Tallulah Bankhead, Groucho Marx holds his quiz on the show and teaches Ezio Pinza how to sing “Some Enchanted Evening.” (Original air date November 12, 1950. NBC network. Running time 1:29:38)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>June 23, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/838 - June 23, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Sea Legs Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to Nicaragua.  (Original broadcast dates July 30, 31, and August 1, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:07, 14:02 and 14:02)
0:45:00 - Superman   Batman and Robin watch from the audience, as Superman prepares to debate villain  “Big George” Latimer before the people of Metropolis. (Original air date May 19, 1947. Syndicated. Running time 14:26)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Twelfth Night”  A family feud going on for years is about to end in Dodge. (Original air date December 22, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:12)
1:20:00 - Country Music Time  excerpts of June Carter (probably recorded 1959. Air Force syndication. Running time 9:10)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Gamble”  A series of floating gambling games leads to the death of a cop during a raid. (Original air date May 08, 1952. NBC network. Running time 27:01)
2:00:00 - Hopalong Cassidy    Who is “The Robbing Parson?” (Original air date August 27, 1948. Commodore syndication. Running time 25:27)
2:30:00 - The Bing Crosby Show    Crosby duets with guest Ethel Merman, and they perform a Hopalong Cassidy skit with guest William Boyd. (Original air date March 22, 1950. CBS origination. Running time 26:54)
3:00:00 - The Whistler   “A Pattern For Terror”  After threatening a rival’s life, a man finds himself driving a car with a cop in the front seat and a body in the back!  (Original air date July 16, 1945. CBS network. Running time 29:11)
3:30:00 - Mr. Keen, Tracer Of Lost Persons    “The Rented Cottage Murder Case” A strange cottage, renting for $25 during the housing shortage, is the scene of the murder of a cripple.  (Original air date April 03, 1952. NBC network. Running time 27:50)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>June 16, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/837 - June 16, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Open Town Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to a little town in Missouri… that is a cesspool of corruption.  (Original broadcast dates July 26 and 27, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:41 and 13:42)
0:30:00 - It’s Time To Smile   Eddie Cantor entertains guests Groucho Marx, Gracie Allen, George Burns, and Jack Benny on his show. (Original air date June 09, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 28:56)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Second Son”  An episode never played on The Big Broadcast before, in our 60 years! An English chap loses his money and his horse playing poker with Pete Knutson. (Original air date January 12, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:06)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: Chet Atkins. With excerpts from The Grand Ole Opry, from 1955 and 1959.
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Safe”  Detective Friday and his partner go after a safecracking team. (Original air date May 01, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:26)
1:55:00 - A commemoration of Juneteenth: Interview with Laura Smalley, Hempstead, Texas, 1941
2:00:00 - Night Beat    Frank Lovejoy and William Conrad star in a two-hander about a nervous father-to-be.  (Original air date December 28, 1951. NBC network. Running time 30:34)
2:30:00 - The Life Of Riley    Junior and Egbert Gillis are off to camp — will Riley and Gillis be able to stand their absence? (Original air date  October 18, 1945. NBC origination. Running time 25:02)
3:00:00 - Suspense    “Summer Storm”  Henry Fonda stars in this psychological thriller about a man brewing a storm inside. (Original air date August 27, 1949. CBS network. Running time 25:51)
3:30:00 - The Adventures Of Father Brown    “The Mystified Mind”   (Original air date August 13, 1945. Mutual network. Running time 28:58)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>June 9, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/836 - June 9, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 9 Jun 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Open Town Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to a little town in Missouri … that is a cesspool of corruption.  (Original broadcast dates July 23, 24 and 25, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:01, 13:45, 14:02)
0:45:00 - Exploring Tomorrow   “The Trouble With Robots”  The country of Transylvania is now being run by robots and a mad Baron.  (Original air date May 28, 1958. Mutual network. Running time 19:10)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Ugly”  The townsfolk of Dodge form a mob to chase out an ugly man. (Original air date December 15, 1957. CBS network. Running time 24:14)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Bunco”  Detective Friday and his new partner look for a con-man. (Original air date April 17, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:16)
2:00:00 - Candy Matson, YUkon 2-8209    “The Fort Ord Story”. Candy is invited to an army dance at Fort Ord and solves a double murder in the process.  (Original air date September 23, 1949. NBC network. Running time 28:33)
2:30:00 - Jubilee    Ernie “Bubbles” Whitman hosts Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Erskine Hawkins, Phil Moore and Gene Rodgers. (Original air date September 20, 1943. AFRS origination. Running time 26:48)
3:00:00 - NBC University Theater    “Nineteen-Eighty-Four”  David Niven stars in George Orwell’s story set in the age of “double think.” Big Brother is watching us all! (Original air date August 27, 1949. NBC network. Running time 56:49)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>June 2, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/835 - June 2, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 2 Jun 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Star Of Capetown Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny tracks down a killer, and the missing diamond.  (Original broadcast dates July 19 and 20, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:02, 13:41)
0:30:00 - D-Day Remembrance, excerpts from CBS, NBC, Pool reports and more from June 6, 1944
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Jud’s Woman”   A woman seeks protection from Marshall Dillon from her abusive husband. (Original air date December 1, 1957. CBS network. Running time 24:56)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Show”   A seven-week-old baby has been abandoned in the Los Angeles bus station… perhaps. (Original air date April 10, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:48)
2:00:00 - The Story Of Doctor Kildare    Lew Ayres and Lionel Barrymore star in this series; a street violinist’ wife is dying of cancer, but he can’t pay afford the hospital bills. (Original air date November 16, 1949. MGM syndication. Running time 27:45)
2:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America   “Assignment For The Prof”   Burgess Meredith stars as a geology professor who accepts a dangerous mission in Normandy, vital to the Allies’ invasion plans. (Original air date  August 27, 1945. NBC network. Running time 27:04)
3:00:00 - Radio Almanac    Orson Welles introduces and performs in a very well-written and acted portrait of the home front during the invasion. (Original air date June 7, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:42)
3:30:00 - New World A’ Coming    “A Statement By The Negro Community On D-Day”.  Featuring Marian Anderson, Roi Ottley, Walter White, Channing Tobias and Sheldon Hale Bishop. (Original air date June 7, 1944. Station WMCA. Running time 25:57)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>May 26, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/834 - May 26, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Star Of Capetown Matter”  Parts 1, 2 and 3. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny travels to South Africa to check up on a rare diamond, and finds murder.  (Original broadcast dates July 16, 17 and 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50 and 13:50)
0:45:00 - Against The Storm  A Memorial Day tribute to fallen soldiers. (Original broadcast date May 30, 1941. NBC Network. Running time 14:12)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Odd Man Out ” A mystery turns into a moving drama. (Original air date November 24, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:35)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Rose”    A missing persons case.  (Original air date March 27, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:22)
2:00:00 - Let’s Pretend    “King Arthur and How He Won His Sword”.   (Original air date October 02, 1954. CBS Network. Running time 26:22)
2:30:00 - The Campbell Playhouse “The Things We Have”  An original and moving drama by Orson Welles about a young immigrant who discovers what makes America unique. (Original air date May 26, 1939. CBS network. Running time 59:47)
3:30:00 - “How Sleep The Brave”    This special program features film star Lew Ayers, saluting World War II dead, “How Sleep the Brave” is based on a blank verse poem published by Joseph A. Bourdow. (Original air date May 31, 1948. Armed Forces Radio Service. Running time 24:07)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>May 19, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/833 - May 19, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Shady Lane Matter”  Parts 4 and 5. Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is sent to a quiet little New England town, with danger lurking just beyond the picket fence.  (Original broadcast dates July 12 and 13, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:03 and 13:03)
0:30:00 - The Hinds Honey and Almond Cream Program   Gracie has just returned from Washington, D. C., where she addressed the annual dinner of The Women’s National Press Club.  (Original broadcast date March 13, 1940. CBS Network. Running time 28:32)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Gunshy”  A newcomer to Dodge from Baltimore is out of place on the prairie. (Original air date November 10, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:47)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Border”    A crime wave of hold-ups, and a trail that leads to the Mexican border.  (Original air date March 20, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:35)
1:50:00 - Personally, It’s Off the Record, featuring Fats Waller (Original air date September 23, 1943. CBS and WABC. Running time 11:07)
2:00:00 - Destination Freedom    “The Shy Boy”. The story of Thomas “Fats” Waller, told from the viewpoint of James P. Johnson, his teacher and mentor.   (Original air date June 11, 1950. Station WMAQ. Running time 30:07)
2:30:00 - Mr. Keen, Tracer Of Lost Persons “The Broken Window Murder Case”  A dead rabbit provides Mr. Keen with the final clue to a killer. (Original recording date May 25, 1950. CBS network. Running time 29:54)
3:00:00 - The Lone Ranger    A story about claim stealing and the Pony Express in 1860.  (Original broadcast date February 23, 1938. NBC network. Running time 29:47)
3:30:00 - Cavalcade of America    “The Last of the Scouts”  A biography of Buffalo Bill (Original broadcast date March 9, 1938. CBS network. Running time 24:07)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>May 12, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/832 - May 12, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Shady Lane Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is sent to a quiet little New England town, with danger lurking just beyond the picket fence.  (Original broadcast dates July 9, 10 and 11, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:06, 13:06 and 13:06)
0:30:00 - excerpts from The Red Skelton Show   A Mother’s Day program.  (Original broadcast date May 06, 1949. NBC Network. Running time 16:33)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Bull”  Matt Dillon is on the trail of a bad guy — well, two bad guys — and they are after each other. (Original air date November 03, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:02)
1:20:00 - The Gulf Headliners, featuring Will Rogers; a Mother’s Day address (Original air date May 12, 1935. NBC network. Running time 3:29)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Fire”    Detectives Friday and Jacobs are called in by a family that rented an apartment only to be threatened by the landlord with a gun when they try to move in.  (Original air date March 13, 1952. NBC network. Running time 25:57)
2:00:00 - Broadway Is My Beat     Two suspects in a murder case have the perfect marriage, or so the wife claims. (Original air date June 20, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:24)
2:30:00 - X Minus One“Mr. Costello, Hero” Mr. Costello, a passenger on a rocket ship, creates suspicion and dissension, everywhere he goes. (Original recording date July 03, 1956. NBC network. Running time 27:07)
3:00:00 - Screen Directors Playhouse    “Bachelor Mother”   Lucille Ball stars, by audience request, in this comedy about a department store sales clerk, a baby, and the son of the store’s owner.   (Original broadcast date March 08, 1951. NBC network. Running time 58:14)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>May 5, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/831 - May 5, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 May 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Midas Touch Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is at Lake Mojave with killers, killers, everywhere.  (Original broadcast dates July 5 and 6, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:01 and 13:01)
0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks   Eve Arden stars as our favorite teacher Connie Brooks, who is planning to go away to a teacher’s convention with her favorite teacher, Mr. Boynton.  (Original broadcast date November 12, 1950. CBS Network. Running time 26:05)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Miguel’s Daughter”  A Mexican girl named Josefina Ramirez is harassed by two men, and her father swears to avenge her honor. (Original air date August 03, 1958. CBS network. Running time 19:24)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Evans”    An accusation of police brutality involving a narcotics dealer.  (Original air date March 06, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:27)
1:45:00 - The Tenth Man   “Out Of The Shadow”   An attractive job candidate faces discrimination when his mental health history is shared. (Original air date September 17, 1947. The National Mental Health Foundation syndication. Running time 13:19)
2:00:00 - Night Beat     Randy Stone is held up and shot by a seventy-year-old man! What are his reasons? (Original air date March 06, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:35)
2:30:00 - Suspense  Tyrone Power stars; when a man is accused of murder, he runs into a friend, and blackmail. (Original recording date March 22, 1954. CBS network. Running time 29:48)
3:00:00 - The CBS Radio Workshop    “Report On The We’ans” A portrait of our culture, as it might appear to those six thousand years in the future.   (Original broadcast date November 11, 1956. CBS network. Running time 24:53)
3:30:00 - Command Performance    Ginger Rogers hosts a star-studded show, with performances by Frank Sinatra, Alice Faye, and Arthur Q. Bryan appears as Bugs Bunny and Elmer Fudd.  (Original broadcast date August 21, 1943. AFRS origination. Running time 29:06)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>April 28, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/830 - April 28, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Midas Touch Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny heads out to Lake Mojave to investigate a gold mine.  (Original broadcast dates July 2, 3, and 4, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:10, 13:07 and 13:25)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Professor Lute Bone”  A traveling professor offers a magic tonic that cures all ills.  (Original air date November 14, 1953. CBS network.)
1:35:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Plant”    A woman disappears and her husband becomes a suspect. (Original air date February 28, 1952. NBC network.)
2:10:00 - Radio Retrospective: Duke Ellington
2:20:00 - Destination Freedom  “Echoes Of Harlem”  A story of Duke Ellington and how he put his band together. (Original air date November 07, 1948. Station  WMAQ Chicago.)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre    “Dear Ruth”  A romantic comedy about a young girl who writes love letters to a soldier, pretending that she’s her own older sister.  (Original broadcast date April 26, 1948. CBS network. Running time 53:19)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>April 21, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/829 - April 21, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Long Shot Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny flies out to the West Coast. Parts 4 and 5.  (Original broadcast dates June 28 and 29, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:10 and 13:25)
0:30:00 - The Phil Harris-Alice Faye Show   Featuring actor Anne Whitfield as Little Phyllis; a film scout has discovered Phyllis at the talent show, will she be a star? (Original broadcast date November 20, 1949. NBC Network. Running time 29:51)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Margin”  A cattle herder suspects another of stealing his stock, and but doesn’t have sufficient evidence.  (Original air date October 13, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:38)
1:20:00 - 2024 Library of Congress’ National Recording Registry inductees, featuring  Gene Autry and Patti Page
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Phone Call”    Detective Friday and his team investigate a jewelry robbery.  (Original air date February 14, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:08)
2:00:00 - The Eternal Light   “The Battle Of The Warsaw Ghetto”  A story presented for Passover.  The script won an award from the Writer’s War Board when first presented on the eve of Yom Kippur, 1943. (Original air date April 19, 1959. NBC network. Running time 29:32)
2:30:00 - The Adventures Of The Saint “Next Of Kin”  Vincent Price stars, alongside a young Anne Whitfield featured as a young girl who may be in danger. (Original recording date February 18, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:45)
3:00:00 - Escape    “The Birds”  Daphne du Maurier’s terrifying tale of when the birds attack en masse; later adapted into a film by Hitchcock.   (Original broadcast date July 10, 1954. CBS network. Running time 28:02)
3:00:00 - The Cavalcade Of America    “The Battle Hymn of the Republic”  The story of how Julia Ward Howe came to write the title hymn.  (Original broadcast date December 4, 1940. NBC Red network. Running time 29:00)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>April 14, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/828 - April 14, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Long Shot Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny flies out to the West Coast. Parts 1, 2 and 3.  (Original broadcast dates June 25, 26, and 27, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:35, 13:21 and 13:22)
0:45:00 - Old Gold Show   Excerpt of Don Ameche and Frances Langford as “The Bickersons” (Original broadcast date June 11, 1948. CBS Network. Running time 10:49)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Rooks”  Marshall Dillon is sick, but unfortunately crime doesn’t take a sick day. (Original air date October 6, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:41)
1:20:00 - Henry Mancini and “Moon River”, on WNYC’s  Lyrics and Lyricists, March 14, 1971.
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Almost No-Show”    A woman’s brother is missing, and Detective Friday and partner investigate. (Original air date January 31, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:36)
2:00:00 - Father Knows Best  Father has waited until the day taxes are due to file.  (Original air date March 15, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:05)
2:30:00 - The Abbott and Costello Show   Costello has some extra cash to loose before he files his taxes, so it’s off to the races! (Original recording date March 13, 1947. NBC network. Running time 25:43)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre    “Alexander Graham Bell”  Don Ameche stars in the radio adaptation of the film that made him a household name; the biography of inventor of the telephone.   (Original broadcast date May 14, 1945. CBS network. Running time 55:25)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>April 7, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/827 - April 7, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 7 Apr 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Pearling Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is finds the missing girl, but isn’t pleased.  (Original broadcast date June 21 and 22, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:32 and 13:05)
0:30:00 - Mark Trail   “Wildlife Acres”  Mark is hired to take pictures of a Wildlife Preserve, but there isn’t one! (Original broadcast date March 3, 1950. Mutual Network. Running time 29:46)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Another Man’s Poison” A woman’s dead husband shows up, after she’s remarried. (Original air date September 29, 1957. CBS network. Running time 20:23)
1:20:00 - Marlon Brando centennial salute,  “The Well of Happiness”  (UN RADIO. Original date 1 January 1956. Running time 4:43)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Court”    The show leaves the streets of Los Angeles and takes us inside the courthouse for a lifelike depiction of a murder trial. (Original air date January 24, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:38)
2:00:00 - Let George Do It  “The Bewildered Bird Watcher”  A bird watcher hobbyist contracts P.I. Valentine to look into a possible murder case. (Original air date April 19, 1948. Mutual network. Running time 28:52)
2:30:00 - Freedom U.S.A.  Senator Dean Edwards has to decide whether Timber Lake Forest should be turned into a national park — or stay a lumber camp. (Original recording date December 7, 1952. ZIV Syndication. Running time 27:23)
3:00:00 - The Cavalcade Of America    “I Sing A New World”  A radio fantasy about the spirit of Walt Whitman in America.  (Original broadcast date March 19, 1941. NBC Red network. Running time 29:46)
3:30:00 - Lights Out  “Nature Study”  A walk in the woods, along with death and confession. (Original broadcast date June 22, 1943. CBS network. Running time 27:56)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>March 31, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/826 - March 31, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Pearling Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is asked to look into a phony death-claim by a Wall Street financier.  (Original broadcast date June 18, 19 and 20, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:38, 14:34, 14:38)
0:45:00 - The Hour Of St. Francis “Fifty Days”   The story of Simon Peter in the days following Christ’s Resurrection. (Original broadcast date May 20, 1951. Third Order Of St. Francis syndication. Running time 14:26)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Custer”  A stranger has murdered an old man, but Marshal Dillon can’t prove it. (Original air date September 22, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:36)
1:20:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Juvenile Division”     Detective Friday warns parents of juveniles about an uptick in gang influence. (Original air date January 17, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:05)
1:50:00 - Salute to Rosie the Riveter: excerpts from live event “Meet Rosies from across the Nation” held by Rosie the Riveter Trust and Thanks! Plain and Simple (Original date December 14, 2020. Running time 8:17)
2:00:00 - The Jello Program Starring Jack Benny  Jack and the gang go to the circus. (Original air date April 17, 1938. NBC Red network. Running time 26:40)
2:30:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly   Molly has won a contest, and the prize is a made-to-order coulture Easter outfit. (Original recording date March 23, 1948. NBC network. Running time 24:48)
3:00:00 - Destination Freedom “Up From Slavery”  A powerful adaptation of Booker T. Washington’s autobiography. (Original broadcast date March 13, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:59)
3:30:00 - America, Ceiling Unlimited    Joseph Cotten and Constance Moore star in this Easter-themed episode, featuring “Hymn To A Hero,” a message of comfort and a tribute to love. (Original broadcast date April 9, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:14)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>March 24, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/825 - March 24, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Double Identity Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Is Johnny semi-engaged to a serial killer? (Original broadcast date October 25, 1959. CBS network. Running times 19:19)
0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks   Principal Conklin wants all the school band instruments sparkling, so Stretch Snodgrass takes a crack at it… (Original broadcast date April 30, 1950. CBS network. Running time 27:00)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Child Labor”  Oris Sybert hires two orphans to break his wild horses. (Original air date September 15, 1957. CBS network. Running time 22:25)
1:20:00 - This I Believe: Margaret Sanger (Original air date November 1953. NPR network. Running time 4:13)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Red”  Part 2   Detective Friday goes undercover as a narcotics buyer from “up north” to trap “Cadillac Red,” a heroin wholesaler. (Original air date January 10, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:04)
2:00:00 - Defense Attorney  Mercedes McCambridge stars; a building contractor who thinks women are “too emotional” to be good lawyers hires McCambridge on a $15,000 per year retainer.  (Original air date September 18, 1952. ABC network. Running time 29:16)
2:30:00 - Command Performance   It’s “Ladies Night”, with host Betty Grable.  Artists Florence Gill, Maxine Sullivan, Helen Traubel, Connie Moore and Beatrice Kay. (Original recording date September 2, 1944. AFRS. Running time 29:45)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “Midnight”  Claudette Colbert and Don Ameche star in this amusing romance about a down-and-out American in Paris and a Parisian taxi driver, who find themselves considered Hungarian nobility by French Society. (Original broadcast date May 20, 1940. CBS network. Running time 59:38)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>March 17, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/824 - March 17, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Laughing Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is suspicious of the star comedian’s death threats. Parts 4 and 5. (Original broadcast dates June 14 and 15, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50 and 13:50)
0:30:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny   Dennis Day returns after two years in the Navy, and the whole cast does its version of “Allen’s Alley” (Original broadcast date March 17, 1946. NBC Red network. Running time 26:18)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Loony McCluny”  It’s gold, gold I tell you! Or is it? (Original air date September 8, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:55)
1:20:00 - NPR’s Opening Day (Original air date April 2, 1990. NPR network. Running time 5:27)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Red”  Part 1   Detective Friday goes undercover as a narcotics buyer from “up north” to trap “Cadillac Red,” a heroin wholesaler. (Original air date January 3, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:07)
2:00:00 - The New Adventures Of Sherlock Holmes   “The Adventure Of The Blarney Stone” A murder takes place at Blarney Castle.  (Original air date March 18, 1946. Mutual network. Running time 26:47)
2:30:00 - Quiet, Please   “Dark Rosaleen”   When a man’s beloved dies, he contemplates suicide but is taken to a fair place in Ireland by a strange man in a rowboat. (Original recording date March 13, 1949. ABC network. Running time 29:30)
3:00:00 - The Railroad Hour   “Eileen”   Gordon MacRae stars in this musical production of Victor Herbert’s Irish opera. (Original broadcast date March 14, 1949. ABC network. Running time 44:39)
3:40:00 - Dramatizations From Redbook Magazine   “You Have To Have Something”   Romance among the vaudevillians. (Original broadcast date August 18, 1932. Columbia transcription. Running time 14:41)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>March 10, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/823 - March 10, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Laughing Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; the heady romance of moonlight on a lonely beach in Mexico. Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original broadcast dates June 11, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:30, 14:30 and 14:30)
0:45:00 - Grape Nuts and Grape Nuts Flakes Program Starring Jack Benny   Mary Livingston runs the show, broadcasting from New York City. The cast does its version of, “Casablanca” (Original broadcast dates October 17, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 20:27)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Jobe’s Son”  Family matters lie at the heart of this poignant story. (Original air date September 1, 1957. CBS network. Running time 24:36)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Producer”  A trail of pornography leads to a run-down Hollywood studio.  (Original air date February 21, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:28)
2:00:00 - The Eternal Light   “The Search”   Marian Seldes stars in this biography of social and public health advocate Lillian Wald.  (Original air date December 25, 1960. NBC network. Running time 29:37)
2:30:00 - Murder Clinic  “A Scrap Of Lace”  A handkerchief is the clue for detective Rosita Story. (Original recording date September 22, 1942. Mutual network. Running time 29:30)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “Madame Curie”  Greer Garson and Walter Pidgeon star in the story of Madame Curie’s breakthrough scientific discoveries, and her work with her husband Pierre Curie.  (Original broadcast date September 16, 1946. CBS network. Running time 53:05)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>March 3, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/822 - March 3, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 3 Mar 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Malcolm Wish, M.D. Matter”  Edmond O’Brien as Johnny Dollar; Johnny goes to San Francisco to find a missing doctor.  (Original broadcast dates June 20, 1951. CBS network. Running time 28:25)
0:30:00 - Duffy’s Tavern  The gang overhears Archie on the phone to his doctor, and it doesn’t sound good! (Original broadcast dates February 9, 1949. NBC network. Running time 26:35)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Long As I Live”  Doc has been shot, and the only man to save his life is Marshall Dillon, with surgical consult by Doc himself! (Original air date December 8, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:42)
1:20:00 - Five Minute Mysteries “Pattern Of Guilt”  Can you solve the mystery before the country doctor? You’ve got less than five minutes! (Original air date 1948. NBC syndication. Running time 5:00)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Elevator”  A dead woman is found in a hospital elevator. (Original air date April 24, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:53)
2:00:00 - The Doctor Fights   “Mayer Island and Back”  The story of Captain Henry Kessler, a doctor who healed a man whose leg was cut off by a Japanese pilot’s propeller, but who was determined to return to combat flying with an artificial leg! (Original air date June 19, 1945. CBS network. Running time 30:05)
2:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America   “That They Might Live”  The true life story of Marie Zakshefska, a pioneering doctor. (Original recording date October 19, 1942. NBC red network. Running time 25:21)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “The Girl In White”  June Allyson stars in this radio adaptation of the film based on the memoirs of Dr. Emily Dunning Barringer, the first female ambulance surgeon and the first woman to secure a surgical residency. (Original broadcast date May 18, 1953. CBS network. Running time 51:39)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item> vj


<item>
<title>February 25, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/821 - February 25, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Indestructible Mike Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is not going to take no for an answer.  (Original broadcast dates June 7 and 8, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:06 and 13:10)
0:30:00 - Alec Templeton excerpts    multiple excerpts from The Cresta Blanca Carnival and Guest Star (Original broadcast dates April , 1944, May 1947. CBS network and Treasury syndication. Running time, various)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Grass”  A homesteader is being spooked off his farm, but he’s suspicious of the wrong man. (Original air date August 25, 1957. CBS network. Running time 24:23)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Overtime”  A banker’s twenty-two-year-old daughter, Judith Sullivan, has been kidnapped and held for a $30,000 ransom. Barton Yarborough’s penultimate radio performance.  (Original air date December 13, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:49)
2:00:00 - The Tex and Jinx Show    Ethel Waters speaks with hosts Tex McCrary and Jinx Falkenburg about music, theater and show business as a Black pioneer artist. (Original air date August 4, 1947. Station WNBC. Running time 29:35)
2:30:00 - Command Performance   Ethel Waters performs, along with Jack Benny and violinist Jascha Heifetz; Richard Haydn appears as the only “fish mimic” in the world.  (Original recording date July 14, 1942. AFRS. Running time 29:38)
3:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop  “The Great Microphone Mystery”  also known as “The Case Of The Mysterious Leap Year.”  A zany who’s-who of CBS radio in 1940, with appearances by Norman Corwin, Bob Trout, Burgess Meredith and Nila Mack.  (Original broadcast date February 29, 1940. CBS network. Running time 29:59)
3:30:00 - Hollywood Star Playhouse  “The Tenth Planet”  Joseph Cotten stars as a man whose brother has been taken to another planet, to help the Earth recover after its invasion and conquest. (Original recording date September 7, 1952. NBC network. Running time 29:19)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>February 18, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/820 - February 18, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Indestructible Mike Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; corruption, fraud and confusion abound and it’s up to Johnny to untangle the mess. Parts 1, 2 and 3.  (Original air date June 4, 5 and 6, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:45, 13:11 and 13:38)
0:30:00 - Jubilee     Featuring Duke Ellington and Lena Horne. (Original broadcast January 18, 1945. AFRS. Running time 29:18)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Peace Officer”  A Big Broadcast debut, thanks to Ted Davenport of Radio Memories; Marshall Dillon ousts the dishonest sheriff of Tascosa, who swears to kill him. (Original air date August 18, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:20)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Walk”  Sgt. Friday goes undercover as a buyer of heroin to break up a narcotics gang. Actor Lee Marvin appears.  (Original air date November 16, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:17)
2:00:00 - The Hinds Honey and Almond Cream Program    Gracie announces her presidential campaign for the year 1940. (Original air date February 28, 1940. CBS network. Running time 29:12)
2:30:00 - Suspense   “You Were Wonderful”   Lena Horne stars as a wartime nightclub singer in South America, involved in a plot to supply information to the Nazis. (Original recording date November 9, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:59)
3:00:00 - Biography In Sound  “George Washington, The Man Nobody Knows”  A radio biography of President Washington gives a portrait of him both as a “Great Man” and also a man of flaws. (Original recording date July 05, 1955. NBC network. Running time 54:37)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>February 11, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/819 - February 11, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Matter of Reasonable Doubt”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a widow wants to leave all her estate to her granddaughter in her will, but other family members questions her sanity. Parts 4 and 5.  (Original air date May 31, and June 1, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:11 and 13:21)
0:30:00 - The Adventures Of Ozzie and Harriet     Ozzie wants to go to a football game but has promised the boys to go with them on a hike. (Original broadcast October 17, 1948. NBC network. Running time 28:38)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Jayhawkers”  A band of Jayhawkers has been preying on a cattle drive from Texas. The Marshal lends a hand. (Original air date August 04, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:50)
1:25:00 - Radio Retrospective: Vox Pop looks at Mardi Gras 1946, excerpts. (Broadcast March 4, 1946. Running time 8:39)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Canary”  The mother of a sixteen-year-old  has been murdered. (Original air date December 6, 1951. NBC network. Running time 27:03)
2:00:00 - New World A’ Coming     “The Story Of Ted Morgan, A Negro Reporter”.   A Black reporter from the North travels to the South, determined to report on a murder trial, where a Black man is accused of killing a white man. (Original air date May 28, 1944. Station WMCA. Running time 24:45)
2:30:00 - Escape   “The Man Who Stole The Bible”   It’s Mardi Gras time in New Orleans, and a salesman has a date with the devil! (Original recording date May 5, 1950. CBS network. Running time 29:11)
3:00:00 - Let George Do It  “Tag! You’re It”  Bob Bailey as George Valentine. Murder in the radio studio, and a new game show — tag, you’re it! (Original recording date September 25, 1950. Mutual network. Running time 29:18)
3:00:00 - Quiet, Please  “Valentine”  See if you can guess who this true life story is about before the closing organ cue… An Illinois romance almost founders, due to lack of a Valentine. (Original recording date February 13, 1949. ABC Bue network. Running time 29:05)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>February 4, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/818 - February 4, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 4 Feb 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Matter of Reasonable Doubt”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a widow wants to leave all her estate to her granddaughter in her will, but other family members questions her sanity. Parts 1, 2 and 3.  (Original air date May 28, 29, and 30, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:41, 13:41, 13:41)
0:45:00 - Orson Welles Commentary   “The Affidavit of Isaac Woodard, Jr.”  OrsonWelles reads an affidavit attested to by Isaac Woodard, Jr., a Black man, who was beaten into blindness by a white policeman referred to as “Officer X.” Orson vows to search out the identity of “Officer X.”  (Original broadcast July 28, 1946. ABC network. Running time 14:16)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Big Hands”   A homesteader brings her husband’s dead body into Dodge, murdered by a man with big shoulders. (Original air date August 04, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:50)
1:25:00 - Radio Retrospective: Sidney Roger, “Interview with Rosa Parks” (Broadcast December 20, 1962, recorded April 1956. Running time 3:12)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Affair” A man is robbing stores, and then beating the clerks. (Original air date November 29, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:46)
2:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop     “The Reluctant Dragon”  Nila Mack’s adaptation of Kenneth Grahame’s classic story, about St. George and the Dragon who preferred not to fight. (Original air date April 20, 1941. CBS network. Running time 29:55)
2:30:00 - Destination Freedom   “Truth Goes To Washington”   Weslan Tilden stars as Sojourner Truth, a mystic, abolitionist and fighter for women’s suffrage. (Original recording date August 15, 1948. Station WMAQ. Running time 27:54)
3:00:00 - My Friend Irma  A story of plagiarism, kind of. Professor Kropotkin has finished his concerto after years of hard work. After a publisher turns it down, Al and Irma write lyrics to it and have it published as a pop tune. (Original recording date February 16, 1948. CBS network. Running time 26:13)
3:00:00 - Once Upon A Midnight  “Malice Aforethought”  The pilot episode of the series proposed by Alfred Hitchcock himself; a British doctor decides to kill his wife. (Original recording date May 11, 1945. ABC Blue network. Running time 31:57)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 28, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/817 - January 28, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Tears Of Night Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny gets to the bottom of Mrs. Wendover’s confusing past and mental condition. Parts 4 and 5.  (Original air date May 24 and 25, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:10, 13:39)
0:30:00 - The Fred Allen Show  excerpts; The Mighty Allen Art Players do a hillbilly opera called, “The Judge Was A Vegetarian So He Couldn’t Meat Out Justice.”  (Original broadcast June 12, 1940. NBC network. Running time 28:28)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Cow Doctor” Ben Pitcher, a man who hates doctors, sends for Doc Adams to tend his sick cow. (Original air date May 28, 1955. CBS network. Running time 24:35)
1:25:00 - Radio Retrospective: Elvis Presley’s national television debut, with excerpts from Stage Show (January 28, 1956. Running time 6:19)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Hands”  A senseless murder; a woman is found brutally strangled in a cheap hotel room. (Original air date November 22, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:25)
2:00:00 - Bold Venture    “The Bold Venture…By Da Vinci!”  Husband and wife Humphrey Bogart and Lauren Bacall star; a dishonest artist steals a painting by Da Vinci, paints a picture of the “Bold Venture” boat over it, and gives it to Shannon to hang on the wall of his office. (Original recording date 1951. Ziv syndication. Running time 26:27)
2:30:00 - Suspense    “Frankenstein”   Mary Shelley’s classic story about a scientist who creates a man, then is pursued by his creation. (Original recording date November 03, 1952. CBS network. Running time 26:11)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “Pygmalion”  A ripping adaptation of George Bernard Shaw’s play, starring Jean Arthur and Brian Aherne. (Original recording date November 27, 1939. CBS network. Running time 54:03)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>January 21, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/816 - January 21, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Tears Of Night Matter”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny meets the mysterious Mrs. Wendover and gets entangled in her perplexing psychosis. Parts 1, 2 and 3.  (Original air date May 21, 22 and 23, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:04, 13:10, 13:39)
0:45:00 - The Witness  “A Good Man’s Anger”  J. Carrol Naish stars as an elder man, upset about plans to a demolish a neighborhood park to create a parking lot.  (Original recording 1959. The Episcopal Church syndication. Running time 14:22)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Kitty Caught”  Kitty is taken hostage by bank robbers. (Original air date October 16, 1954. CBS network. Running time 25:11)
1:25:00 - Tribute: Telly Savalas featuring excerpts from “Telly Savalas Radio Special: Self Portrait” (1975 Audio Fidelity Records, Produced by Fred Robbins)
1:30:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Bungalow”  Sgt. Friday and his partner seek out tips from a stool pigeon about the perpetrator behind series of second-story jobs. (Original air date November 15, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:41)
2:00:00 - Benny Hill Time    Written by and starring comedian Benny Hill. (Original air date March 1964. BBC network. Running time 29:17
2:30:00 - Family Theatre  “The Pardoner’s Tale”  J. Carrol Naish stars in this adaptation of Chaucer’s tale,  (Original air date July 06, 1949. Mutual network. Running time 28:45)
3:00:00 - Rogue’s Gallery     “Snowbound”  A beautiful woman and her suspicious husband lead Rogue to yet another hit on the head, a bullet in the shoulder and a toss off a cliff.  (Original recording date May 09, 1946. Mutual network. Running time 29:02)
3:30:00 - On Stage  “An Ideal Couple”   Cathy and Elliot Lewis star as a seemingly happy married couple, and tell their story through the medium of a radio game show.  (Original recording date June 18, 1953. CBS network. Running time 29:33)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>January 14, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/815 - January 14, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Matter Of The Medium: Well-Done”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny gets closer to the truth of a phony spiritualist. Parts 4 and 5.  (Original air date May 17 and 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:30, 13:30, 13:30)
0:30:00 - My Friend Irma  Irma’s boyfriend Al won’t work for a living, so she decides he needs a psychiatrist.  (Original air date April 2, 1951. CBS network. Running time 29:23)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Bloody Hands”  A listener favorite: Marshal Dillon is tired of killing, and resigns his job. (Original air date July 14, 1957. CBS network. Running time 24:47)
1:25:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Hit and Run Killer”  An elderly woman and her grandson are hit by a delivery van.  (Original air date November 8, 1951. NBC network. Running time 27:04)
1:50:00 - Radio Retrospective: Max Roach centennial tribute. Murray discusses Marx Roach’s civil rights activism and musicianship with David Rodriguez, Executive Vice President &amp; Executive Producer of New Jersey Performing Arts Center, and former Executive Director of the Apollo Theater.
2:00:00 - The Life Of Riley    Riley and Peg recount his stint in politics. (Original air date October 22, 1948. NBC network. Running time 26:00)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Gift Of Jumbo Brannigan”   William Bendix stars as a safecracker released from jail, who has plans to strike again, until his son surprises him with a different scheme. (Original air date March 1, 1951. CBS network. Running time 28:54)
3:00:00 - You Bet Your Life  Secret word: Floor    Unedited tape of Groucho Marx’s fast-paced comedy quiz show.  (Original recording date March 2, 1949. NBC network. Running time 54:27)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 7, 2024 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/814 - January 7, 2024.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 7 Jan 2024 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Matter Of The Medium: Well-Done”  Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is suspicious at a seance. Parts 1, 2 and 3.  (Original air date May 14, 15 and 16, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:30, 13:30, 13:30)
0:45:00 - Radio Retrospective: Earl Scruggs.  Murray discusses Earl Scruggs’ artistry and legacy with Dobro and lap steel guitar player Jerry Douglas and former NEA Director of Folk and Traditional Arts Barry Bergey.
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Word Of Honor”  After treating a wounded man, Doc gives his word of honor not to reveal the identity or hiding place of the killers. (Original air date January 10, 1953. CBS network. Running time 28:45)
1:35:00 - Dragnet   “The Big Lease”  A man named Chester Dillon has disappeared; a portrait of foul play gradually becomes evident. (Original air date November 01, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:21)
2:00:00 - The Halls Of Ivy  The students haven’t built a snowman outside the Hall residence. Ronald Colman and Benita Hume star. (Original air date February 10, 1950. NBC network. Running time 25:15)
2:30:00 - Escape  “The Abominable Snowman”   William Conrad stars as a man determined to find the creature of the Himalayas, at all costs. (Original air date September 13, 1953. CBS network. Running time 27:37)
3:00:00 - The Campbell Playhouse.  “Twentieth Century”    The screwball comedy by Ben Hecht and Charles MacArthur, set in a cross-country train. Orson Welles stars as a Hollywood producer, master of the snowjob.  (Original air date March 24, 1939. CBS network. Running time 56:18)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 31, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/813 - December 31, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Father Knows Best   Robert Young stars as Jim Anderson, who has resolved for the new year not to lose his temper, ever. (Original air date December 29, 1949. NBC network. Running time 25:49)

0:30:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny     Jack’s New Year’s resolution is to be friendly with Fred Allen. The cast does their annual New Year’s allegory: “The New Tenant.” (Original air date December 31, 1944. NBC Red network. Running time 25:03)

1:00:00 -  The Shadow   “The Man Who Murdered Time”   A mad scientist, about to die, invents a time machine with the ability to repeat December 31st eternally. (Original air date January 01, 1939. Mutual network. Running time 27:26)

1:30:00 - Family Theatre   “The Happiest Person In The World”    William Bendix (Life of Riley) stars with Walter Tetley (The Great Gildersleeve) in this fantasy about “little 1948”, who’s sent out to locate the happiest person in the world. (Original air date January 08, 1947. Mutual network. Running time 29:06)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 25, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/812 - December 25, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Suspense  “The Cave”  A fanciful tale that takes place at Christmastime, about two boys who enter a cave filled with pirates.  (Original air date December 20, 1955. CBS network. Running time 28:06)
0:30:00 - Father Knows Best   A Christmas fable about Hans Christian Andersen and his many children’s characters. Robert Young stars.  (Original air date December 21, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:07)
1:00:00 - The Campbell Playhouse   “A Christmas Carol”   The definitive version of the classic story, with Lionel Barrymore. (Original air date December 24, 1939. CBS network. Running time 58:45)
2:00:00 - Duffy’s Tavern    Jeff Chandler guest stars on Ed Gardner’s show; Archie is depressed and solidly “anti-Christmas” until a stranger pays him a visit. (Original air date December 22, 1948. NBC network. Running time 29:39)
2:30:00 - You Are There   “The Crowning Of Charlemagne”    The events of December 25, 800. (Original air date December 25, 1949. CBS network. Running time 29:19)
3:00:00 - Philco Radio Time   Is there anything more vintage Christmas than Bing Crosby singing “Adeste Fideles” and “White Christmas”? (Original air date December 25, 1946. CBS network. Running time 37:38)
3:30:00 - Family Theatre    “The Nativity ” The story of how It all began, and how it will continue.  (Original air date December 24, 1952. Mutual network. Running time 24:07)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>

<!--

<item>
<title>December 24, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/811 - December 24, 2023.mp3" length="125939712" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>04:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks   The story sometimes called “The Magic Christmas Tree”, Connie Brooks receives visits from all her friends, including Minerva — or was it all a dream?  (Original air date December 25, 1949. CBS network. Running times 28:39)

0:30:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly   Fibber is outside shoveling snow, trying to find his lost key ring. (Original air date December 23, 1947. NBC network. Running time 29:02)

1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Christmas Story”  Marshal Dillon tells a story to a stranger out in the lonesome praire.  (Original air date December 20, 1952. CBS network. Running time 29:56)

1:30:00 - Favorite Story   “Journey To Bethlehem”  The story of the birth of Jesus, told from the unique point of view of Saul of Tarsus, later known as St. Paul. (Original air date December 21, 1948. Station KFI. Running time 28:17)

2:00:00 - Night Beat  Hard-working journalist Randy Stone never seems to get time off from the deadlines and the bylines — so when he gets five whole days off he can’t quite believe the Christmas miracle.  (Original air date December 21, 1951. NBC network. Running time 28:57)

2:30:00 - The Six-Shooter  Jimmy Stewart stars as The Six Shooter; a western-inspired version of Charles Dickens’ A Christmas Carol (Original air date December 20, 1953. NBC network. Running time 28:02)

3:00:00 - This Is My Best    “The Plot To Overthrow Christmas”  Orson Welles introduces this Norman Corwin story told in verse: the attack against Santa Claus! (Original air date December 19, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:03)

3:30:00 - Family Theatre   “The Crossroads Of Christmas”    An inn-keeper of Nazareth is jeopardized by his Roman-hating nephew, who is hiding from the Centurions. (Original air date December 17, 1952. CBS network. Running time 54:20)

4:00:00 - Lum &amp; Abner     The Jot ‘Em Down boys annual “Christmas Story”;  a walk through the snowy woods for a Pine Ridge version of the Nativity story. (Original air date December 25, 1944. NBC Blue network. Running time 14:42)

4:15:00 - Christmas Sing With Bing     Bing Crosby is joined by Jo Stafford, ringing in Christmas Day with all our favorite holiday songs, won’t you sing along?  (Original air date December 24, 1961. CBS network. Running time 37:38)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>
-->

<item>
<title>December 17, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/810 - December 17, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “Small Time Swindlers of Big Time Department Stores”   Charles Russell as Johnny Dollar; a holiday tale about a robber targeting Christmas shoppers. (Original air date December 24, 1949. CBS network. Running times 27:36)
0:30:00 - The Lone Ranger    The origin story for Dan Reid, nephew to The Lone Ranger. (Original air date December 25, 1942. Mutual network. Running time 29:22)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Beeker’s Barn”  Marshal Dillon is called out to Beeker’s barn to investigate trespassers, on a cold winter’s night.  (Original air date December 20, 1959. CBS network. Running time 20:44)
1:20:00 - The Cinnamon Bear   Episode 1.  The first chapter in this beloved children’s holiday serial. Two children find the Cinnamon Bear in their attic, and enlist his help to find their missing silver star ornament.  (Original air date November 27, 1937. Syndicated. Running time 14:48)
1:35:00 - Dragnet   “.22 Rifle For Christmas”  What may be the most popular and highly regarded Dragnet episode of all; a child and his friend play a dangerous game. (Original air date December 22, 1949. NBC network. Running time 26:46)
2:00:00 - Richard Diamond, Private Detective   “The Christmas Show”  Dick Powell stars; a noir take on A Christmas Carol. (Original air date December 21, 1951. ABC network. Running time 26:01)
2:30:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly    Fibber takes on the task of repairing old broken toys that will be given away to unfortunate children, and he’s running late. (Original air date December 24, 1946. NBC network. Running time 29:14)
3:00:00 - Lux Radio Theatre   “It’s A Wonderful Life”    James Stewart and Donna Reed star in the radio adaptation of the classic Christmas movie set in Bedford Falls, about a man with great ambitions, an angel, and a new lease on life. (Original air date March 10, 1947. CBS network. Running time 54:20)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 10, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/809 - December 10, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Sudden Wealth Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a holiday tale about an investment plan promising to double your money seems too good to be true… (Original air date December 13, 1959. CBS network. Running times 22:54)
0:30:00 - Let’s Pretend  “The House of the World”   An allegorical story from this Peabody Award-winning children’s series (Original air date December 26, 1942. CBS network. Running time 29:43)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Home Surgery”  Marshal Dillon is forced to amputate the leg of a settler on the prairie. (Original air date June 23, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:04)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Market”  (Original air date October 25, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:27)
1:50:00 - Radio Retrospective: “On the Adoption of The Universal Declaration Of Human Rights”  by Eleanor Roosevelt  (Original air date Deember 9, 1948. General Assembly of the United Nations in Paris. Running time 6:21)
2:00:00 - The Grand Alliance   A hymn of praise to the United Nations, in honor of United Nations Day; starring Joseph Cotten and written by Norman Corwin.  (Original air date October 24, 1953. United Nations Radio syndication. Running time 28:30)
2:30:00 - Nick Carter, Master Detective  “Shakespeare’s Ghost”  A stolen rare manuscript, a dead body, a thespian ghost! (Original air date December 30, 1945. Mutual network. Running time 26:19)
3:00:00 - Mercury Theatre on the Air    “Julius Caesar”    Orson Welles and John Houseman’s Broadway sensation of Shakespeare’s political drama adapted for radio; a masterpiece of the artform.  (Original air date September 11, 1938. CBS network. Running time 59:26)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>December 3, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/808 - December 3, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 3 Dec 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Red Mystery Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is asked to track down his favorite fishing guide, who happens to be missing! (Original air dates December 20, 1959. CBS network. Running times 24:25)
0:30:00 - The Eternal Light  “The Physician Of Birkenau”   A Polish doctor who survived anti-semitism before World War II and a D. P. camp after the war. (Original air date April 04, 1948 NBC network. Running time 29:36)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Summer Night”  A wagon train passes through Dodge on its way west, leaving behind a baby girl.  (Original air date June 16, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:33)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Story Man”  (Original air date October 18, 1951. NBC network. Running time 27:17)
1:50:00 - Hanukkah Lights  “A Candle for Kerala” by Ariel Dorfman  (Original air date 1992. NPR network. Running time 10:25)
2:00:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly    Fibber and Molly are getting a jump on their Christmas shopping. (Original air date December 07, 1948. NBC network. Running time 27:20)
2:30:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny   Jack is Christmas shopping for shoe laces for Don. Will he get metal or plastic tips? (Original air date December 8, 1946 NBC network. Running time 27:14)
3:00:00 - The George Burns and Gracie Allen Show    Gracie and guest Elsa Lanchester try to get guest Charles Laughton to portray Santa Claus at the Christmas Pageant. (Original air date December 21, 1943. CBS network. Running time 28:49)
3:30:00 - The Adventures Of The Falcon  “The Case Of The Unwelcome Christmas Present”  (Original air date December 24, 1950. NBC network. Running time 27:28)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>November 26, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/807 - November 26, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Silver Blue Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny investigates the theft of thousands of dollars worth of silver blue mink furs, involving teenage gang members and their family members. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates May 10 and 11, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:36, 14:33)
0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks   Connie Brooks is tasked with everyone else’s Christmas shopping and collecting clothes for a charity drive — what could possibly go wrong?  (Original air date December 17, 1950. CBS network. Running time 26:21)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Dodge Podge”  A grown son is forsaking his father for a kinder father-figure.  (Original air date June 09, 1957. CBS network. Running time 22:30)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Shoplift”  Detective Friday and his partner arduously track down the culprit behind multiple shoplifting incidents. (Original air date October 11, 1951. NBC network. Running time 27:18)
1:50:00 - Radio Retrospective: Opera singer Maria Callas
2:00:00 - Casey, Crime Photographer. “After Turkey, The Bill”  A young ex-con is framed for a gas station robbery on Thanksgiving. (Original air date November 27, 1947. CBS network. Running time 29:22)
2:30:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny   Jack gets his tree ready for the holidays. (Original air date December 21, 1952. CBS network. Running time 27:52)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “Miracle on 34th Street”  Our Big Broadcast traditional airing of this famous radio adaptation of the classic film; featuring the three adult stars of the original 1947 movie: Maureen O’Hara, John Payne, and — as Kris Kringle –de Edmund Gwenn.   (Original air date December 20, 1948. CBS network. Running time 53:55)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>November 19, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/806 - November 19, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Silver Blue Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny investigates the theft of thousands of dollars worth of silver blue mink furs, involving teenage gang members and their family members. (Original air dates May 7, 8 and 9, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:36, 14:33, 14:33)
0:45:00 - Lum and Abner   The boys have a hard time parting with their friend, Chester the Turkey. (Original air date November 28, 1946. ABC network. Running time 10:04)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Pal”  Chester is in love … with a canine companion. The trouble is, his heart belongs to another.   (Original air date May 26, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:05)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: John F. Kennedy Assassination. Excerpts from We Interrupt This Broadcast. “The Assassination Of President Kennedy” (3:19) and “The Assassination Of Lee Harvey Oswald” (3:42)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Want Ad”  Grand theft auto begins at the small-time level.  (Original air date October 4, 1951. NBC network. Running time 27:18)
2:00:00 - My Friend Irma  Irma brings home a friend for thanksgiving – a live turkey! (Original air date  November 15, 1948. CBS network. Running time 29:20)
2:30:00 - Father Knows Best  Thanksgiving without the children around seems like a relaxing proposition, until it’s a reality. (Original air date November 23, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:29)
3:00:00 - Family Theatre  “Home For Thanksgiving”  An American woman and her Austrian husband return to the city where he grew up. Arriving on Thanksgiving, they find only ruins.   (Original air date November 27, 1947. Mutual network. Running time 29:23)
3:30:00 - Jeff Regan, Investigator    “The Pilgrim’s Progress”  Jack Webb stars as Jeff Regan, tasked with a seemingly simple gopher job — that turns into a murder investigation.  (Original air date November 20, 1948. CBS Pacific network. Running time 29:26)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>November 12, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/805 - November 12, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Callicles Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny looks for a millionaire’s son who has disappeared without a trace. (Original air dates May 3 &amp; 4, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - A Date With Judy    Oogie brings over “Baby” for Judy to baby sit. “Baby” is the mascot of the high school football team and happens to be a guinea pig. (Original air date August 04, 1942. NBC Red network. Running time 26:23)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “One Night Stand”  Ben Argo arrives in Dodge with $15,000 in gold and two men after him.  (Original air date May 19, 1957. CBS network. Running time 22:28)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big September Man”   A psychological drama, involving a beating.  (Original air date September 27, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:22)
1:50:00 - Radio Retrospective: Astronaut Alan Shephard
2:00:00 - X Minus One  “The Cave Of Night” The plight of an astronaut trapped in space. (Original air date February 01, 1956. NBC network. Running time 27:39)
2:30:00 - The Halls Of Ivy  A football coach is in danger of being ousted by the board of directors. (Original air date October 11, 1950. NBC network. Running time 26:14)
3:00:00 - Rocky Fortune  “The Football Fix”  Frank Sinatra as Rocky Fortune;  Rocky is hired to protect a football player who won’t take a bribe, but who does appear in two places at the same time.  (Original air date February 02, 1954. NBC network. Running time 25:56)
3:30:00 - The Eternal Light  “The Space Builders”  What man may do on the moon someday, is being done in Israel in 1958.  (Original air date December 21, 1958. NBC network. Running time 29:38)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>November 5, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/804 - November 5, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 Nov 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Callicles Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny looks for a millionaire’s son who has disappeared without a trace. (Original air dates April 30, May 1 and 2, 1956. CBS network. Running times 19:02)
0:45:00 - The Roy Rogers Show    Legendary wester-style singer, guitarist and actor on his own show, with (Original air date August 20, 1953. NBC. Running time 21:05)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Sheep Dog”   Marshall Dillon is not looking forward to calling in a young man accused of murder, or telling his hard-working father.  (Original air date May 12, 1957. CBS network. Running time 24:36)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Sour”   A heinous crime involving jewel thieves and an elder woman. (Original air date September 20, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:06)
2:00:00 - The Jell-O Program Starring Jack Benny  The cast looks into the future to see what the show will sound like in forty years. (Original air date January 16, 1938. NBC Red network. Running time 29:27)
2:30:00 - Tales Of The Texas Rangers  “Quicksilver”  The Rangers track down the killer of a ranch family, starting with a clue in the hog feed! (Original air date August 12, 1950. NBC network. Running time 26:05)
3:00:00 - The Ford Theatre   “The Front Page”   Charles MacArthur’s classic comedy about the rough and tumble Chicago newspaper game and the escaped murderer in the roll-top desk.  (Original air date May 9, 1948. NBC network. Running time 56:55)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 29, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/803 - October 29, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Ghost to Ghost Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny investigates a whole town which seems to be haunted, it’s not just a haunted house. (Original air dates May 18, 1958. CBS network. Running times 19:02)
0:20:00 - Lights Out “The Dark”   Arch Oboler’s masterpiece; a 1962 Capitol Records reproduction of his 1938 legendary story about an evil force that turns people inside out. (7:22)
0:30:00 - Suspense    “The House in Cypress Canyon”  Robert Taylor and Cathy Lewis star in a frightening tale about a locked closet, screams in the night and a terrifying vicious creature on the prowl. (Original air date December 05, 1946. CBS. Running time 26:33)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Spring Term”   After an innocent man is killed right on Front Street, Matt figures out that he is the target of a killer hired by Danch, a man with no ear. (Original air date June 13, 1953. CBS network. Running time 27:59)
1:25:00 - The Abbott and Costello Show,  excerpt “Who’s On First?” (Original air date April 17, 1947. NBC network. Running time 4:27)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Waiter”   An elderly shopkeeper has been brutally killed. (Original air date September 13, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:11)
2:00:00 - Quiet, Please  “The Thing On The Fourble Board”  A creature from beneath the earth climbs up an oil well pipe to the surface.  (Original air date August 09, 1948. Mutual network. Running time 23:34)
2:30:00 - Escape   “Three Skeleton Key”  Vincent Price stars in this chilling story about three men trapped in a lighthouse, as ravenous rats descend upon them.  (Original air date March 17, 1950. CBS network. Running time 28:49)
3:00:00 - The Mercury Radio Theatre On the Air   “War of The Worlds”.   Orson Welles and John Houseman’s masterpiece, celebrating 85 years. An immersive experience of martians invading the earth. Sound effects by Ora Nichols.  (Original air date October 30, 1938. CBS network. Running time 59:21)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>October 22, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/802 - October 22, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Shepherd Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny investigates a murdered doctor, a sordid affair and the jealous husband. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates April 9 and 20, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:35 and 14:35)
0:30:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly     Fibber and Molly attend a Halloween party at neighbor Gildersleeve’s house. (Original air date October 24, 1939. NBC. Running time 28:58)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “How To Kill A Friend”   Two outlaws hire an old friend of Marshall Dillons to murder him. (Original air date May 5, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:08)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Seventeen” A teen-age riot in a movie theatre leads to the discovery of a marijuana ring  (Original air date September 6, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:08)
2:00:00 - Night Beat  A slasher is terrorizing Chicago, targeting women. Starring Frank Lovejoy and Joan Banks.  (Original air date November 10, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:21)
2:30:00 - Hallmark Playhouse  “Afterward”  An Edith Wharton ghost story starring Lurene Tuttle. (Original air date August 05, 1948. CBS network. Running time 26:21)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre   “Suspicion”.   Joan Fontaine and her then-husband Brian Aherne star in this Hitchcock classic about a woman who suspects her husband of murder. (Original air date May 4, 1942. CBS network. Running time 53:33)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>






<item>
<title>October 15, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/801 - October 15, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Shepherd Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; A doctor has increased his life insurance to $100,000, feeling that he may be killed. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates April 16, 17 and 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:156, and 13:15)
0:45:00 - Tribute to Dick Bertel   The Golden Age of Radio     Dick Bertel and Ed Corcoran sit down with Vincent Price. (Original air date November, 1972. Station WTIC. Running time 14:05)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Medicine Man”   The law is the star of the show. (Original air date April 28, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:20)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: Dewey-Stassen Presidential debate – 1948
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Crazy”  Has there been a homicide or not? Detective Friday must uncover the truth.  (Original air date August 30, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:59)
2:00:00 - The Weird Circle  “The House and The Brain” An evil spirit kept alive 400 years haunts a house.  (Original air date July 15, 1943. NBC network. Running time 24:48)
2:30:00 - Stroke Of Fate   What if Queen Marie Antoinette had survived the Reign Of Terror? (Original air date October 25, 1953. NBC network. Running time 25:02)
3:00:00 - Suspense   “The Lodger”.   The story of a very unusual “lodger.” Is he really Jack the Ripper? (Original air date February 14, 1948. CBS network. Running time 58:30)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>October 8, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/800 - October 8, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 8 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Laird Douglas-Douglas Of Heatherscote Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired as a bodyguard for a very unique client. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates April 12 and 13, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:46, and 13:46)
0:30:00 - The Phil Harris-Alice Faye Show    Phil decides to take drastic steps to get the attention of the New York press. (Original air date February 05, 1950. NBC Blue network. Running time 26:06)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Bear Trap”  A little bit of harmless boasting turns sparks confusion and jealousy… and danger. (Original air date April 21, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:38)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospecitve: Hubert Humphrey – 1948 Democratic Convention speech
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big In-Laws”  A gang of truck hijackers are striking frequently, and randomly, seemingly without a pattern.  (Original air date August 23, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:16)
2:00:00 - Richard Diamond, Private Detective  A fake spiritualist is taking advantage of a wealthy family, and Detective Diamond is going to prove it.   (Original air date September 10, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:19)
2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries   “The Lonely Sleep”. A lonely window trimmer invents the ideal mannequin…and she’s so lifelike too!  (Original air date September 25, 1945. CBS network. Running time 29:40)
3:00:00 - Radio City Playhouse  “Long Distance”.   Jan Miner gives a tour-de-force performance in this gripping drama, as a wife of a convicted murderer who tries to stay his execution by telephone. (Original air date July 03, 1948. NBC network. Running time 28:07)
3:30:00 - Favorite Story  “The Legend of Sleepy Hollow”.  Washington Irving’s classic tale about schoolmaster Ichabod Crane and the headless horseman. (Original air date May 29, 1948. NBC network. Running time 27:03)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>October 1, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/799 - October 1, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 1 Oct 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Laird Douglas-Douglas Of Heatherscote Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired as a bodyguard for a very unique client. Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates April 9, 10 and 11, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:24, 13:18 and 13:13)
0:45:00 - The Heartbeat Of Broadway  “The Story Behind My Fair Lady” (February, 1959. American Heart Association syndication. Running time 14:22)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Saludos”  Sheriff Dillon must bring three men back to Dodge on horseback — to identify which one of them is a killer. (Original air date April 14, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:31)
1:20:00 - Lum and Abner    The boys plan to dress up like ghosts to scare the widow Jessup out of Lum’s house. (Original air date October 06, 1943. NBC Blue network. Running time 11:31)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Winchester”  Is an older man’s death the result of suicide or murder? Detective Friday and his partner look for answers.  (Original air date August 16, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:20)
2:00:00 - Screen Directors Playhouse  “The Big Clock”.  A classic noir story of a crime reporter who is on the trail of a big murder story, but he can’t reveal the murderer.  (Original air date July 08, 1949. NBC network. Running time 25:52)
2:30:00 - Creeps By Night   “Those Who Walk In Darkness”. Peter Lorre and Boris Karloff team up to inspire terror with this tale of a blind man, his desperate wife and an unscrupulous doctor.  (Original air date April 25, 1944. ABC network. Running time 29:26)
3:00:00 - Best Plays   “Arsenic and Old Lace”.   Original Broadway cast members Jean Adair and Boris Karloff reprise their roles in this screwball mystery black comedy.  (Original air date July 06, 1952. NBC network. Running time 58:17)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 24, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/798 - September 24, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The La Marr Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny’s aborted vacation and aborted romance takes another turn as he closes in on the murderer. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates March 29 and 30, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:33, 14:32, 14:32)
0:30:00 - Richard Diamond, Private Detective    Dick Powell as Richard Diamond; Diamond is hired to be the bodyguard of Timothy… the seal. (Original air date February 05, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:20)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Rock Bottom”  A retired gunman asks Marshal Dillon to return his gun when Largo Greenland comes to town to kill him. (Original air date April 07, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:56)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: President Dwight Eisenhower – Radio and Television Address to the American People on the Situation in Little Rock, Arkansas, September 24, 1957.  
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Screen”  With the help of the Los Angeles News, the police tackle a new and growing problem, crooked TV repairmen.  (Original air date August 09, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:36)
2:00:00 - The Eternal Light   “Men Of The World”.  It’s now six weeks after Yom Kippur, and Nathan and Ezra think that Rabbi David has too much to atone for. (Original air date December 14, 1958. NBC network. Running time 29:44)
2:30:00 - The Big Show    Tallulah Bankhead hosts a cavalcade of stars, including Herb Jeffries, Oscar Levant, Judy Canova and Jane Russell.  (Original air date April 06, 1952. NBC network. Running time 1:27:22)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 17, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/797 - September 17, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The La Marr Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is on vacation, and love is in the air. Unfortunately, there’s also murder. Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates March 26, 27 and 28, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:33, 14:32, 14:32)
0:45:00 - Hank Williams Centennial: Excerpts from Grand Ole Opry (Original air date November 12, 1949. NBC net, WSM station.); Excerpts from Garden Spot Program (Original recording date 1950, various.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Chicken Smith”  The wife of Chicken Smith is seen with the new owner of the Lady Gay Saloon. What will the chicken farmer do about it? (Original air date March 31, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:59)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Sophomore”  A young boy admits a series of petty thefts. (Original air date July 19, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:17)
2:50:00 - The American Trail   “Dispatch To New York”.   Fictitious reporter Tom Farrell writes the story of the adoption of the Constitution in 1787. (Original air date February 06, 1953. The Ladies’ Auxiliary of The Veterans of Foreign Wars syndication. Running time 14:53)
2:08:00 - Eternal Light    “Let There Be Light“.   A new Rabbi in town must gain the trust of his congregants.  (Original air date September 18, 1960. NBC network. Running time 29:58)
2:40:00 - Suspense  “Leinengen vs. The Ants”  William Conrad gives a tour-de-force performance as Leinengen, a man determined to save his land from relentless, vicious, Brazilian Army ants.    (Original air date August 25, 1957. CBS network. Running time 25:45)
3:05:00 - The Adventures Of Philip Marlowe.  “The Fifth Mask”  There were five masks. One for greed, one for cowardice, one for cruelty and one for deceit. They all covered a murder, but it was the fifth mask that really counted! It uncovered the killer! (Original air dates September 08, 1950. CBS network. Running time 29:16)
3:30:00 - Rogers Of The Gazette.  Will’s editorial urging citizens to “Do It Now!,” has unexpected repercussions for an old man and his horse.  (Original air dates November 18, 1953. CBS network. Running time 30:00)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 10, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/796 - September 10, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Jolly Roger Fraud Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an action-packed mystery about a sunken ship in San Diego. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates March 22 and 23, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:47 and 13:37)
0:40:00 - Lum and Abner   Grandpappy Spears has lost his memory, and the boys of the Jot ‘Em Down store are scheming how to bring it back.  (Original air dates April 14, 1943. NBC Blue network. Running time 12:45)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Saddle Sore Sal”  A visitor come to Dodge from the Texas panhandle, with vigilante justice on her mind.  (Original air date March 24, 1957. CBS network. Running time 25:26)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Late Script”  A $20,000 ransom is demanded for the release of a kidnapped businessman. (Original air date July 26, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:30)
2:17:00 - Suspense  “The Rescue”   Jimmy Stewart stars in this nail-biter mystery about a woman on a hotel ledge is threatening to jump to escape her captors (Original air date April 19, 1951. CBS network. Running time 26:06)
3:00:00 - Destination Freedom   “The Making Of A Man”  Part one of the story of Frederick Douglass, an enslaved man who fought for the freedom of his race. (Original air dates July 25, 1948. Station WMAQ. Running time 28:55)
3:30:00 - Destination Freedom   “The Key To Freedom”   Part two of the story of Frederick Douglass, the famous writer, editor and abolitionist.  (Original air dates August 01, 1948.. Station WMAQ. Running time 29:47)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>September 3, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/795 - September 3, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 3 Sep 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Jolly Roger Fraud Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an action-packed mystery about a sunken ship in San Diego. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates March 19, 20 and 21, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:02 and 13:5813:42, 13:37 and 13:41)
0:40:00 - The Stan Freberg Show,excerpts   Stan interviews a shady character claiming to be a union activist. (Original air dates September 29, 1957. CBS network. Running time 17:41)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Spring Freshet”  Two wanted men kidnap Kitty. (Original air date March 17, 1957. CBS network. Running time 18:57)
1:20:00 - Guest Star, excerpts.   Tony Bennett stars.  (Original air date May 09, 1954. Treasury Department syndication. Running time 11:05)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Set-Up”   The cops break up a burglary ring that involves a hatcheck girl. (Original air date July 12, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:13)
2:00:00 - New World A’ Coming    “Hot Spots, U.S.A.”  The role that racism played in the labor tensions in wartime American industry during the Second World War. (Original air date January 07, 1945. WMCA station. Running time 24:37)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Man Who Threw Acid”   A thinly disguised fictional dramatization of the infamous attack on union organizer and newspaper columnist Victor Riesel.   (Original air date July 18, 1956. CBS network. Running time 23:51)
3:00:00 - The Green Hornet  “Dead Men Talk”   An honest judge suspects Axis spies are infiltrating the city’s labor unions. (Original air dates July 25, 1943. NBC Blue network, WXYZ. Running time 29:01)
3:30:00 - Mr. District Attorney  “The Case Of The Hijacked Worker”. The D.A. fights a scheme of “labor pirating.”    (Original air dates August 19, 1942. NBC Red network. Running time 29:42)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>August 27, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/794 - August 27, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The  Clinton Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny continues his investigation of a fire, and every public official seems to be involved! Parts 4 &amp;amp; 5. (Original air dates March 15 and 16, 1956. CBS network. Running times 14:02 and 13:58)
0:30:00 - Halls of Ivy      A young man is upset by a routine genetics lecture.  Ronald Colman and Benita Hume star. (Original air dates October 3, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:34)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Grebb Hassle”  Marshal Dillon is threatened by Billy Grebb, after the Marshal kills his brother. (Original air date March 10, 1957. CBS network. Running time 20:02)
1:20:00 - Accent on Jazz   Chris Albertson interviews Lester Young (Original air date August 24, 1958. WCAU-FM. Running time 5:20
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Love”  A woman has disappeared with her two-year-old daughter. (Original air date July 05, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:02)
2:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks    Mr. Conklin wants to get a jump on the school year, and so he calls school into session on Saturday! (Original air date January 29, 1950. CBS network. Running time 29:26)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Whole Town’s Sleeping”  A serial killer named “The Lonely One” is terrorizing the young women of a small town; Jeanette Nolan stars as a woman who won’t be deterred from her nighttime freedom.   (Original air date  June 14, 1955. CBS network. Running time 24:50)
3:00:00 - Doctor Christian  “Old Battle-Axe”  Jean Hersholt stars as Dr. Christian; a retired Kindergarten teacher finds new purpose living with a family with a very special little boy. (Original air dates November 02, 1949. CBS network. Running time 28:50)
3:30:00 - The Big Show, excerpts     Martha Raye is featured on Tallulah Bankhead’s variety show.  (Original air dates January 14, 1951. CBS network. Running time 17:21)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 20, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/793 - August 20, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Clinton Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny may need some extra help in this confusing mystery about building fraud. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates March 12, 13 and 14, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:45:00 - The Challenge Of The Yukon     “Belle Brady’s Gesture”  Sergeant Preston and his talented dog, King, get involved with Belle, the owner of “The Palace Cafe”. (Original air dates April 20, 1944. Station WXYZ. Running time 14:20)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Colleen So Green”  A beautiful woman comes to Dodge, and men fall all over themselves trying to help her. (Original air date March 03, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:59)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Cliff”  An elder woman has been killed by suffocation, and the suspect is likewise an elder. (Original air date June 28, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:14)
2:00:00 - X Minus One    “The Roads Must Roll”  The engineer union goes on strike, and stops the roads from rolling. (Original air date January 04, 1956. NBC network. Running time (27:43)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Most Dangerous Game”  Orson Welles and Keenan Wynn star in the classic tale of man against man.  (Original air date September 23, 1943. CBS network. Running time 29:57)
3:00:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre    Fred Allen looks at heat waves, summer vacations, and does their own version of “The Hour of Good Intentions”.  (Original air dates June 25, 1941. CBS network. Running time 59:35)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 13, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/792 - August 13, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The  Plantagenet Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired for a private investigation and finds a murdered woman at the start! Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates March 8 and 9, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - The Blue Beetle    “Rounding Up The Payroll Bandits”  The Blue Beetle solves a mystery with new-fangled devices like a mobile phone and mobile recorder. (Original air dates June 26 and 28, 1940. Fox Features syndication. Running time 12:38 and 12:37)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Impact”  Marshal Dillon is suspicious of recurrent “accidents” at a ranch, and an elderly woman is at risk.(Original air date February 24, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:30)
1:20:00 - The Player   “Fate Upsets A Plan”  Paul Frees performs all the roles in this gripping thriller. (Original air date 1948. Capital syndication. Running time 13:47)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Run”  Detective Friday pursues a hit-and-run driver after a deadly attack.  (Original air date June 21, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:08)
2:00:00 - Mr. Chameleon     “The Gold Cigarette Holder Murder Case”   Karl Swenson in the role of Chameleon, a detective on the case of some twisted sisters. (Original air date May 3, 1950. CBS network. Running time 30:00)
2:30:00 - Herb Shriner Time,  excerpts  Raymond Scott and Herb Shriner bring their unique flavor to the airwaves (Original air date September 30, 1948. CBS network. Running time 7:00)
2:38:00 - Suspense  “The Long Night”  Frank Lovejoy stars in a tense and emotional drama about an air traffic controller and the lost pilot he must land safely.  (Original air date July 13, 1958. CBS network. Running time 21:26)
3:00:00 - The Silver Theatre  “Stars In Their Courses” Parts 1 &amp; 2.    Helen Hayes stars in this drama about a talented actress and her whirlwind romance, rise to fame, and marital strife.  (Original air dates November 13 and 20, 1938. CBS network. Running time 27:00 and 28:08)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>August 6, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/791 - August 6, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The  Plantagenet Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is hired for a private investigation and finds a murdered woman at the start! Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates March 5, 6, and 7, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 14:07, 13:46)
0:45:00 - Radio Almanac   excerpt    Orson Welles and Lucille Ball try their hands at comedy together (Original air date  March 8, 1944. CBS network. Running time 13:00)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Hellbent Harriet”  A widow is spiritual and suspicious — and both help her identify her husband’s murderer. (Original air date February 10, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:59)
1:20:00 - The Bob Hope Show excerpt Bob and guest Rhonda Fleming appear in a skit about a happily married couple, based on their newly released film, “The Great Lover.” (Original air date December 20, 1949. Running time 8:39)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Building”  A wealthy woman is missing.  (Original air date June 14, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:02)
2:00:00 - Dimension X     “Hello Tomorrow”   A story of genetic engineering, and imperfection. (Original air date September 15, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:20)
Lucille Ball performs for CBS’s “Suspense”
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Dime a Dance”.  Lucille Ball stars as dance hall girl who is being targeted by a serial-killer of redheads.  (Original air date January 13, 1944. CBS network. Running time 29:22)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  “The Man Who Came To Dinner”    Lucille Ball and Clifton Webb star in the classic Kaufman and Hart play about an obnoxious  — famous — houseguest. (Original air date March 27, 1950. CBS network. Running time 52:07)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>July 30, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/790 - July 30, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Fathom Five Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is involved with a sea adventure – drowned fortunes, cryptic clues and recovered treasures! Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates March 1 and 2, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - Philco Radio Time excerpt     Oscar Levant is Bing Crosby’s special guest on his musical variety program. (Original air date  November 10, 1948. ABC network. Running time 15:23) 
Information Please panel from left to right: Oscar Levant, John Kieran, Cedric Hardwicke, and Franklin P. Adams.
0:45:00 - Kraft Musical Hall   excerpt    Al Jolson ribs show regular Oscar Levant for his prior week’s appearance on competitor Bing Crosby’s show; Mr. Levant plays a beautiful piano piece. (Original air date  November 18, 1948. NBC network. Running time 6:01)
0:52:00 - Information Please   excerpt     Clifton Fadiman puts questions to guest panel including Lillian Gish, Franklin P. Adams, John Kieran, and Oscar Levant. (Original air date  October 11, 1938. NBC network. Running time 9:50)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Cold Fire”  A bank teller has been accused of stealing $2000 in gold and is killed while resisting arrest. (Original air date February 3, 1957. CBS network. Running time 20:29)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Imposter”  A young boy has disappeared, and Detective Friday and the L.A.P.D. extend their search across the country. (Original air date June 7, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:58)
1:50:00 - Interview with Pulitzer Prize-winning playwright Doug Wright, of the Tony Award-winning “Good Night, Oscar”.  Murray and Doug sit down to talk about Oscar Levant, his radio time and his unique brand of genius.
2:00:00 - Command Performance   excerpt   Oscar Levant performs George Gershwin’s “Rhapsody in Blue”. (Original air date March 29, 1948. Running time 6:07)
2:10:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes  excerpts   Jack is in New York City preparing to perform at Carnegie Hall; Oscar Levant appears in a parody of the radio quiz show Information Please (Original air date January 17, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 15:51)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Murder In G-Flat”.  Jack Benny stars as a milk-mannered piano tuner faced with an unscrupulous dilemma.  (Original air date April 5, 1951. CBS network. Running time 24:55)
3:00:00 - X Minus One  “Almost Human”    A newly-created robot falls into dangerous hands. (Original air date August 11, 1955. NBC network. Running time 23:50)
3:00:00 - Night Beat  “The Night Is A Weapon”   A man suffers from nyctophobia — fear of the darkness — and is the unwitting patsy of a man with a murder plan. (Original air date February 13, 1950. NBC network. Running time 29:14)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 23, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/789 - July 23, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Fathom Five Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny gets involved with a sea adventure – drowned fortunes, cryptic clues and recovered trasures! Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates February 27, 28 and 29, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:44, 13:44 and 13:53)
0:45:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly      Fibber, Doc and the Old Timer find the Old Timer’s uranium mine. (Original air date  August 17, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:04)JACKIE ROBINSON holds National Baseball Hall of Fame induction plaque
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Woman Called Mary”  Buffalo Mary has been beaten up and robbed (Original air date January 27, 1957. CBS network. Running time 19:57)
1:20:00 - Jackie Robinson, Hall Of Fame Induction speech (Original air date July 23, 1962).
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Bindle”  Detective Friday goes undercover to expose a narcotics ring. (Original air date May 31, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:15)
2:00:00 - The Adventures Of The Saint  “The Saint” is accused of having a photo that is being used for blackmail, but he doesn’t have the photo! Vincent Price stars. (Original air date November 26, 1950. NBC network. Running time 28:30)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Three O’Clock”.  Van Heflin stars in this nail biter; A man is tied to a time bomb, which is set to detonate at 3 o’clock.  (Original air date March 10, 1949. CBS network. Running time 26:45)
3:00:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes    Jack and the gang visit the Marine Corps Air Station in the Mohave desert; Jack is mining for gold. (Original air date November 07, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 28:59)
3:00:00 - Frontier Gentleman  “The Gold Digger”   Kendall meets two gold miners who have struck it rich…and a saloon lady very determined to take it away from them. (Original air date September 28, 1958. CBS network. Running time 24:36)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 16, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/788 - July 16, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Bennett Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is on the trail of an arsonist. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates February 23 and 24, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:5, 14:01)
0:30:00 - Duffy’s Tavern      Slippery McGuire wants Archie to invest in a scheme to put split atoms back together. (Original air date December 21, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:35)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Categorical Imperative”  Marshal Dillon and Chester ride out into a blizzard to re-capture an escaped prisoner who will possibly be turned loose anyway! (Original air date January 20, 1957. CBS network. Running time 22:29)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Mailman”  Mail box theft. (Original air date May 24, 1951 NBC network. Running time 26:17)
1:45:00 - The Quick and the Dead  “Chain Reaction”  Bob Hope is our host in this Peabody Award winning series installment that won for “simplifying and dramatizing a difficult technical subject and…dwelling on the good as well as the evil that lies in the conquest of nuclear energy.” (Original air date July 06, 1950. NBC network. Running time 12:49)
2:00:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly  The first two episodes in a story arc about Fibber, Doc and the Old Timer hunting for uranium.  (Original air date August 13 and August 16, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:14, 14:15)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Report From A Dead Planet”.  A spaceship lands on a beautiful world and finds that all the inhabitants have vanished.   (Original air date July 10, 1960. CBS network. Running time 19:26)
3:00:00 - Hiroshima Countdown    An excellent radio documentary; many people involved with the development and the use of the atomic bomb against Japan are heard, including survivors from Hiroshima and Nagasaki. (Original air date August 9, 1985. MPR. Running time 56:22)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 9, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/787 - July 9, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Bennett Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; Johnny is on the trail of an arsonist. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates February 20, 21, and 22 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50, 13:50)
0:45:00 - The Smiley Burnette Show      Starring Smiley Burnette – the singing, comic sidekick of Gene Autry, Roy Rogers, and other movie cowboys. (Original air date 1950. Running time 12:03)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Ozymandias”   A land dispute ruffles family feathers.  (Original air date January 13, 1957. CBS network. Running time 21:56)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Blast”  A gruesome story about a woman murdered with a shotgun. (Original air date May 17, 1951 NBC network. Running time 26:12)
1:50:00 - Interview with Joe Webb, radio researcher of Suspense
2:00:00 - Suspense  “Donovan’s Brain” Part One.  A determined scientist plans to keep Mr. Donovan’s brain alive — with terrible consequences.  Starring Orson Welles. (Original air date May 18, 1944. CBS network. Running time 26:21)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Donovan’s Brain” Part Two.  The brain takes over; Orson Welles in a masterful performance.   (Original air date May 25, 1944. CBS network. Running time 26:25)
3:00:00 - The Amazing Nero Wolfe    A murder mystery with the imperturbable Mr. Wolfe solving a case of a missing original Shakespearean folio. (Original air date November 30, 1945. Mutual network. Running time 27:55)
3:30:00 - The Green Hornet “The Great Detective”.  He hunts the biggest of all game!  Public enemies who try to destroy our America! — but who is he? Oliver Perry is determined to find out the Green Hornet’s secret identity. (Original air date December 26, 1944. NBC Blue network. Running time 29:21)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>July 2, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/786 - July 2, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Cui Bono Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder in a small town is a big mystery. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates February 16 and 17, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:45, 13:45)
0:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America      “Declaration of Independence”   The debating, the negotiation, and the personal politics of the days leading up to the signing of the Declaration of Independence. (Original air date January 1, 1936. CBS network. Running time 27:11)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Devil’s Hindmost”   A woman leaves her abusive husband, but it isn’t a clean getaway.  (Original air date January 06, 1957. CBS network. Running time 23:44)
1:20:00 - “Gallant Men” recited by Sen. Everett Dirksen (November 30, 1966. Capitol Records. Running time 2:38)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Trio”   Detective Friday attempts to keep the streets of L.A. safe during a busy July 4th weekend. (Original air date July 03, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:51)
2:00:00 - The Pursuit Of Happiness  Burgess Meredith is the master of ceremonies for this variety program, featuring Paul Robeson, produced and directed by Norman Corwin. (Original air date November 05, 1939. CBS network. Running time 27:40)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “Sorry Wrong Number”   As requested by Big Broadcast listeners! Perhaps the most well-known episode of Suspense; Agnes Moorehead stars as an invalid woman who overhears on a telephone party line a plot to murder someone. (Original air date May 25, 1943. CBS network. Running time 29:09)
3:00:00 - The NBC University Theatre  “The Adventures Of Huckleberry Finn”   A radio adaptation of Mark Twain’s classic; adventures on the Mississippi with Huckleberry Finn, Tom Sawyer, Jim, and other characters. (Original air date July 23, 1950. NBC Red network. Running time 58:16)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>






<item>
<title>June 25, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/785 - June 25, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Cui Bono Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder in a small town is a big mystery. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates February 13, 14 and 15, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:53, 13:53, 13:52)
0:45:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly      In 1954, the future is bold and bright — with new fangled mobile phones and freeways.  (Original air date April 15, 1954. NBC network. Running time 14:26)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Shooting Stopover”   While transporting a prisoner to Wichita, Marshal Dillon and other stage coach passengers are trapped at a way station by robbers who are after a shipment of gold.  (Original air date August 30, 1959. CBS network. Running time 24:06)
1:20:00 - In Person: Dinah Shore (Original air date March 19, 1943. Blue network. Running time 14:53)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Drive” John Iverson is found murdered by a piece of concrete. (Original air date August 14, 1952. NBC network. Running time 26:56)
2:00:00 - Mr. and Mrs. Blandings  Mr. Blandings gets lost while driving the family to their new dream home. (Original air date August 25, 1951. NBC network. Running time 29:12)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “On A Country Road”   As requested by Big Broadcast listeners! The classic thrilled about an escaped madwoman and a couple out of gas in the dark. Cary Grant, Cathy Lewis, and Jeanette Nolan star. (Original air date November 16, 1950. CBS network. Running time 26:02)
3:00:00 - The Jell-O Program Starring Jack Benny    Jack has purchased a new car…a Maxwell! (Original air date October 24, 1937. NBC Red network. Running time 26:16)
3:30:00 - The Whistler  “Highway Of Escape” A young woman, stuck in the desert with her stepfather, finally kills the old man and drives off with the first motorist passing by. A flight across the desert follows. (Original air date July 09, 1945. CBS network. Running time 26:46)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>June 18, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/784 - June 18, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Mason-Dixon Mismatch Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; two fathers lay claim to a young dead woman. (Original air dates June, 1957. CBS network. Running times 28:41)
0:30:00 - The Marriage      Hume Cronyn and Jessica Tandy star; Ben’s father has arrived for a three week visit, and is a most disruptive influence. (Original air date February 7, 1954. NBC network. Running time 23:40)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Marshal Proudfoot”  Chester’s father is in Dodge to visit his son… whom he thinks is the Marshal.  (Original air date July 20, 1958. CBS network. Running time 20:26)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: Coretta Scott King — Solidarity Day Address (June 19, 1968. Running time 7:19)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Drills”  A lot of dogged detective work goes into cracking a difficult case.  (Original air date May 10, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:35)
2:00:00 - The U.N. Story  “Letter From Father”.  “A Human Rights Day Program” produced by United Nations Radio and UNESCO. A father writes a letter to his future child, beautifully delivered by an unsurpassed English-speaking actor, Laurence Olivier. (Original air date 1953. Program #53. United Nations Radio syndication. Running time 14:26)
2:16:00 - Let George Do It  “The Father Who Had Nothing To Say”   The son of a convicted murderer needs the help of George Valentine. (Original air date September 13, 1948. Mutual-Don Lee network. Running time 29:49)
2:45:00 - The Witness “Papa Knows Best”   Robert Young, “America’s Dad”, hosts; J. Carroll Naish stars as an immigrant father who breaks up a gang enticing his son.  (Original air date 1959. Episcopal Church syndication. Running time 14:19)
3:00:00 - The Green Hornet   “Johnny Comes Home”  The Green Hornet helps a father to break ties with a gang. (Original air date August 30, 1945. WXYZ station. Running time 28:04)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>June 11, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/783 - June 11, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Flight Six Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder and mystery in Mexico. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates February 2 and 3, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:40, 13:55)
0:30:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre      Fred Allen tries to interest guest Oscar Levant in his new Broadway show, a spoof of Oklahoma! (Original air date April 23, 1944. CBS network. Running time 22:25)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “The Tragedian”  Marshall Dillon helps an out-of-work actor in Dodge, meanwhile a guilty man’s brother attempts a jail break. (Original air date October 26, 1958. CBS network. Running time 23:47)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Casing”  The L.A. Police lab deciphers fingerprints, photographs, and powder burns to investigate a suicide. (Original air date May 3, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:28)
1:50:00 - The Heartbeat Of Broadway    “The Story Behind Guys and Dolls”.  A wonderful behind-the-scenes documentary about one of the greatest musicals ever written, with the voices of creators Frank Loesser and Abe Burrows, and original cast members Vivian Blaine, Sam Levene, Stubby Kaye, Robert Alda, and Isobel Bigley. (Original air date 1959. Program #2. American Heart Association syndication. Running time 14:39)
2:00:00 - The Damon Runyon Theatre  “The Idyll Of Miss Sarah Brown”   The story that inspired the musical, “Guys and Dolls”; about the gambler “Sky,” and the missionary Sarah Brown.   (Original air date November 7, 1948. Mayfair syndication. Running time 26:35)
2:30:00 - Suspense  “The Hitch-hiker”   Orson Welles’ masterful performance of Lucille Fletcher’s classic, about a hitchhiker and a motorist on a lonely road, together. (Original air date September 2, 1942. CBS network. Running time 29:32)
3:00:00 - Biography In Sound  “The Actor”  What is an actor? This question is opined on by notable members of the theater world of the 1950s, including Laurence Olivier, Tallulah Bankhead, Lionel Barrymore, Ethel Barrymore, Arthur Miller, Uta Hagen, Jackie Cooper, Peter Ustinov, and Jose Ferrer. (Original air date March 6, 1955. NBC network. Running time 54:26)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>June 4, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/782 - June 4, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 4 Jun 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Flight Six Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; murder and mystery in Mexico. Parts 1, 2 and 3. (Original air dates January 30, 31 and February 1, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:40, 13:40, 13:40)
0:45:00 - Lum and Abner      Lum and Abner plan a summer vacation — “back to nature” (Original air date September 8, 1942. NBC Blue network. Running time 12:06)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Cherry Red”  A widow is harassed by her husband’s killer. (Original air date December 16, 1956. CBS network. Running time 21:24)
1:20:00 - D-Day Remembrance, excerpts
1:30:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Saint”   A stolen car racket is a complicated mystery. (Original air date April 26, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:01)
2:00:00 - Dangerous Assignment    Steve Mitchell’s first assignment takes him to Sicily in search of stolen relief supplies.  (Original air date July 9, 1949. NBC network. Running time 29:22)
2:30:00 - A Date With Judy    Judy has been writing fan mail to actor Joseph Cotten, and thinks he has been writing her back… what will she do when he shows up in her town?  (Original air date February 6, 1945. NBC Red network. Running time 26:08)
3:00:00 - CBS Is There  “Sir Frances Drake Defeats The Spanish Armada”  One of the first installments of this popular series — later You Are There — CBS news reporters cover the events of July 29, 1588. An exciting recreation of the sea battle that saved England. (Original air date August 04, 1947. CBS network. Running time 29:50)
3:30:00 - Escape “Conqueror’s Isle”   Supermen are hiding in the South Pacific. (Original air date March 5, 1949.  CBS network. Running time 29:29)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>May 28, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/781 - May 28, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   “The Duke Red Matter”   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; the death of a racehorse raises suspicion. Parts 4 and 5. (Original air dates January 26 and 27, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - Maxwell House Coffee Time      George and Gracie seek a summer replacement, so they can travel to New York to catch the Louis-Conn fight. (Original air date May 30, 1946. NBC network. Running time 25:23)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   “Braggart’s Boy”  Tom Cleveland comes to Dodge from back East, and turns into a gunfighter…or does he? (Original air date December 9, 1956. CBS network. Running time 21:31)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    “The Big Speech”  A young kid has pistol-whipped a doctor and stolen a large quantity of narcotics. (Original air date April 19, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:12)
1:50:00 - The American Labor Hour “Captain Hugh Mulzac”. The story of Captain Hugh Mulzac and members of the integrated crew of the “Liberty Ship,” he captained, the SS Booker T. Washington. (Recorded on January 2, 1943, Running time 14:16)
2:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop   “The Parade”    An anti-war story about a parade down the streets of New York that cannot be seen or heard. (Original air date February 7, 1950. NBC network; San Fransisco origination. Running time 29:43)
2:30:00 - The Adventures Of Michael Shayne; Private Detective   Wally Maher and Cathy Lewis star; Detective Michael Shayne is invited to a party to re-create a murder mystery. (Original air date May 28, 1945. Mutual-Don Lee network. Running time 27:14)
3:00:00 - The Hollywood Radio Theater (The Lux Radio Theatre)  “Battleground”  Excellent war stories about the “Battered Bastards Of Bastogne.” (Original air date December 7, 1954.  NBC network. Running time 53:20)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>May 21, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/780 - May 21, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Duke Red Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; the death of a racehorse raises suspicion. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates January 23, 24, and 25, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:30, 13:38, 13:30)
0:45:00 - Lum and Abner      Lum and Abner plan an elaborate party (Original air date March 11, 1943. Blue network. Running time 11:21)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Tail To The Wind&quot;  A non-violent homesteader is violently bullied. (Original air date November 25, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:14)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Threat&quot;  A man has been attacked and robbed, and knows his assailant, but fear keeps him from cooperating with the police.  (Original air date April 12, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:16)
1:50:00 - Tribute to Jack French, radio historian, excerpts from 2020 interview
2:00:00 - Candy Matson, YUkon 2-8209   &quot;The Eric Spaulding Concert&quot;  Natalie Masters stars as private investigator, Candy Matson; a famous conductor hires Candy to prevent his concert from being sabotaged. (Original air date February 7, 1950. NBC network; San Fransisco origination. Running time 29:43)
2:30:00 - A Day In The Life Of Dennis Day   Dennis writes a dramatic radio program, and then has to play all the parts himself! (Original air date November 14, 1946. NBC network. Running time 25:48)
3:00:00 - The Cavalcade Of America &quot;Check Your Heart At Home&quot;  Shirley Booth stars in a story based on the book, &quot;They Sent Me To Iceland,&quot;. A woman puts aside her dreams of a show business career to volunteer for the Red Cross in Iceland when the war begins. (Original air date December 13, 1943.  NBC Red network. Running time 29:16)
3:30:00 - Broadway Is My Beat Sherman Gates is found poisoned in the loge of a movie theatre, which leads to a murdered photographer. (Original air date December 3, 1949. CBS network. Running time 29:34)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>



<item>
<title>May 14, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/779 - May 14, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Ricardo Amerigo Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a musical mystery. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates January 19 and 20, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:50, 13:50)
0:30:00 - Life With The Lyons    &quot;Mothering Sunday&quot;  Bebe Daniels and her real-life family star in this premiere British sitcom  (Original air date March 31, 1957. BBC. Running time 30:27)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Pretty Mama&quot;  Hank Marble has been shot in the back, leaving behind a young and pretty widow. (Original air date November 11, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:37)
1:20:00 - Aladdin Lamp With Smilin&apos; Ed McConnell  (Original air date 1937. Syndicated, NBC Orthacoustic transcription.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Little Mother&quot;  A woman has been forging charge slips in department stores for the last six years.  (Original air date October 6, 1953. NBC network. Running time 26:24)
2:00:00 - The Life Of Riley   Riley and the family have big plans to pamper Pam on Mother&apos;s Day — but one by one they fall afoul. (Original air date May 14, 1944. NBC Blue network. Running time 22:25)
2:25:00 - The Hank Williams Mother&apos;s Best Flour Show   (Original air date March 15, 1951. WSM station. Running time 11:33)
2:30:00 - The Lone Ranger    A soldier is shot while deserting to help his blind mother. (Original air date February 16, 1944. Running time 28:25)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre   &quot;Lady For A Day&quot;    A comedy-drama about Apple Annie, a Depression-era street person. Her daughter is arriving from Spain, thinking her mother is a society matron. (Original air date May 1, 1939. CBS network. Running time 30:34)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>May 7, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/778 - May 7, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 7 May 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Ricardo Amerigo Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a famous violin sparks mystery and danger. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates January 16, 17 and 18, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:34, 13:34, 13:34)
0:45:00 - Stay Tuned For Terror   &quot;The Man Who Raised the Dead&quot;  Author Robert Bloch&apos;s tale written for especially for radio, about the awesome power and responsibility of reanimating the dead.    (Original air date July 27, 1945. WMAQ station. Running time 13:25)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Brother Whelp&quot;  A gunfighter returns to Dodge after six years, and he finds his old girlfriend married to his brother. (Original air date November 18, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:37)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Friend&quot;  Mr. Gray reports that his wife Hazel has been murdered, but there is something suspicious about the circumstances.  (Original air date April 5, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:58)
1:50:00 - Radio Retrospective: V.E. Day, excerpts
2:00:00 - My Friend Irma  Irma&apos;s boss has purchased a race horse named, &quot;Laughing Boy.&quot; (Original air date June 2, 1953. CBS network. Running time 24:49)
2:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America   &quot;Commencement In Khaki&quot;    A romance about the post-war Army College at Camp Kilmer, New Jersey.  (Original air date January 28, 1946. CBS network. Running time 25:47)
3:00:00 - Murder By Experts   &quot;Summer Heat&quot;    A newly graduated lawyer awakes with a dead body in bed and has a very difficult time getting rid of that body! (Original air date June 13, 1949. Mutual network. Running time 28:33)
3:30:00 - New World A&apos; Coming  &quot;The Meaning Of V-E Day To Negroes&quot;    Oliver Harrington, a foreign correspondent for the Pittsburgh Courier, interviews &quot;average&quot; New York Black Americans.  (Original air date May 20, 1945. WMCA station. Running time 24:59)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>April 30, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/777 - April 30, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Caylin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man is found dead and there are too many suspects. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates January 5 and 6, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:53, 13:45)
0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks    Madison High is holding an auction of some very nice furniture, perhaps Mr. Conklin would care to donate?  (Original air date March 19, 1950. CBS network. Running time 26:13)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Crowbait Bob&quot;  An old man dies and leaves everything to Kitty. (Original air date November 10, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:37)
1:20:00 - Radio Retrospective: 1948 Kentucky Derby with Clem McCarthy (Original air date May 1, 1948. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Trunk&quot;   A divorcee named Josephine Allen has been murdered, and her body found in a car trunk.  (Original air date September 7, 1954. NBC network. Running time 26:11)
2:00:00 - The Jack Benny Program For Grape-Nuts and Grape-Nuts Flakes.   Jack has sold a broken down horse to Rochester for $4. Rochester&apos;s entered him in the Kentucky Derby! (Original air date April 25, 1943. NBC Red network. Running time 29:29)
2:30:00 - Suspense  &quot;Elementals&quot;    Stephen Vincent Benét&apos;s story of primal instinct versus human resolve. Can a man and a woman go without food for one week, and then not fight each other for a crumb?  (Original air date June 12, 1960. CBS network. Running time 24:21)
3:00:00 - Four For The Fifth   &quot;The Laughter&quot;    Fred MacMurray stars in this story of the courage of resilience and evils of complacency.  (Original air date June 17, 1944. Treasury Department syndication. Running time 30:34)
3:30:00 - Mr. Keen, Tracer Of Lost Persons   &quot;The Engaged Girl Murder Case&quot;    Mr. Keen solves a murder case while on horseback! (Original air date November 10, 1949. CBS network. Running time 26:17)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>April 23, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/776 - April 23, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Caylin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man is found dead and there are too many suspects. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates January 2, 3 and 4, 1956. CBS network. Running times 13:36, 13:36, 13:36)
0:45:00 - Radio Retrospective: Dorothy Thompson    An excerpt from an NBC special broadcast, Ms. Thompson reports on Nazi Germany&apos;s invasion of Poland. (Original air date September 2, 1939. NBC network. Running time approximately 10:00)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Dirty Bill&apos;s Girl&quot;  Rose, the card dealer in the Long Branch, plans to kill a man. (Original air date October 28, 1956. CBS network. Running time 22:32)
1:20:00 - Symphony Sid, excerpt.   Tito Puente performs in a band remote from the &quot;Birdland&quot; club in New York City. (Original air date September 22, 1952.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Ben&quot;  A man is pulled from his car on a deserted street, robbed, and beaten viciously before his car is stolen.   (Original air date March 15, 1951. NBC network. Running time 26:07)
2:00:00 - The Halls of Ivy   Dr. Hall has been asked to recite a poem for an appreciative audience, but is reluctant to participate. (Original air date July 5, 1950. NBC network. Running time 26:47)
2:30:00 -  Will of Stratford    An NBC special program celebrating the 373rd anniversary of William Shakespeare&apos;s birth.  (Original air date April 15, 1937. NBC network. Running time 29:52)
3:00:00 - Suspense   &quot;Make Mad The Guilty&quot;    Hume Cronyn stars as an out-of-work Shakespearean actor who fakes his own death when his wife leaves him for her muscular lover.  (Original air date April 10, 1948. CBS network. Running time 29:22)
3:30:00 - The Lady Esther Screen Guild Theatre   &quot;First Love&quot;    Shirley Temple stars in this modern Cinderella story about a young girl who finds romance, despite her cruel relatives.   (Original air date May 14, 1945. CBS network. Running time 26:39)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>April 16, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/775 - April 16, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Forbes Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; mystery abounds in a NY embezzlement case. Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates December 29 and 30, 1955. CBS network. Running times 13:32 and 14:32)
0:45:00 - The Stan Freberg Show     Program number 1.  Comedian Stan Freberg lampoons the entertainment industry, and Las Vegas casinos. (Original air date July 14, 1957. CBS network. Running time 29:40)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Til Death Do Us&quot;    (Original air date October 21, 1956. CBS network. Running time 24:50)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Couple&quot;   A confidence team specializes in victimizing churches and clergymen.  (Original air date February 22, 1951. NBC network. Running time 25:51)
2:00:00 - The Raleigh Room    The incomparable Hildegarde visits with special guests Hank Greenberg, Paul McGrath and Jackie Keck. (Original air date October 16, 1945. NBC network. Running time 29:38)
2:30:00 -  The Cavalcade Of America    &quot;Sawdust Underground&quot;   The story of two G. I.&apos;s who escape from Nazi occupied France by hiding as a clown and an acrobat in a circus.  (Original air date September 10, 1945. NBC network. Running time 29:11)
3:00:00 - Suspense   &quot;Crossfire&quot;    Starring three Roberts: Robert Young, Robert Ryan, Robert Mitchum. A murder mystery about a fanatical antisemite. Which of three soldiers committed murder?  (Original air date April 10, 1948. CBS network. Running time 59:30)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>April 9, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/774 - April 9, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Forbes Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; mystery abounds in a NY embezzlement case. Parts 1, 2 &amp; 3. (Original air dates December 26, 27 and 28, 1955. CBS network.)
0:45:00 - Stay Tuned For Terror   &quot;The BoogeyMan Will Get You&quot;   A psychological thriller about a teenage girl&apos;s suspicions and a bachelor. (Original air date 1945. Station WMAQ)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Gunshot wound&quot;    Revenge exacts a deadly toll. (Original air date October 14, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Radio retrospective: Mercury 7 Press Conference, April 9 1959.
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Cast&quot; Over a dozen men have disappeared without a trace.  (Original air date February 8, 1951. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - The Lucky Strike Program Starring Jack Benny    Benny&apos;s traditional Easter Sunday show – he and Mary Livingstone stroll down Wilshire Boulevard in Los Angeles, singing &quot;Happy Easter,&quot; and encountering their friends along the way. (Original air date April 13, 1952. CBS network.)
2:30:00 - The Greatest Story Ever Told    &quot;The Resurrection&quot;    (Original air date April 06, 1947. ABC network.)
3:00:00 - The Great Gildersleeve  Sunrise Easter service and an unexpected blessing. (Original air date April 9, 1952. NBC network.)
3:30:00 - The Six-Shooter     A Big Broadcast Easter tradition; Jimmy Stewart stars as Brett Poinset, and investigates a crisis at Easter Creek. (Original air date April 15, 1954. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>









<item>
<title>April 2, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/773 - April 2, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 2 Apr 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Todd Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an expensive tip from an ex-con starts Johnny on the trail of stolen goods, and a murder attempt; Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates January 12 and 13, 1956. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - Take It Or Leave It     Fred Allen and his cast of regulars take on inflation, rationing, and Veronica Lake&apos;s new ‘do; Falstaff Openshaw recites a poem on rationing. (Original air date February 28, 1943. NBC network)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;The Gambler&quot;    A riverboat gambler named Jim Ascombe comes to Dodge to kill Jim Cass (Original air date October 07, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Radio retrospective: Interview with Jack Webb, from 1958 reel to reel tape interview.
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Children&quot;   A mother is missing, and her children are begging for food. (Original air date February 01, 1951. NBC network.)
1:50:00 - Excerpt from Anthology  &quot;The Three Witches of Macbeth&quot;  Alec Guinness stars in scenes from Shakespeare&apos;s Scottish Play. (Original air date February 01, 1951. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Dangerous Assignment  Plans for an improved Nazi &quot;buzz bomb&quot; have been stolen. (Original air date February 24, 1951. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - Eternal Light    &quot;The Passover Of Rembrandt Van Rijn&quot;   The famous painter of Amsterdam is commissioned to paint Moses for the city fathers. He searches for descendants of the biblical figure to use for his model.  (Original air date April 18, 1948. NBC network.)
3:00:00 - The CBS Radio Mystery Theatre      &quot;The Corpse That Would Not Die&quot;  A suspenseful tale adapted from Émile Zola&apos;s Thérèse Raquin (Original air date June 07, 1976. CBS network.)
3:30:00 - Lum and Abner      A haunting we will go! (Original air date October 07, 1943. Blue network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>March 26, 2023 - Git</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/772 - March 26, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Todd Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; an expensive tip from an ex-con starts Johnny on the trail of stolen goods, and a murder attempt; Parts 1, 2 &amp;3. (Original air dates January 9, 10 and 11, 1956. CBS network.) 
0:40:00 - X Minus One    &quot;Martian Sam&quot;   The Los Angeles Dodgers sign a real Martian as a left-handed pitcher. (Original air date April 3, 1957. NBC network)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;The Brothers&quot;    (Original air date September 30, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Tomato&quot;   Friday and the L.A. police track down &quot;The Big Tomato&quot; (Original air date January 25, 1951. NBC network.)
1:50:00 - Interview with Susan Stamberg and Deanna Hackney discussing &quot;Women in the Newsroom&quot; 
2:00:00 - The Cavalcade Of America    &quot;Nellie Was A Lady&quot;   The adventures of Nellie Bly, trailblazer reporter for the New York World, who made an around the world journey in less than eighty days, and forever opened up opportunities for women reporters. (Original air date September 17, 1945. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - Destination Freedom    &quot;The Ballad Of Satchell Paige&quot;   The story of the &quot;greatest pitcher of all time.&quot;   (Original air date May 15, 1949. Station WMAQ.)
3:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks      Sometimes called &quot;The Baseball Uniform Shortage&quot;, Madison High doesn&apos;t have enough funds to have a baseball team this spring, but Miss Brooks has a plan, naturally.  (Original air date March 26, 1950. CBS network.)
3:30:00 - The Adventures Of Philip Marlowe      &quot;The Anniversary Gift&quot;. A rare appearance of William Conrad as Philip Marlowe; Marlowe is hired to retrieve a valuable platinum watch from a corpse.  (Original air date April 11, 1950. CBS network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>March 19, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/771 - March 19, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar  &quot;The Lansing Fraud&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man with a $50,000 policy dies but the cause is suspicious; Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates December 15 and 16, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:40:00 - The Adventures of Jane Arden  &quot;Elevator Murder&quot;  Part One, News reporter Jane Arden is trapped in a crowded elevator with a killer, but who is it? Written by Marianne Prugh. (Original air date January 15, 1941. Webber Productions syndication)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke  &quot;Box O&apos;rocks&quot;    Marshall Dillon must solve the mystery of a faux funeral and a coffin filled with rocks. (Original air date September 23 1956. CBS network.)
1:37:00 - Dragnet  &quot;The Big Dance&quot;  (Original air date January 18, 1951. NBC network.)
2:17:00 - Night Beat  Randy Stone dials his phone at random and speaks to a woman about to be murdered by her insane husband. (Original air date July 31, 1950. NBC network.)
3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre  &quot;Front Page Woman&quot;    Paulette Goddard and Fred MacMurray co-star in this adaptation of the film about two news reporters duking it out for clout in the newsroom. (Original air date January 16, 1939. CBS network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>March 12, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/770 - March 12, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar  &quot;The Lansing Fraud&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar; a man with a $50,000 policy dies but the cause is suspicious; Parts 1, 2 &amp;3. (Original air dates December 12, 13, and 14, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:44:00 - Policewoman  &quot;The Case Of The Scheming Bridegroom&quot;   Based on the adventures of the real New York City policewoman, Mary Sullivan. (Original air date June 29, 1947. ABC network)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke  &quot;Thick ‘n&apos; Thin&quot;    Two old friends begin fighting. (Original air date September 16, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Franklin D. Roosevelt addresses the nation for the first time as President of the United States, excerpt (Original air date March 12 1933. All networks.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet  &quot;The Big Holdup&quot;    Detective Friday and his partner are after a viscous killer known as &quot;The Rattlesnake Bandit&quot; . (Original air date January 4, 1951. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Maxwell House Coffee Time  Gracie is inspired to train Girl Scouts-to-be, as the Girl Scouts celebrate their thirty seventh anniversary. (Original air date March 10, 1949. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - The Whistler  &quot;Married To Murder&quot;   Cathy Lewis and Elliot Lewis star in a twisted tale of the art of murder.   (Original air date September 25, 1944. CBS network.)
3:00:00 - Author Meets The Critics  A discussion about &quot;American Argument,&quot; by Pearl Buck and Eslanda Goode Robeson. (Original air date February 06, 1949. NBC network, WNBC New York.)
3:30:00 - The Railroad Hour  &quot;Spring Is Here&quot;. Gordon MacRae stars in this rare musical adaptation of an even rarer musical by Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart  (Original air date May 12, 1952. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>March 5, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/769 - March 5, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 Mar 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar  &quot;The Cronin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar is pulled in to protect a gorgeous and valuable necklace with diamonds and emeralds, known as the  &quot;Circle Of Fire&quot; ; Parts 4 &amp; 5. (Original air dates December 8 and 9, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - The Marriage  Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn star; Elizabeth wants a more meaningful life. (Original air date November 15, 1953.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke  &quot;Belle&apos;s Back&quot;    A woman named Belle has returned to Dodge, after living with a gunman. (Original air date September 9, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Oscar Brand&apos;s Folk Song Festival, excerpt featuring Doc Watson (Original air date 1970. WNYC station.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet  &quot;The Big Break&quot;  As slippery a devil as Friday and Romero have ever encountered. (Original air date December 14, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - You Are There  &quot;The Trial Of Anne Hutchinson&quot;  Puritans put the first American feminist on trial in 1637. (Original air date September 26, 1948. CBS network.)
2:30:00 - The Private Files Of Rex Saunders  &quot;High Dividends Or Shallow Graves&quot;  Rex Harrison stars as a &quot;gentleman detective&quot;.   (Original air date May 30, 1951. NBC network.)
3:00:00 - The NBC University Theatre  &quot;Hedda Gabler&quot;    Ibsen&apos;s classic play portrays hardship and life troubles faced by women during 19th century. (Original air date August 27, 1950. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>February 26, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/768 - February 26, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Cronin Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar is pulled in to protect a gorgeous and valuable necklace with diamonds and emeralds, known as the  &quot;Circle Of Fire&quot; ; Parts 1, 2, and 3. (Original air dates December 5, 6 and 7, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - It&apos;s Time To Smile, excerpt    Guest Betty Hutton wows the crowd on Eddie Cantor&apos;s show, also starring Rudy Vallee. (Original air date January 27, 1943. NBC Red.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Old Pal&quot;    A man is murdered, and the Wells Fargo money stolen; suspicion circles around a young woman trying to leave town. (Original air date September 02, 1956. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Picture&quot;  Sergeant Friday breaks a vicious Los Angeles pornography ring. (Original air date December 07, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - The Ford Theatre    &quot;A Connecticut Yankee In King Arthur&apos;s Court&quot;   Mason Adams stars. The Mark Twain classic: a satire of chivalry, monarchy, religion, and superstition, celebrating American democratic values and ingenuity. (Original air date October 05, 1947. NBC network.)
2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries    &quot;Tempo In Blood&quot;  A murderer introduces himself to the murderee, and a piano player plays a wrong note!   (Original air date January 12, 1948. CBS network.)
3:00:00 - What Must Be Done      &quot;Education&quot; Part two.  A special series and fascinating discussion about the scourge of racism in the late &apos;60s, and how it affects public education. Panel discussion lead by Percy Sutton. (Original air date July 8 1968. WLIB Radio, New York.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>




<item>
<title>February 19, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/767 - February 19, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Henderson Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a death in the exotic locale of… Montana?  ; Parts 4 and 5 (Original air dates December 1 and 2, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:30:00 - Rogers Of The Gazette    Will Rogers, Jr. stars as newspaper editor in a small town, and has been receiving letters from a mysterious &quot;A. Lincoln&quot;. (Original air date November 11, 1953. CBS.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;No Sale&quot;    Two bullies demand that Kitty sell them the Long Branch Saloon, but she&apos;s not going down without a fight. (Original air date August 26, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - One Out Of Seven    &quot;Equality, A Most Wonderful Thing&quot;.  Jack Webb does all the voices in this program, except for the singing of baritone Joseph James; program explores racial equality in post-war America. (Original air date March 20, 1946. KGO station.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Car&quot;  Someone has been robbing food markets, but not the person who confesses. (Original air date November 30, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - An Open Letter On Race Hatred    Peabody Award winning broadcast written and directed by William N. Robson, detailing the 1940s Detroit race riots. (Original air date July 24, 1943. CBS network.)
2:30:00 - Black Radio: Telling It Like It Was    &quot;Civil Rights and Let&apos;s Have Church&quot;   In the fifties and sixties, Black DJs did more than play music — they were among the first messengers of the civil rights movement. In the second half of the hour, we hear about the importance of religious broadcasting to the Black community.   (Original air date January 1996. PRX.)
3:00:00 - X Minus One      &quot;Dwellers In Silence&quot;  Twenty years after mankind abandoned the Earth, a spaceship from Mars lands. (Original air date November 10, 1955. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>





<item>
<title>February 12, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/766 - February 12, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Henderson Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a death in the exotic locale of… Montana?  ; Parts 1, 2 and 3 (Original air dates November 28, 29, and 30, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:35:00 - Our Miss Brooks    Miss Brooks tries to get Mr. Boynton to take her out to dinner for Valentine&apos;s Day. (Original air date February 19, 1950. CBS.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Annie Oakley&quot;    A woman&apos;s love is being fought for – at least she claims it is. (Original air date August 19, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Rate Your Mate, excerpt    Host Joey Adams questions a husband and wife team on this radio precursor to the popular TV show The Newlyweds. (Original air date August 5, 1950. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Betty&quot;  A gang of swindlers has selling worthless junk to relatives of dearly departed, using obituaries as their entry point.  (Original air date November 23, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Black Radio: Telling It Like It Was    25th Anniversary Edition, Hour Two: &quot;Jack Cooper &amp; Al Benson&quot; and &quot;WDIA, The Goodwill Station&quot;    A brilliant documentary chronicling the history of African Americans and their representation in radio from the earliest days through the 1940s and 1950s. (Original air date January, 1996. PRX.)
2:30:00 - Let George Do It     &quot;The Eight Ball&quot;   Detective Valentine is mixed up in a mystery involving a dead man — who is also named George Valentine!  (Original air date April 2, 1951. Mutual network.)
3:00:00 - Destination Freedom      &quot;The Heart Of George Cotton&quot;  The story of Dr. Ulysses Dailey and Daniel Hale Williams and their pioneering efforts in heart surgery. (Original air date August 8, 1948. Station WMAQ.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>February 5, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/765 - February 5, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 5 Feb 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar   &quot;The Amy Bradshaw Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates death threats against a famous actress; Parts 4 and 5 (Original air dates November 24 and 25, 1955. CBS network.) 
0:25:00 - Jubilee    Ernie &quot;Bubbles&quot; Whitman as M.C. of this variety show created for black soldiers in WWII, featuring Cab Calloway, Burns and Allen and Nat King Cole.  (Original air date February 14, 1944. AFRS.)
0:55:00 - The Studs Terkel Show    featuring Sidney Poitier  (Original air date October 1, 1959. WFMT station.)
1:00:00 - Gunsmoke   &quot;Snakebite&quot;    Strangers arrive in Dodge and kill a man’s dog, and revenge is swift. (Original air date August 12, 1956. CBS network.)
1:20:00 - Mail Call    Ida Lupino, Robert Benchley and Groucho Marx perform a parade of the thriller Double Indemnity. (Original air date August 12, 1956. CBS network.)
1:30:00 - Dragnet    &quot;The Big Parrot&quot;  Arson in a rooming house covers up a double murder.  (Original air date November 16, 1950. NBC network.)
2:00:00 - Black Radio: Telling It Like It Was    25th Anniversary Edition &quot;Hour One: &quot;In the Beginning&quot; and &quot;Pride &amp; Enlightenment&quot;    A brilliant documentary chronicling the history of African Americans and their representation in radio from the earliest days through the 1940s and 1950s. (Original air date January 1, 1996. PRX.)
2:30:00 - Freedom&apos;s People      &quot;Contributions To Music&quot; part of  &quot;The Story Of The American Negro.&quot; The music that the slaves brought with them to America, and how it grew.  (Original air date September 21, 1944. NBC Red network.)
3:00:00 - Candy Matson, Yukon 2-8209       &quot;Symphony Of Death&quot;  A famous composer predicts that he is going to die, and leaves a musical trail of clues. (Original air date June 20, 1950. NBC network.)
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 29, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/764 - January 29, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Amy Bradshaw Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates death threats against a famous actress; Parts 1, 2 and 3 (Original air dates November 21, 22, and 23, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:40:00 - The Chase and Sanborn Hour <br /> Clark Gable guest stars and goes head to head with Charlie McCarthy.  (Original air date October October 29, 1939. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Lost Rifle&quot;    An upsetting tale of child abuse and the consequences. (Original air date July 29, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Mother&quot;  A newborn has gone missing from the hospital. (Original air date November 9, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - Romance <br /> &quot;The Bear&quot;    A western adaptation of Chekov&apos;s one-act farce of the same name, starring Virginia Gregg and John Dehner. (Original air date November 5, 1955. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Charlie McCarthy Show <br /> W.C. Fields and Charlie McCarthy face off at a barbershop.  (Original air date February 20, 1944. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Lux Radio Theatre <br /> &quot;Kiss of Death&quot;   Victor Mature stars in screenwriter Ben Hecht&apos;s story of innocent gangsters, molls and revenge. (Original air date January 12,1948. CBS network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 22, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/763 - January 22, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Broderick Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar must find a missing woman, who was last seen when she was only 11 years old; PARTS 4 and 5 (Original air dates November 17 and 18, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Our Miss Brooks <br /> Walter Denton&apos;s radio gives a strange and concerning weather report.  (Original air date October 08, 1950. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Letter of the Law&quot;    Marshal Dillon is forced to evict a reformed gunfighter named Brandon Teak from his land. (Original air date July 15, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Church&quot;  A new member of the congregation receives anonymous letters and phone calls threatening her with murder. (Original air date November 2, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>1:50:00 - The Radio Almanac <br /> Ann Sothern and Orson Welles star.  (Original air date May 17, 1944. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Adventures Of Philip Marlowe <br /> &quot;Red Wind&quot;    A real Raymond Chandler story of double-crossing. (Original air date September 26, 1948. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Inner Sanctum Mysteries <br /> &quot;The Vengeful Corpse&quot;  A woman burned as a witch returns to enact revenge.  (Original air date September 12, 1949. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Eternal Light <br /> &quot;Try Not To Love Such A Country&quot;  Stories from Sholem Aleichem:  A young boy arrives from the old country with many of the traditions from the old country.   (Original air date January 13, 1963. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>3:30:00 - I Was A Communist For The FBI <br /> &quot;Draw The Red Curtain&quot;. Dana Andrews stars as comrade Cvetic, assigned to help the Party take over an actor&apos;s guild.  (Original air date July 06, 1952. ZIV Syndication.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 15, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/762 - January 15, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Broderick Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar must find a missing woman, who was last seen when she was only 11 years old; PARTS 1, 2 and 3 (Original air dates November 14, 15 and 16, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - The Studs Terkel Program <br /> Studs Terkel interviews Martin Luther King, Jr.  (Original air date October 28, 1964. Chicago station WFMT.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Passive Resistance&quot;    A man chooses to solve his quarrels without gun violence, and needs protection. (Original air date July 8, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - Lum and Abner <br /> Lum and Abner look into insurance.  (Original air date February 1, 1945. NBC Blue network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Meet&quot;   Joe Friday has a tense assignment, risking his life going undercover. (Original air date October 26, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - New World A&apos;Coming <br /> &quot;Executive Order 8802&quot;     The history of Executive Order 8802, a temporary end to racial segregation in hiring and in the military during WWII. (Original air date November 5, 1944. New York City station WMCA.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Adventures Of Sam Spade, Detective <br /> &quot;The Lazarus Caper&quot;.  Howard Duff stars as Sam Spade.  (Original air date September 12, 1948. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Beyond Tomorrow <br /> &quot;Incident At Switchpath&quot;   An invasion! Based on the story, &quot;The Sky Was Full Of Ships,&quot; by Theodore Sturgeon.  (Original air date April 11, 1950. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>3:30:00 - Arch Oboler&apos;s Plays <br /> &quot;Lust For Life&quot;.  The story of Vincent Van Gogh.  (Original air date August 16, 1945. NBC network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 8, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/761 - January 8, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 9 Jan 2023 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Lorko Diamonds Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a diamond robbery in Algiers; PARTS 4 and 5 (Original air dates November 10 and 11, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - The Texaco Star Theatre <br /> Fred Allen&apos;s first show of the 1942 season, with guest star Charles Laughton.  (Original air date October 4, 1942. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Gun For Chester&quot;    Chester fears that someone is out to kill him. (Original air date July 1, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - excerpt from  Duffy&apos;s Tavern    Archie wants to film his life story, and hires comedian Larry Storch to impersonate Hollywood stars to fill out the cast.  (Original air date January 11, 1946. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Grandma&quot;   An elderly woman has been passing bad checks. (Original air date October 19, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - X Minus One <br /> &quot;Nightmare&quot;     Based on Stephen Vincent Benet&apos;s poem, &quot;Revolt Of The Machines&quot;;  a clerk discovers what the computers are planning. (Original air date July 21, 1955. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Big Show <br /> Tallulah Bankhead&apos;s star-studded spectacle with guests Eddie Cantor, José Ferrer, Bob Hope, Jimmy Durante, and music by Meredith Willson.  (Original air date November 19, 1950. NBC network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>January 1, 2023</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/760 - January 1, 2023.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 2 Jan 2023 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> 
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Lorko Diamonds Matter&quot;   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar investigates a diamond robbery in Algiers; PARTS 1,2 and 3 (Original air dates November 7,8 and 9, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:40:00 - Suspense <br /> &quot;The Thirty-Second Of December&quot;   A gambler buys a watch with many dials, including one that travels through time  (Original air date December 28, 1958. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Pucket&apos;s New Year&quot;    (Original air date January 1, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Quack&quot;   A woman commits suicide after being robbed by a phony Dr. Schulte, owner of the Los Angeles College of Psychotherapeutics. (Original air date October 12, 1950.) NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - Maxwell House Coffee Time <br /> George Burns and Gracie Allen decide to board a returning soldier in their home. (Original air date January 3, 1946. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Quiet, Please <br /> &quot;Rain On New Year&apos;s Eve&quot;    The writer of a horror movie gets in the last word.  (Original air date December 31, 1947. Mutual network.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Mercury Theatre <br /> &quot;Hell on Ice&quot;    A gripping dramatization of the true story of a 19th-century expedition to the North Pole, and its terrible fate. (Original broadcast date October 10, 1938. CBS network.)</p>
</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 25, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/759 - December 25, 2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description>
	<p>0:00:00 - The First Nighter Program <br /> &quot;Little Town Of Bethlehem&quot;   (Original air date December 23, 1945. NBC network.) (Running time 27:46)</p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Duffy&apos;s Tavern <br /> Archie is fed up with the holiday, until he receives a visit from a stranger.    (Original air date December 22, 1948. NBC network.) (Running time 28:56)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> Christmas in Dodge City.    (Original air date December 20, 1952. NBC network.) (Running time 27:53)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - The Six-Shooter <br /> A western &quot;A Christmas Carol&quot; with Jimmy Stewart. (Original air date December 20, 1953, NBC network.) (Running time 28:58)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop <br /> &quot;The Day They Gave Babies Away&quot;   A Christmas story about six orphans who must find news homes. (Original air date December 21, 1946. CBS network.)(Running time 29:48)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - The Cavalcade Of America <br /> &quot;A Child Is Born&quot;     An original nativity play, by poet Stephen Vincent Benét. (Original air date December 21, 1942. NBC red network.)(Running time 29:27)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Our Miss Brooks <br /> &quot;The Magic Christmas Tree&quot;     (Original air date December 25, 1949. CBS network.) (Running time 27:20)</p>
	<p>3:30:00 - Philco Radio Time <br /> Bing Crosby leads everyone in Christmas hymns such as &quot;Adeste Fideles&quot;, and presents a moving Christmas play titled, &quot;The Small One.&quot;  (Original air date December 25, 1946, ABC network.) (Running time 27:19)</p>

</description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 24, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/758 - December 24, 2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> 
	<p>0:00:00 - Fibber McGee and Molly <br /> Fibber paints his Christmas tree white. Teeny and The King&apos;s Men sing &quot;The Night Before Christmas.&quot; (Original air date December 18, 1945. NBC network.) (Running time 27:00)</p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Father Knows Best <br /> Sometimes called &quot;Stranded in a snowstorm&quot;; the Anderson family has different ideas of how each would like to spend Christmas. (Original air date December 24, 1953, NBC network.) (Running time 28:07)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - The Columbia Workshop <br /> &quot;Bread On The Waters&quot;     (Original air date December 22, 1938. CBS network.) (Running time 29:49)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - The Greatest Story Ever Told <br /> &quot;No Room At The Inn&quot;. The story of the Nativity, based on the book by Fulton Oursler of the life of Jesus.      (Original air date December 21, 1947. ABC network.)(Running time 24:42)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - Lum &amp; Abner <br /> &quot;Traditional Christmas Story&quot; A walk in the woods is something more. (Original air date December 24, 1944, NBC network.) (Running time 14:42)</p>
	<p>2:15:00 - The Challenge Of The Yukon <br /> A young boy gets a puppy for Christmas, thanks to Sergeant Preston.  (Original air date December 19, 1946. WXYZ station.)(Running time 14:18)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Family Theatre <br /> &quot;Lullaby Of Christmas&quot;.  A Christmas fable about a young boy who could not speak, at the time of the birth of Jesus.  (Original air date December 19, 1951. Mutual network)(Running time 29:56)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Campbell Playhouse <br /> &quot;A Christmas Carol&quot;    Lionel Barrymore in his defining role, in Charles Dicken&apos;s classic ghost story.   (Original air date December 24, 1939. CBS network.)(Running time 54:12)</p>
 </description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 18, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/757 - December 18, 2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> Empty for this first episode. </description>
<itunes:keywords>
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Missing Mouse Matter&quot;   A singing mouse named Gulliver has been kidnapped — wait, a singing mouse? (Original air date December 23, 1956. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - Suspense <br /> &quot;The Cave&quot;   A fanciful story about two boys who discover pirates in a magical cave on Christmas Day.  (Original air date December 20, 1955. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Where&apos;d They Go?&quot;   Marshal Dillon and Chester ride out to arrest a man accused of robbery but are sidetracked by charitable needs and deeds.   (Original air date December 29, 1957. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big Little Jesus&quot;   A Los Angeles Mission reports the statue of Jesus has been stolen the day before Christmas. (Original air date December 22, 1953.) NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Eternal Light <br /> &quot;Anne Frank: The Diary Of A Young Girl&quot;   A radio adaptation of the famous journal by Anne Frank, a Jewish teenager who chronicled her family&apos;s life in hiding under Nazi persecution. (Original air date December 14, 1952. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Rocky Fortune <br /> &quot;The Plot To Murder Santa Claus&quot;     Frank Sinatra stars as detective Rocky Fortune; there&apos;s a plot to murder Santa Claus.  (Original air date December 22, 1953. NBC network.)</p>
	<p>2:52:00 - excerpt New World A&apos;Coming (Original air date December 24, 1944.)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - The Shadow <br /> &quot;Cold Death&quot;  Orson Welles stars as The Shadow, entering the mind of a Scrooge-like slumlord who keeps the press out of his shantytown with gangsters.  (Original broadcast date December 19, 1937.  Mutual network.)</p>
<p>3:00:00 - Broadway Is My Beat <br /> Nick Norman is just out of Sing Sing after fifteen years and is scheduled to play Santa Claus for the P.A.L. (Original broadcast date December 24, 1949. CBS network.)</p>
</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>December 11, 2022</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle/>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/wamu.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/756-11Dec2022.mp3" length="101265408" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>03:59:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> 
	<p>0:00:00 - Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar <br /> &quot;The Valentine Matter&quot;  Parts 4 and 5.   Bob Bailey as Johnny Dollar, investigating  the murder of Danny Valentine. (Original air date November 3 and 4, 1955. CBS network.) </p>
	<p>0:30:00 - My Favorite Husband <br /> Lucille Ball as Liz Cooper; there are only seven shopping days until Christmas. What is George planning to give Liz for Christmas? (Original air date December 16, 1949. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:00:00 - Gunsmoke <br /> &quot;Cheap Labor&quot;  A peaceful man is threatened by a jealous brother of his fiancée.   (Original air date June 17, 1956. CBS network.)</p>
	<p>1:20:00 - Excerpt from &quot;The Sound of Jazz&quot; featuring Billie Holiday&apos;s &quot;Fine and Mellow&quot; (Original air date December 8, 1957)</p>
	<p>1:30:00 - Dragnet <br /> &quot;The Big 38&quot;   A brutal story of a store clerk shot and murdered. (Original air date October 5, 1950.) NBC network.)(Running time 26:04)</p>
	<p>2:00:00 - The Challenge Of The Yukon <br /> &quot;The Man With The Red Coat&quot;  A little girl confuses Sergeant Preston&apos;s red Mountie suit with Santa&apos;s costume. (Original air date December 22, 1948. ABC network.)</p>
	<p>2:30:00 - Suspense <br /> &quot;Out For Christmas&quot;    Raymond Burr stars as an ex-con who gets out of jail just before Christmas, looking for trouble.  (Original air date December 21, 1958. CBS network.)(Running time 23:29)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Big Town <br /> Edward G. Robinson stars as Steve Wilson of the The Illustrated Press, who investigates a suspicious Christmas charity racket.  (Original broadcast date December 21, 1937. CBS network.)(Running time 26:26)</p>
	<p>3:00:00 - Quiet Please <br /> &quot;Berlin, 1945&quot;   A great Christmas story about a group of American G.I.&apos;s celebrating the holiday in conquered Germany. (Original broadcast date December 26, 1948. ABC network.)(Running time 28:59)</p>
 </description>
<itunes:keywords>Old Time Radio</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>About Jekyll</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle>Podcast Example: About Jekyll</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/jekyll-logo.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/jekyll-hyde.mp3" length="461569" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 01:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> Just a test site with audio posting. Show Notes Available at https://michael833.github.io/test2.html.</description>
<itunes:keywords>jekyll</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block/>
</item>


<item>
<title>What is Atom?</title>
<itunes:author/>
<itunes:subtitle>Podcast Example: What is Atom?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary/>
<itunes:image href="https://michael833.github.io/assets/logo.png"/>
<enclosure url="https://michael833.github.io/audio/track1.mp3" length="1029183" type="audio/mp3"/>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 01:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<description> All about atom and rss - test. Show Notes Available at https://michael833.github.io/test1.html.</description>
<itunes:keywords>atom</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>